**The Meet Group Inc.**

Privacy Policy
==============

_Last Updated: October 8, 2024_

The Meet Group, Inc., its brands, affiliates, and subsidiaries ("**TMG**"," "**we**," "**our**," or "**us**") values your privacy. This Privacy Policy ("**Policy**") describes how TMG collects, uses, discloses, and otherwise processes personal information described in this Policy, as well as the rights and choices you have regarding such personal information.

For additional information about the privacy choices you have regarding your personal information, please review [Section 6. Your Privacy Choices](#your_privacy_choices), as well as [Section 13. Additional Privacy Information for Certain Jurisdictions](#additional_privacy_information), which includes additional information about privacy rights for residents of certain jurisdictions. If you are a resident of California, please refer to [Section 13.B. Additional Information for California Residents](#additional_information_for_california_residents) for information about the categories of personal information we collect and your rights under California privacy laws.

When you create a profile on one of our Services, your personal information may be visible also to users of our other Services, and other applications we own and other applications and websites not owned by us with which we share our live platform. For a list of our current live partners, click [here](https://talent.tagged.com/partner-policy-tagged.html). For users of Skout or MeetMe: When you create a profile on Skout or MeetMe, your personal information may be visible to users on both platforms.

By using our Services (as defined below), you agree that your personal information will be handled as described in this Policy. Your use of our Services and any dispute over privacy, is subject to this Policy and our [Terms and Conditions](https://secure.tagged.com/terms_of_service.html), including their applicable terms governing limitations on damages and the resolution of disputes.

**Table of Contents**

1. Scope
2. Personal Information Collected
3. Purposes for Collection and Processing
4. Disclosures of Personal Information
5. Cookies, Targeting, and Analytics
6. Your Privacy Choices
7. External Links and Features
8. User Generated Content
9. Security
10. Children's Privacy
11. Changes to this Policy
12. Contact Us
13. Additional Privacy Information for Certain Jurisdictions

**1\. Scope**

Except as otherwise described below, this Policy applies to the personal information TMG collects and processes related to: visitors of our website where this Policy is posted, including any of our websites that link to or post this Policy (the "**Sites**"); individuals who download and use our mobile applications ("**Mobile Apps**"); individuals who register for or participate in our events, surveys, research, promotions, and sweepstakes conducted by us; current, former, and prospective customers, vendors and service providers, and business partners; and individuals who communicate or otherwise interact or engage with us or the services available through our Sites, Mobile Apps, or other online services (collectively referred to as the "**Services**").

**2\. Personal Information Collected**

As further described below, we may collect personal information directly from you, from third-party sources, and automatically through your use of our Services.

**Personal Information Collected Directly from You**. While the personal information we collect varies depending upon your use of our Services and our interactions with you, in general, we may collect the following categories of personal information directly from you:

* **Contact Information**. When you contact us, including if you send us a message or sign up to learn more about our Services, we may collect your name, email address, phone number, or other similar identifiers, as well as your message, the nature of your inquiry, and any other information you so choose to provide.
    
* **Account and Profile Information**. When you sign up for an account in connection with our Services, we may collect your name, email address, phone number, address (e.g., zip code), username and password, date of birth, ethnicity, and gender, profile image and photo, and billing address information, as well as any other information provided in connection with creating or maintaining your account, or that you otherwise submit to us through your account.
    
* **Purchases, Payments, and Rewards**. When you make a purchase or payment through our Services, we may collect information such as payment type, payment card details, billing, shipping address, purchasing information, and any other financial or commercial-related information necessary for facilitating our Services.
    
* **Communications and Interactions**. When you email, call, or otherwise communicate or interact with us or with other TMG users, including if you sign up for our mailing lists, complete forms on our Sites or Mobile Apps, interact with our social media pages, post a review or testimonial, submit content in any online discussion groups, or otherwise enter information into public-facing comment fields, blogs, or community forums sponsored by or affiliated with TMG, we may collect, receive, and maintain records of your contact details, communications and interactions, your posts or submissions, and our responses, if applicable.
    
* **Promotional Information**. If you agree to receive marketing communications from us, we may collect your name, email address, phone number, preferences, and if relevant, information about your account and profile, including the Services and features you use. If you participate in special activities, offers, programs, or promotions we offer, we may also collect certain contact details, your age, and any other information that may be required by law. If you win a promotion, we may also need to collect certain tax information and/or waivers and releases, depending on the prize.
    
* **Responses and Feedback**. If you participate in surveys, questionnaires, or research activities or initiatives conducted by us, such as for user satisfaction or other similar purposes, we may collect your responses and feedback, and any other information you choose to provide.
    
* **Events and Registration Details**. We may also collect personal information related to your participation in our events as well as other requests that you submit to us related to our Services. For example, if you register for or attend an event that we host or sponsor, we may collect information related to your registration for and participation in such event.
    
* **Preferences and Other Requests**. We also may collect information about your preferences, including communications preferences, preferences related to your use of our Services, and any other preferences or requests you provide when interacting with us.
    
* **Business Development Information**. To assess and pursue potential business opportunities, we may collect and receive personal information about current, former, and prospective customers, vendors and service providers, business partners, including contact information and other similar identifiers, company and professional information, and communications records.
    
* **Biometric Information Collected with Your Consent for Limited Purposes**. We do not generally collect biometric information from users. However, in certain circumstances, we may ask you to consent to our processing biometric information and identifiers to fight fraudulent accounts (including bots) and other misuse of our Services, age estimation and verification purposes and profile verification purposes. Further details are provided in our Biometric Data Specific Notice which can be accessed [here](https://terms.hi5.com/biometrics).

**Personal Information Collected from Third Parties**. We may also collect and receive certain personal information about you from third party sources, such as from business partners, customers and other TMG users, data analytics and marketing providers, operating systems and social media platforms, public databases, and vendors and service providers who provide services or perform functions on our behalf. For example, we may collect your name, contact details, and other similar information from business partners and vendors and service providers for purposes of providing our Services. In addition, we may collect the following information from third-party sources:

* **Social Media and Platform Registration Information**. While using our Services, you may choose to share information or content, log into, or sign on to the Services through various social media platforms, social networking services, or other third-party features or integrated services. When you connect to our Services using your social media accounts or other similar integrated services and features, we may collect or receive personal information about you that you have provided to that social media account, service, or feature. For example, we may collect information from your account and profile, such as your name, email, user ID, profile picture, friend list, and other similar information available on your profile. You should check your privacy settings on each social media platform, feature, or integrated service to better understand how your personal information may be used, disclosed, or otherwise processed by these parties.
    
* **Referral Information**. We may offer you the ability to invite friends or refer other users to access or use our Services. In doing so, we may collect and receive certain personal information about you, including from other current or prospective TMG users and customers who similarly engage in these activities.
    
* **Lead and Prospect Information**. We may receive lead and prospect information from third parties about prospective customers that may be interested in our Services. We may also engage with third parties to enhance or update our customer information. For example, we may receive certain personal information from data analytics and marketing providers for purposes of reaching new customers, or from business partners, vendors and service providers for purposes of providing our Services.

**Personal Information Collected Automatically**. We and our third-party service providers may automatically collect or derive personal information about you related to your use of our Services, including through the use of cookies, pixel tags, and other similar technologies. The personal information we may automatically collect includes:

* **Device and Browsing Information**. When you use our Services, we may collect browser type, domain name, page views, access times, date/time stamps, operating system, language, device type, unique ID, Internet service provider, referring and exiting URLs, clickstream data, operating system, language, and similar device and browsing information.
    
* **Activities and Usage**. We also may collect activity information related to your use of the Services, such as information about the links clicked, searches, features used, items viewed, time spent within the Services, your interactions with us and others within the Services, and other similar activity and usage information.
    
* **Location Information**. We also may collect or derive general location information about you, such as through your IP address.

For more information about our use of cookies and other similar technologies, please see [Section 5. Cookies, Targeting, and Analytics](#cookies_targeting_analytics) below.

**3\. Purposes for Collection and Processing**

Generally, we may collect, use, disclose and otherwise process the categories of personal information we collect for the following purposes:

* **Services and Support**. To provide and operate our Services, manage your account, communicate with you about your use of the Services, provide troubleshooting, technical support, or for similar support purposes, and to respond to your inquiries, fulfill your requests, facilitate payment processing, and to otherwise run our day-to-day operations.
    
* **Analytics and Improvement**. To better understand how users access and use the Services, and for other research and analytical purposes, such as to evaluate and improve the Site, our Services, and business operations, including to develop our Services and its features, and for internal quality control and training purposes.
    
* **Communication**. To respond to your questions, send you requested materials and newsletters, as well as information and materials regarding our Services and offerings. We may also use this information to send administrative information to you, for example, information regarding the Services and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies.
    
* **Customization and Personalization**. To tailor content we may send or display on the Services, including to offer location customization and to otherwise personalize your experiences and offerings.
    
* **Marketing and Advertising**. For marketing, advertising, and promotional purposes. For example, to send you promotional information about our Services, including information about TMG events, webinars, presentations, sales, deals, discounts, and new offerings, as well as any other information that you sign up to receive.
    
* **Research and Surveys**. To administer surveys and questionnaires, such as for market research, user satisfaction, or other similar purposes.
    
* **Insight Development and Data Enhancement**. We may combine personal information collected through the Services with other information that we or third parties collect about you in other contexts. In most cases, the information that we may combine with the personal information collected through the Services for market research, such as demographic information, does not directly identify consumers.
    
* **Planning and Managing Events**. For event planning and other management-related purposes, such as event registration and attendance, connecting you with other event attendees and TMG users, and contacting you about relevant events, presentations, and our Services. We may also use personal information for purposes of facilitating special events, sweepstakes, contests, and promotions, which may have their own specific rules to participate.
    
* **Security and Protection of Rights**. To protect the Services and our business operations, our rights and those of our stakeholders and investors, to prevent and detect fraud, unauthorized activities and access, and other misuse of our Site, including where we believe necessary to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety or legal rights of any person or third party, or violations of our Terms and Conditions.
    
* **Compliance and Legal Process**. To comply with applicable legal or regulatory obligations, including as part of a judicial proceeding, to respond to a subpoena, warrant, court order, or other legal process, or as part of an investigation or request, whether formal or informal, from law enforcement or a governmental authority.
    
* **Auditing, Reporting, and Other Internal Operations**. To conduct financial, tax and accounting audits, audits, and assessments of our operations, including our privacy, security, and financial controls, as well as for risk and compliance purposes. We may also use personal information to maintain appropriate business records and enforce our policies and procedures.
    
* **General Business and Operational Support**. To assess and implement mergers, acquisitions, reorganizations, bankruptcies, and other business transactions such as financings, and to administer our business, accounting, auditing, compliance, recordkeeping, and legal functions.

**4\. Disclosures of Personal Information**

We may disclose the personal information we collect for the purposes described above, to provide you our Services, to respond to and fulfill your requests, as otherwise directed or consented to by you, and with the following recipients:

* **Brands, Affiliates, and Subsidiaries**. We may disclose the personal information we collect with our brands, corporate affiliates, and subsidiaries.
    
* **Business Partners**. In some circumstances, TMG may partner with other businesses to offer its Services, including to facilitate certain programs or special offerings, and we may disclose personal information to those business partners.
    
* **Vendors and Services Providers**. We may disclose the personal information we collect to vendors and service providers who perform functions on our behalf, such as IT and website hosting, payment processors, marketing and marketing research providers, customer support, data storage, data analytics providers, auditors, consultants, advisors and agents, and legal counsel.
    
* **Other TMG Users**. With other users of the Services in the context of specific features that are social in nature. For example, if you invite others to use our Services, or if you submit or make available information through our public-facing, interactive features, community forums, or discussion blogs, including when you post reviews or testimonials, certain personal information, may be available to, and searchable by, other users of the Services.
    
* **Third Party Marketing and Analytics Providers**. We may also disclose your personal information, such as device and browsing, and activities and usage information, to third party marketing and data analytics providers, and other companies who provide marketing, advertising, campaign management, or analytics services on our behalf.

We may also disclose your personal information in the following circumstances:

* **In Support of Business Transfers**. If we or our affiliates are or may be acquired by, merged with, or invested in by another company, or if any of our assets are or may be transferred to another company, whether as part of a bankruptcy or insolvency proceeding or otherwise, we may disclose or transfer the personal information we have collected from you with or to the other company in accordance with applicable laws. We may also disclose certain personal information as necessary prior to the completion of such a transaction or other corporate transaction such as a financing or restructuring, to lenders, auditors, and third-party advisors, including attorneys and consultants.
    
* **Compliance and Legal Obligations**. We may also disclose personal information to third parties to the extent required by applicable law and legal obligations. For example, we may disclose information in response to subpoenas, court orders, and other lawful requests by regulators, government entities, and law enforcement, including responding to national security or law enforcement disclosure requirements, or as otherwise required by law or legal process. In addition, and if applicable, we may disclose the names of sweepstakes and contests winners in accordance with applicable law.
    
* **Security and Protection of Rights**. Where we believe doing so is necessary to protect the Services, our rights and property, or the rights, property, and safety of others. For example, we may disclose personal information to (i) prevent, detect, investigate, and respond to fraud, unauthorized activities and access, illegal activities, and misuse of the Services, (ii) situations involving potential threats to the health, safety, or legal rights of any person or third party, or (iii) enforce, detect, investigate, and take action in response to violations of our Terms and Conditions. We may also disclose personal information related to litigation and other legal claims or proceedings in which we are involved, as well as for our internal accounting, auditing, compliance, recordkeeping, and legal functions.
    
* **Other Disclosures**. We may disclose personal information in other ways not described above that we notify you of or that we obtain your consent for, or that are otherwise authorized or required by law.

Notwithstanding anything else described in this Policy, we may use and disclose aggregated, deidentified, and other non-identifiable data related to our business and the Services for quality control, analytics, research, development, and other purposes. Where we use, disclose or process deidentified data (data that is no longer reasonably linked or linkable to an identified or identifiable natural person, household, or personal or household device) we will maintain and use the information in deidentified form and not to attempt to reidentify the information, except in order to determine whether our deidentification processes are reasonable and adequate pursuant to applicable privacy laws.

**5\. Cookies, Targeting, and Analytics**

We and our third-party service providers use cookies, pixels, local storage objects, log files, and other mechanisms to automatically collect browsing, activity, device, and other similar information within our Services. We use this information to, for example, analyze and understand how users access, use, and interact with our Services, to identify and resolve bugs and errors in our Services, to assess secure, protect, optimize and improve the performance of our Services, as well as for marketing and analytics purposes, and to personalize content in our Services. To manage your preferences regarding cookies, targeted advertising, and other similar tracking mechanisms within our Services, please see [Section 6. Your Privacy Choices](#your_privacy_choices) below.

**Cookies**. "Cookies" are small text files stored on a user's device (such as a computer or smartphone) by a website they visit. Cookies are created by the website's server and sent to the user's browser, where it is stored for future reference. Some cookies allow us to make it easier for you to navigate our Services, while others are used to enable a faster log-in process, support the security and performance of the Services, or allow us to track aggregate and statistical information about user activity within the Services.

**Pixel Tags**. Pixel tags (sometime called web beacons or clear GIFs) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies. While cookies are stored locally on your device, pixel tags are embedded invisibly within web pages and online content. We may use these, in connection with our Services to, among other things, track the activities of users, and help us manage content and compile usage statistics. We may also use these in our emails to let us know when they have been opened or forwarded, so we can track response rates and gauge the effectiveness of our communications.

**Log Files**. We may collect certain activity information from log files. Log file information is automatically collected when you access our Sites. We record certain information from these log files, including web requests, IP address, browser type and version, language information, referring and exiting URLs, links clicked, pages viewed and other similar information.

**Third Party Analytics**. We may use automated devices, applications, and tools, such as Google Analytics, which are operated by third party companies, to evaluate usage of our Services. These third-party companies may use cookies, pixels, and other tracking technologies to collect usage data about our Services and provide us with reports and metrics that help us evaluate usage of our Services and enhance performance and user experiences. To learn more about Google's privacy practices, please review the Google Privacy Policy at https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/. You can also download the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on to prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

**Third-Party Advertising**. We work with third-party ad networks, analytics, marketing partners, mobile ad networks, and others ("third-party ad companies") to personalize content and display advertising within our Services, as well as to manage our advertising on third-party websites. We and these third-party ad companies may use cookies, pixels tags, SDKs, and other tools to collect browsing and activity information within our Services (as well as on third-party sites and services), as well as IP address, unique ID, cookie and advertising IDs, and other online identifiers. We and these third-party ad companies use this information to provide you more relevant ads and content within our Services and on third-party sites, and to evaluate the success of such ads and content.

**Cross-Device Use**. We and our third-party service providers may use the information we collect about you (whether directly from our Sites or Mobile Apps, through your device(s), or from third party sources) to help us and our third-party service providers identify other devices you use (e.g., a mobile phone, tablet, other computer, etc.). We and our third-party service providers may also use the cross-device use and other information we learn about you to serve targeted advertising or personalize content within our Services. To opt-out of cross-device advertising, you may follow the instructions set forth below. Please note, if you opt-out of these targeted advertising cookies, the opt-out will be specific to the web browser, app, or device from which you accessed the opt-out. If you use multiple devices or web browsers, you will need to opt-out each browser or device that you use.

**Custom Lists and Matching**. We may share or make available certain customer list information (such as your name, email address and other contact information) with third parties so that we can better target ads and content to you across third party websites, platforms and services. In some cases, these third parties may help us to enhance our customer lists with additional demographic or other similar information so we can better target our advertising and marketing campaigns.

**6\. Your Privacy Choices**

**Managing Your Preferences**. We make available several ways for you to manage your preferences and privacy choices, as described below:

* **Account and Profile**. You can review and update some of the personal information we maintain about you by logging into your account and updating your account and profile information.
    
* **Marketing Communications**. We may send periodic promotional emails, content, or other similar communications to you. You may opt-out of these communications by following the instructions provided to you in the communication. If you opt-out of receiving promotional content from us, we may still send you communications about your account or any services you have requested or received from us. Additionally, you can manage your communication preferences in your account and profile settings.
    
* **Push Notifications**. You can manage the type of push notifications you receive from us by adjusting your mobile device settings or by modifying the settings within our Mobile Apps.

**Cookie Preferences/Targeted Advertising**. We also make available several ways for you to manage your preferences regarding cookies, targeted advertising, and other similar tracking mechanisms within our Services. Many of these choices are browser and device specific, which means that you may need to set the preference for each browser and device you use to access our Services. In addition, if you delete or block cookies, you may need to reapply these preferences to each browser and/or device. Further, opting out of cookies and advertising does not mean that you will no longer receive advertising content from us, and you may continue to receive generic or "contextual" ads from us.

* **Cookie Settings**. To prevent cookies from tracking your activity on our Sites or visits across multiple websites, you can set your browser to block certain cookies or notify you when a cookie is set. You can also delete cookies. The "Help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your device from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to delete cookies. Visitors to our Sites who disable cookies will be able to browse the Site, but some features may not function.
    
* **Browser Signals**. To the extent required by applicable law, if our Sites detect that your browser is transmitting an opt-out preference signal, such as a "global privacy control" (or GPC) signal, we will apply that signal to opt that particular browser on your device out of targeting cookies on our Sites. If you come to our Sites from a different device or from a different browser on the same device, you will need to apply GPC for that browser and/or device as well.
    
* **Industry Ad Choice Programs**. You can also control how participating third-party ad companies use the information that they collect about your visits to our Sites and those of third parties, in order to display more relevant targeted advertising to you. For more information and to opt out of receiving targeted ads from participating third-party ad networks go to:
    
    * **U.S. Users**: [aboutads.info/choices](http://aboutads.info/choices) (Digital Advertising Alliance) (You can also download the DAA AppChoices tool in order to help control interest-based advertising on Mobile Apps on your mobile device).

Residents of certain jurisdictions may have additional rights to their personal information, as set forth below in [Section 13. Additional Privacy Information for Certain Jurisdictions](#additional_privacy_information).

**7\. External Links and Features**

Our Services may contain links to third-party websites or features or provide certain third-party connections or integrated services. Any access to and use of such linked websites or features is not governed by this Policy, but instead is governed by the privacy policies of those third parties. We are not responsible for the information practices of such third parties, including their collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information. You should review the privacy policies and terms for any third parties before proceeding to those websites or using those features.

**8\. User Generated Content**

We may offer public-facing interactive features, community forums, or discussion blogs in connection with our Services that enable you to share information about the Services, or other issues of interest (e.g., reviews, testimonials, and questions). You should be aware that any communications you submit or post to any such interactive features on the Services may be viewable and searchable by others, including TMG users and the public. By submitting or posting to such public-facing, interactive features you acknowledge that you have no expectation of privacy or confidentiality in the content you submit for such features, whether or not it contains personal information about you.

**9\. Security**

We have implemented reasonable precautions aimed to protect the information we collect from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Please be aware that despite our best efforts, no data security measures can guarantee security.

**10\. Children's Privacy**

Our Services are not designed for children, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of eighteen (18). If we learn that personal information has been collected on the Services from persons under the age of 18, then we will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. If you are a parent or legal guardian and you believe we have collected your child's information in violation of applicable law, please contact us using the contact information below.

**11\. Changes to this Policy**

This Policy is current as of the date set forth above. We may change, update, or modify this Policy from time to time, so please be sure to check back periodically. We will post any updates to this Policy here. If we make any changes to this Policy that materially affect our practices regarding our use of the personal information we have previously collected from you, we will notify endeavor to provide you with notice, such as by emailing you or by posting prominent notice on our Sites, in our Mobile Apps, or within the Services.

**12\. Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or our privacy practices, you may email us at [support@themeetgroup.com](mailto:support@themeetgroup.com) or contact us at:

The Meet Group, Inc.  
100 Union Square Drive  
New Hope, PA 18938

**13\. Additional Privacy Information for Certain Jurisdictions**

Residents of certain jurisdictions have additional rights under applicable privacy laws, as described in this section.

**A. U.S. State Privacy Laws**

If you are a resident of California, please review [Section 13.B, Additional Information for California Residents](#additional_information_for_california_residents) below for a description of your rights pursuant to California privacy laws.

Residents of certain U.S. states may have additional rights under applicable privacy laws, subject to certain limitations, which may include:

* **Access**. To confirm whether we are processing their personal information and to obtain a copy of their personal information in a portable and, to the extent technically feasible, readily usable format.
    
* **Deletion**. To delete their personal information provided to or obtained by us.
    
* **Correction**. The right to correct inaccuracies in their personal information, taking into account the nature and purposes of the processing of the personal information.
    
* **Opt**\-**Out**. To opt out of certain types of processing, including:
    
    * to opt out of the "sale" of their personal information;
        
    * to opt out of targeted advertising by us; and
        
    * to opt out of any processing of personal information for purposes of making decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects.

You may submit a request to exercise most of your privacy rights under U.S. state privacy laws by contacting us at [support@themeetgroup.com](mailto:support@themeetgroup.com). To opt out of sales and targeted advertising by us, you can adjust your cookies settings or download an opt-out preference signal, such as the "global privacy control" (or GPC). Please see [Section 6. Your Privacy Choices](#your_privacy_choices) above for additional information about the privacy choices we provide and how to exercise them.

We will respond to your request as required under applicable U.S. privacy law(s). When you submit a request, we will take steps to verify your identity and request by matching the information provided by you with the information we have in our records. In some cases, we may request additional information in order to verify your identity, or where necessary to process your request. If we are unable to verify your identity after a good faith attempt, we may deny the request and, if so, will explain the basis for the denial. If we deny your request, you may appeal our decision by emailing us.

To the extent required under applicable U.S. privacy laws, you may also designate someone as an authorized agent to submit requests and act on your behalf. Authorized agents will be required to provide proof of their authorization in their first communication with us, and we may also require that the relevant consumer directly verify their identity and the authority of the authorized agent.

**B. Additional Information for California Residents**

This section of the Policy provides additional information for California residents and describes our information practices pursuant to applicable California privacy laws, including the California Consumer Privacy Act (the "**CCPA**"). To the extent you are a California resident, and we collect "personal information" subject to the CCPA, the following applies. This section does not address or apply to our handling of our handling of publicly available information or personal information that is otherwise exempt under the CCPA.

**Categories of Personal Information Collected and Disclosed**. The following table identifies the categories of personal information we may collect about you (and may have collected in the prior 12 months), as defined by the CCPA, as well as the categories of third parties to whom we may disclose this information for a business or commercial purpose. Depending on how you use the Services, we may collect and disclose the following categories of personal information:

* **Identifiers.** Includes direct identifiers such as name, alias, email, phone number, address, user ID or username, unique personal identifier, online identifier, IP address, or other similar identifiers.
    
    **Third Party Disclosures for Business or Commercial Purposes:**
    
    * Advisors and agents
    * Affiliates and subsidiaries
    * Other TMG users
    * Data analytics providers
    * Advertising networks
    * Social networks
    * Internet service providers
    * Operating systems and platforms
    * Regulators, government entities and law enforcement
    * Others with your permission or as required by law
* **Customer Records.** Includes your account and profile information and customer records that contain personal information, such as username, account name, name, demographics and other characteristics or descriptions, contact information, and financial or payment information (i.e., payment type, payment card details, billing, and shipping address).
    
    **Third Party Disclosures for Business or Commercial Purposes:**
    
    * Advisors and agents
    * Affiliates and subsidiaries
    * Data analytics providers
    * Advertising networks
    * Social networks
    * Regulators, government entities and law enforcement
    * Others with your permission or as required by law
* **Commercial Information.** Includes records of Services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or use histories or tendencies.
    
    **Third Party Disclosures for Business or Commercial Purposes:**
    
    * Advisors and agents
    * Affiliates and subsidiaries
    * Data analytics providers
    * Advertising networks
    * Social networks
    * Regulators, government entities and law enforcement
    * Others with your permission or as required by law
* **Internet or Other Electronic Network Activity Information.** Includes, but is not limited to, browsing history, clickstream data, search history, and information regarding interactions with our Sites, Mobile Apps, and the Services, advertisements, or emails, including other usage data related to your use of any of our Services or other similar online services.
    
    **Third Party Disclosures for Business or Commercial Purposes:**
    
    * Affiliates and subsidiaries
    * Data analytics providers
    * Advertising networks
    * Social networks
    * Internet service providers
    * Operating systems and platforms
    * Regulators, government entities and law enforcement
    * Others with your permission or as required by law
* **Location Data.** Such as general location information about a particular individual or device.
    
    **Third Party Disclosures for Business or Commercial Purposes:**
    
    * Affiliates and subsidiaries
    * Other TMG users
    * Data analytics providers
    * Advertising networks
    * Social networks
    * Internet service providers, and operating systems and platforms
    * Regulators, government entities and law enforcement
    * Others with your permission or as required by law
* **Audio, Electronic, Visual, or Similar Information.** Includes, but is not limited to, information collected via call recordings if you are interacting with us in a customer service capacity or if you call us on a recorded line, recorded meetings and webinars, videos, photographs, and user profile images.
    
    **Third Party Disclosures for Business or Commercial Purposes:**
    
    * Advisors and agents
    * Affiliates and subsidiaries
    * Regulators, government entities and law enforcement
    * Others with your permission or as required by law
* **Professional Information.** Includes, but is not limited to, job title, company name, business email, business phone number, and other similar professional-related information.
    
    **Third Party Disclosures for Business or Commercial Purposes:**
    
    * Advisors and agents
    * Affiliates and subsidiaries
    * Regulators, government entities and law enforcement
    * Others with your permission or as required by law
* **Inferences.** Such as inferences drawn from any of the information described in this section about a consumer including inferences reflecting the consumer’s preferences, characteristics, behaviors, attitudes, abilities, and aptitudes.
    
    **Third Party Disclosures for Business or Commercial Purposes:**
    
    * Affiliates and subsidiaries
    * Regulators, government entities and law enforcement
    * Data analytics providers
    * Others with your permission or as required by law
* **Protected Classifications.** We may collect some information that is considered a protected classification under California or federal law, which may include, but not be limited to your ethnicity, gender, age, and date of birth.
    
    **Third Party Disclosures for Business or Commercial Purposes:**
    
    * Affiliates and subsidiaries
    * Other TMG users
    * Regulators, government entities and law enforcement
    * Others with your permission or as required by law
* **Sensitive Personal Information.** In some circumstances, we may collect account log-in information, payment card information and related details, precise geolocation data, racial or ethnic origin, messages and content shared between users, and personal information collected and analyzed concerning a consumer’s health, sex life, or sexual orientation. Additionally, if you win a contest, promotion, or sweepstakes, we may also collect certain government-issued identifiers, such as social security number or driver’s license number, in accordance with applicable law.
    
    **Third Party Disclosures for Business or Commercial Purposes:**
    
    * Affiliates and subsidiaries
    * Regulators, government entities and law enforcement
    * Others with your permission or as required by law

**Sources of Personal Information**. We generally collect personal information from the following categories of sources: directly or indirectly from you; brands, affiliates and subsidiaries; business partners; vendors and service providers; other TMG users; third-party websites and services; social media platforms and social networking websites; Internet service providers; operating systems and platforms; and marketing and data analytics providers.

**Purposes of Collection, Use, and Disclosure**. As described above in [Section 3. Purposes for Collection and Processing](#purposes_for_collection_and_processing), in general, we may collect and otherwise process the categories of personal information we collect for the following business or commercial purposes and as otherwise directed or consented to by you:

* Services and support;
* Analytics and improvement;
* Communication;
* Customization and personalization;
* Marketing and advertising;
* Research and surveys;
* Insight development and data enhancement;
* Planning and managing events;
* Security and protection of rights;
* Compliance and legal process;
* Auditing, reporting, and other internal operations; and
* General business and operational support.

**Sensitive Personal Information**. We do not collect, use, or disclose "sensitive personal information" beyond the purposes authorized by the CCPA. Accordingly, we only use and disclose sensitive personal information as reasonably necessary and proportionate: (i) to perform our services requested by you; (ii) to help ensure security and integrity, including to prevent, detect, and investigate security incidents; (iii) to detect, prevent and respond to malicious, fraudulent, deceptive, or illegal conduct; (iv) to verify or maintain the quality and safety of our services; (v) for compliance with our legal obligations; (vi) to our service providers who perform services on our behalf; and (vii) for purposes other than inferring characteristics about you.

**Retention**. We retain the personal information we collect only as reasonably necessary for the purposes described above or otherwise disclosed to you at the time of collection. For example, we will retain your account information for as long as you have an active account with us and additional information as necessary to comply with our tax, accounting and recordkeeping obligations, to provide you with the services you have requested, as well as an additional period of time as necessary to protect, defend or establish our rights, defend against potential claims, and comply with our legal obligations. In some cases, rather than delete your personal information, we may deidentify or aggregate it and use it in compliance with the CCPA.

**Sales and Sharing of Personal Information**. The CCPA defines "sale" as disclosing or making available personal information to a third-party in exchange for monetary or other valuable consideration, and "sharing" includes disclosing or making available personal information to a third-party for purposes of cross-context behavioral advertising. While we do not disclose personal information to third parties in exchange for monetary compensation, we may "sell" or "share" the following categories of personal information: identifiers; commercial information; location data; and Internet and network activity information. We may disclose these categories to third-party advertising networks, analytics providers, and social networks for purposes of marketing and advertising and to improve and measure our ad campaigns. We do not sell or share sensitive personal information, nor do we sell or share personal information about individuals we know are under age sixteen (16).

**California Privacy Rights**. The CCPA provides California residents with specific rights regarding personal information. Subject to certain conditions and exceptions, California residents have the following rights with respect to their personal information:

* **Right to Know**. You have the right to request: (i) the categories or personal information we collected about you; (ii) the categories of sources from which the personal information is collected; (iii) our business or commercial purposes for collecting, selling, or sharing personal information; (iv) the categories of third parties to whom we have disclosed personal information; and (v) a copy of the specific pieces of personal information we have collected about you.
    
* **Right to Delete**. You have the right to request we delete personal information we have collected from you.
    
* **Right to Correct**. You have the right to request that we correct inaccuracies in your personal information.
    
* **Right to Opt-Out of Sales and Sharing**. You have the right to opt-out of "sales" and "sharing" of your personal information, as those terms are defined under the CCPA.
    
* **Right to Limit Use and Disclosure**. You have the right to limit use and disclose of your sensitive personal information. However, we do not use or disclose sensitive personal information beyond the purposes authorized by the CCPA; thus, this right is not available to California residents.
    
* **Right to Non-Discrimination**. You have the right not to be subjected to discriminatory treatment for exercising any of the rights described in this section.

**Submitting CCPA Requests**. California residents may exercise their CCPA privacy rights as set forth below:

* **Right to Know, Delete, and Correct**. California residents may submit CCPA requests to access/know, delete, and correct their personal information by contacting us at [support@themeetgroup.com](mailto:support@themeetgroup.com).

When you submit a request, we will take steps to verify your identity and request by matching the information provided by you with the information we have in our records. In some cases, we may request additional information in order to verify your identity, or where necessary to process your request. If we are unable to verify your identity after a good faith attempt, we may deny the request and, if so, will explain the basis for the denial.

You may also designate someone as an authorized agent to submit requests and act on your behalf. Authorized agents will be required to provide proof of their authorization in their first communication with us, and we may also require that the relevant consumer directly verify their identity and the authority of the authorized agent.

* **Right to Opt-Out of Sales and Sharing**. To exercise your right to opt-out of the "sale" or "sharing" of your personal information, you may do so via our cookie preference manager. We will apply your opt out based upon the personal information in our records that is linked or reasonably linkable to the information provided in your request. You may also click the "_Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information_" link at the bottom of our Sites and in our Mobile Apps.

In addition, if we detect that your browser or device is transmitting an opt-out preference signal, such as the "global privacy control" (or GPC) signal, we will opt that browser or device out of cookies that result in a "sale" or "sharing" of your personal information. If you come to our Sites or use our Services from a different device or from a different browser on the same device, you will need to opt-out, or use an opt-out preference signal, for that browser and/or device as well. More information about GPC is available at: https://globalprivacycontrol.org/.

**Notice of Financial Incentive**. With respect to some of our Services, TMG may make available certain programs or offerings, and other sweepstakes, contests, or similar promotional offerings (each a "Program") which may include certain offers, rewards, discounts, services, perks, and promotions ("Rewards and Offers"). These Programs may be considered "financial incentives" under the CCPA. We provide these Rewards and Offers to participating users in order to understand and improve customer satisfaction and experiences, and to foster positive customer relationships.

As a basis for offering these Rewards and Offers, we have valued the personal information we obtain based on a reasonable and good faith calculation determined by considering expenses related to the Programs. In doing so, we value the personal information collected through the programs as the equivalent of the costs and expenses incurred to provide the program, including IT, administration, direct costs, third party costs, discounts, and service development costs.

Your personal information is collected and retained, and may be disclosed to our business partners, vendors and service providers, and other third parties, as described in this Policy, including in order (i) to administer the Program, (ii) for research and analytics purposes, (iii) to improve our products and services, (iv) to better reach you with more relevant, targeted offers, and (v) to send you TMG news, updates and offers by email, postal mail, and text message (in accordance with your communications preferences).

You may withdraw from participating in a Program at any time by contacting us using the methods described in this Policy. Please note that if you withdraw from a Program (or submit a CCPA request to delete your Program information), your participation in that Program will be terminated, which means that you will no longer be eligible to earn, use, access or redeem any Program Rewards and Offers, subject to the applicable Program terms.

**California's Shine the Light Law**. Under California's "Shine the Light" law (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.83), California residents who provide us certain personal information are entitled to request and obtain from us, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we have shared with third parties for their own direct marketing use. Such requests may be made once per calendar year for information about any relevant third-party sharing in the prior calendar year. To submit a "Shine the Light" request, you may contact us by using the methods described in this Policy. Please include in your request a current California address and your attestation that you are a California resident.

### CONSUMER HEALTH DATA PRIVACY POLICY

Effective: October 8, 2024

This Consumer Health Data Privacy Policy (“Policy”) applies to the extent The Meet Group, Inc., its brands, and subsidiaries (“we”, “our”, or “us”) process consumer health information for purposes of the Washington My Health My Data Act or other similar state laws through our websites, mobile apps, and other online services that link to or post this Policy (“Services”). This Policy supplements The Meet Group’s Privacy Policy, and we encourage you to review our full Privacy Policy carefully.

### Collection and Use of Consumer Health Data

Depending on what you choose to share when you add personal information to your profile, use the Services to communicate with other members, or use other relevant features, it is possible that you may provide us with consumer health data, such as:

* Information about your physical and mental health conditions or medications;
* Information about health care services that you have sought or are seeking;
* Information about bodily functions, vital signs or measurements;
* Reproductive or sexual health information; and
* Other information about your past, present, or future physical or mental health status.

To the extent you elect to share consumer health data, we primarily use the consumer health data to provide and operate our Services. We also may use consumer health data with your consent or as otherwise permitted by law. For additional details, please review “Purposes for Collection and Processing” in our Privacy Policy.

The Meet Group also may collect biometric information with your consent, such as where you consent to certain account verification procedures. Please see our Privacy Policy and the applicable Biometric Data Specific Notice for more information.

### Disclosure of Consumer Health Data

We may share your consumer health data as reasonably necessary to provide and operate our Services or as otherwise permitted by law. For example, we may share your personal information in the following manner:

* With other users in the context of features that are social in nature, such as when we disclose your profile information to other users, only to the extent that you choose to disclose such information;
* With vendors and service providers who perform functions on our behalf (e.g., Customer Care provider);
* With our brands, corporate affiliates and subsidiaries, such as eHarmony, Inc. and ParshipMeet Group; and
* With other third parties for legal and compliance purposes, where permitted by law, including:
    * With legal, governmental, or judicial authorities as instructed or requested by those authorities or required by applicable laws, or in relation to a legal activity, such as in response to a subpoena or investigation of suspected illicit or illegal activities, or where we believe in good faith that users may be engaged in illicit or illegal activities, or where we are bound by contract or law to enable a network partner to comply with applicable laws;
    * Where we believe doing so is necessary to protect the Services, our rights and property, or the rights, property, and safety of others;
    * With necessary third parties in connection with, or during negotiations for, an acquisition, merger, asset sale, or other similar business transfer that involves all or substantially all of our assets or functions where personal information is transferred or shared as part of the business assets; and
    * As otherwise described in our Privacy Policy; and
* With your consent or at your direction

### Your Rights

You may be entitled, in accordance with applicable law, to submit a request to know, access, or delete consumer health data we have collected about you or withdraw consent to our use of consumer health data. If we decline your request, you may have the right to appeal within a reasonable period of time after you have received notice of this decision.

You can exercise your privacy rights or request an appeal under applicable law, please contact us by submitting a request to **[support@themeetgroup.com](mailto:support@themeetgroup.com)**.

### Policy Updates

The effective date of this Policy is noted above. We reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this Policy, we will notify you here by updating the effective date, or by other means, such as e-mail, at our discretion. We recommend that you review this Policy from time to time to stay informed of our practices. Your continued use of any portion of our Services following the posting of the updated Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.

**The Meet Group Inc.**

Privacy Policy for users having their residence in the European Economic Area or the United Kingdom
===================================================================================================

_Last Updated: October 8, 2024_

The Meet Group, Inc., its brands, affiliates, and subsidiaries values your privacy. This Privacy Policy ("**Policy**") describes how The Meet Group, Inc. ("**TMG**"," "**we**," "**our**," or "**us**") collects, uses, discloses, and otherwise processes personal information (also referred to as personal data in some jurisdictions) described in this Policy, as well as the rights and choices you have regarding such personal information.

For additional information about the privacy choices you have regarding your personal information, please review Section 7. Your Privacy Choices, as well as Section 15. Additional Privacy Information for Certain Jurisdictions, which includes additional information about privacy rights for residents of certain jurisdictions.

If you are a resident of the EU/European Economic Area (EEA), please refer to Section 15.A. Additional Information for Residents of the EU/EEA for information about your rights under the General Data Protection Regulation ("GDPR").

If you are a resident of the UK, please refer to Section 15.B. Additional Information for Residents of the UK for information about your rights under the General Data Protection Regulation as incorporated into United Kingdom law by virtue of section 3 of the United Kingdom's European Union (Withdrawal) Act 2018 ("UK GDPR").

If you are a resident of Switzerland, please refer to Section 15.C. Additional Information for Swiss Residents for information about your rights under the new Swiss Data Protection Law ("nDSG").

When you create a profile on one of our Services, some of your personal information like user name, name, age, gender and sexual orientation in accordance with your privacy settings may be visible also to users of the respective Service and of our other Services, and other applications we own and other applications and websites not owned by us with which we share our live platform. These other users are be based worldwide. For a list of our current live partners, click [here](https://talent.tagged.com/partner-policy-tagged.html).

Your use of our Services, is subject to our [Terms and Conditions](https://secure.tagged.com/terms_of_service.html), including their applicable terms governing limitations on damages and the resolution of disputes.

**Table of Contents**

1. Scope
    
2. Personal Information Collected
    
3. Purposes for Collection and Processing
    
4. Disclosures of Personal Information
    
5. Transfers of personal data in the context of countries located outside the EEA/UK/CH
    
6. Cookies, Targeting, and Analytics
    
7. Your Privacy Choices
    
8. Storage Period of Personal Information
    
9. External Links and Features
    
10. User Generated Content
    
11. Security
    
12. Children's Privacy
    
13. Changes to this Policy
    
14. Contact Us
    
15. Additional Privacy Information for Certain Jurisdictions

**1\. Scope**

Except as otherwise described below, this Policy applies to the personal information TMG collects and processes related to: visitors of our website where this Policy is posted, including any of our websites that link to or post this Policy (the "**Sites**"); individuals who download and use our mobile application ("**Mobile App**", e.g. the Tagged App or the Pets App); individuals who register for or participate in our events, surveys, research, promotions, and sweepstakes conducted by us; and individuals who communicate or otherwise interact or engage with us or the services available through our Sites, Mobile App, or other online services (collectively referred to as the "**Services**").

**2\. Personal Information Collected**

As further described below, we may collect personal information directly from you, from third-party sources, and automatically through your use of our Services.

**Personal Information Collected Directly from You**. While the personal information we collect varies depending upon your use of our Services and our interactions with you, in general, we may collect the following categories of personal information directly from you:

* **Contact Information**. When you contact us, including if you send us a message or sign up to learn more about our Services, we may collect your name, email address, phone number, or other similar identifiers, as well as your message, the nature of your inquiry, and any other information you so choose to provide.
    
* **Account and Profile Information**. When you sign up for an account in connection with our Services (e.g. for a Tagged account), we may collect your name, email address, phone number, address (e.g., zip code), username and password, date of birth, and gender, sexual orientation, profile image and photo, and billing address information, as well as any other information provided in connection with creating or maintaining your account, or that you otherwise submit to us through your account.

If you have chosen a login via third party providers such as Facebook or Apple or also SMS, you do not enter an email address or a password within the registration process. Users then access our Service using the email address they provided and the password they selected (login credentials), or alternatively, using the login credentials of the third party provider.

**Registering via Facebook ("Facebook login")**

We offer single sign-on via Facebook. This offers you the option of registering via your Facebook account. If you use the function, we receive and process the following authentication data from Facebook for the registration: Your email address, profile name, gender, date of birth, and profile picture stored there. Data is transferred in this respect.

When you log in to our website or app using Facebook, Facebook will also collect data from third-party scripts, process it for Facebook analytics purposes, or forward it to third parties. Facebook's Privacy Policy outlines the data that may be collected when you use the Facebook login. This includes data about your device, your use of our Service, the websites you have visited, and the ads you have viewed. Unfortunately, you technically cannot refuse this processing in connection with our Service. If you would not like Facebook to collect data about you related to your use of our online offering and to use it for its own purposes, you should not use the Facebook login.

You can disassociate your Tagged account from your Facebook account at any time on. In this case, we would need you to provide the aforementioned access data.

Further information about the purpose and scope of the collection and the further processing and use of your data by Facebook, as well as your rights and settings options for protecting your data, is available in Facebook's Privacy Policy: [http://www.facebook.com/policy.php](http://www.facebook.com/policy.php).

**Registration/Login via Google**

If you use an Android end device, we offer you the option of registering on or logging in to our Service via your Google account. If you do this, Google Ireland Limited, Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ireland ("Google") will provide us with the data required for registration or login (email address, name, Google Account ID, and Google Account profile picture).

We have no control over the scope of the data collected by Google using the Google login. If you would not like Google to collect data about you related to your use of our online offering and to use it for its own purposes, you should not use the Google login.

Further information about the purpose and scope of the collection and the further processing and use of your data by Google, as well as your rights and settings options for protecting your data, is available in Google's Privacy Policy: [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

**Registration/Login via Apple Sign-In**

If you use an iOS end device, we offer you the option of registering on or logging in to our Service via Apple. If you choose to do so, Apple Inc., One Apple Park Way, Cupertino, California, USA, 95014 ("Apple") will provide us with the information you select and which is required for registration or login (e.g. Apple-generated email address, name).

We have no control over the scope of the data collected by Apple using the Apple login. If you would not like Apple to collect data about you related to your use of our online offering and to use it for its own purposes, you should not use the Apple login.

Further information about the purpose and scope of the collection and the further processing and use of your data by Apple, as well as your rights and settings options for protecting your data, is available in Apple's Privacy Policy: [https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/en/sign-in-with-apple/](https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/en/sign-in-with-apple/).

**When registering/logging in via telephone authentication**

When registering/logging in via telephone authentication we offer to authenticate by your mobile number, therefore you must provide us with your mobile phone number. We will then send you an SMS with a verification code that you must enter in the app to complete the registration process. When you want to log in, we will send you an SMS with a code that you can use to log into your account. In addition, a verification process will take place. This service is provided bySinch America Inc., a Delaware corporation, Legal Department, 3500 Lenox Rd NE, Ste. 1875, Atlanta, GA 30326, Georgia, USA

and is only possible if you have given us your prior consent.

Further information about the purpose and scope of the processing of your data by Google can be found in Sinch's privacy policy: [https://www.sinch.com/privacy-notice/](https://www.sinch.com/privacy-notice/)

* **Purchases, Payments, and Rewards**. When you make a purchase or payment through our Services (e.g., in connection with our Pets game feature), we may collect information such as payment type, payment card details, billing, purchasing information, and any other financial or commercial-related information necessary for facilitating our Services.
    
* **Communications and Interactions**. When you email, call, or otherwise communicate or interact with us or with other TMG users, including if you sign up for our mailing lists, complete forms on our Sites or Mobile App, interact with our social media pages, post a review or testimonial, submit content in any online discussion groups, or otherwise enter information into public-facing comment fields, blogs, or community forums sponsored by or affiliated with TMG, we may collect, receive, and maintain records of your contact details, communications and interactions, your posts or submissions, and our responses, if applicable.
    
* **Promotional Information**. If you agree to receive marketing communications from us, we may collect your name, email address, phone number, preferences, and if relevant, information about your account and profile, including the Services and features you use. If you participate in special activities, offers, programs, or promotions we offer, we may also collect certain contact details, your age, and any other information that may be required by law. If you win a promotion, we may also need to collect certain tax information and/or waivers and releases, depending on the prize.
    
* **Responses and Feedback**. If you participate in surveys, questionnaires, or research activities or initiatives conducted by us, such as for user satisfaction or other similar purposes, we may collect your responses and feedback, and any other information you choose to provide.
    
* **Events and Registration Details**. We may also collect personal information related to your participation in our events as well as other requests that you submit to us related to our Services. For example, if you register for or attend an event that we host or sponsor, we may collect information related to your registration for and participation in such event.
    
* **Preferences and Other Requests**. We also may collect information about your preferences, including communications preferences, preferences related to your use of our Services, and any other preferences or requests you provide when interacting with us.

Generally, you are not obliged to provide us with your personal information. However, the use of certain Services or aspects of our Services may require the provision of personal information, e.g. the registration for a Tagged account. If this is the case, we will point this out to you. If you do not wish to provide us with the required information, you will unfortunately not be able to use the corresponding Service.

**Personal Information Collected from Third Parties**. We may also collect and receive certain personal information about you from third-party sources, such as from business partners especially when using app store providers for purchases, other TMG users, data analytics and marketing providers, operating systems and social media platforms especially when using the above described login functions, , In addition, we may collect the following information from third-party sources:

* **Social Media and Platform Registration Information**. While using our Services, you may choose to share information or content, log into, or sign on to the Services through various social media platforms, social networking services, or other third-party features or integrated services. When you connect to our Services using your social media accounts or other similar integrated services and features, we may collect or receive personal information about you that you have provided to that social media account, service, or feature. For example, we may collect information from your account and profile, such as your name, email, user ID, profile picture, friend list, and other similar information available on your profile. You should check your privacy settings on each social media platform, feature, or integrated service to better understand how your personal information may be used, disclosed, or otherwise processed by these parties.
    
* **Referral Information**. We may offer you the ability to invite friends or refer other users to access or use our Services. In doing so, we may collect and receive certain personal information about you, including from other current or prospective TMG users and customers who similarly engage in these activities.

**Personal Information Collected Automatically**. We and our third-party service providers may automatically collect or derive personal information about you related to your use of our Services, including through the use of cookies, pixel tags, and other similar technologies. The personal information we may automatically collect includes:

* **Device and Browsing Information**. When you use our Services, we may collect browser type, domain name, page views, access times, date/time stamps, operating system, language, device type, unique ID, Internet service provider, referring and exiting URLs, clickstream data, operating system, language, and similar device and browsing information.
    
* **Activities and Usage**. We also may collect activity information related to your use of the Services, such as information about the links clicked, searches, features used, items viewed, time spent within the Services, your interactions with us and others within the Services, and other similar activity and usage information.
    
* **Location Information**. We also may collect or derive general location information about you, such as through your IP address.

For more information about our use of cookies and other similar technologies, please see Section 6. Cookies, Targeting, and Analytics below.

**3\. Purposes for Collection and Processing**

Generally, we may collect, use, disclose and otherwise process the categories of personal information we collect for the following purposes:

* **Services and Support**. To provide and operate our Services (e.g., Tagged or the Pets game feature), manage your account, communicate with you about your use of the Services, provide troubleshooting, technical support, or for similar support purposes, and to respond to your inquiries, fulfill your requests, facilitate payment processing, and to otherwise run our day-to-day operations. This includes making some of your personal information like your user ID, user name, contact details like selected in your privacy settingsvisible to users of the respective Service or our other Services, and other applications we own and other applications and websites not owned by us with which we share our live platform. TMG relies on the legal basis "performance of a contract" (Art. 6 (1) (b) of the GDPR and UK GDPR and Art. 31 (2) (b) nDSG). As far as we process your personal information to make it visible to users of our other Services, and other applications we own and other applications and websites not owned by us with which we share our live platform, TMG relies on the basis "performance of a contract" (Art. 6 (1) (b) of the GDPR and UK GDPR and Art. 31 (2) (b) nDSG).

With respect to location data, TMG relies on your consent (Art. 6 (1) (a), Art. 7 GDPR).

With respect to sexual orientation, TMG relies on your explicit consent (Art. 6 (1) (a), Art. 7, Art. 9 (2) (a) GDPR/UK GDPR) or on the exception in Art. 9 (2) (e) GDPR/UK GDPR provided that you have publicly disclosed your sexual orientation(e.g., in a live stream).

* **Analytics and Improvement**. To better understand how users access and use the Services, and for other research and analytical purposes, such as to evaluate and improve the Site, our Services, and business operations, including to develop our Services and its features, and for internal quality control and training purposes. TMG relies on the legal basis "legitimate interests" (Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR/UK GDPR and Art. 31 (1) nDSG). In this regard, TMG pursues its interest in understanding how the service performs from a business perspective.

**Communication**. To respond to your questions, send you requested materials as well as information and materials regarding our Services and offerings. We may also use this information to send administrative information to you, for example, information regarding the Services and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. TMG relies on the legal basis "performance of a contract" (Art. 6 (1) (b) GDPR/UK GDPR and Art. 31 (2) (a) nDSG) or - where no contract exists between the relevant user and TMG -- "legitimate interests" (Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR/UK GDPR and Art. 31 (1) nDSG). Where TMG relies on "legitimate interests", TMG pursues its interests in providing support as well as to answer requests to ensure user satisfaction.

* **Customization and Personalization**. To tailor content we may send or display on the Services, including to offer location customization and to otherwise personalize your experiences and offerings. TMG relies on the legal basis "performance of a contract" (Art. 6 (1) (b) of the GDPR and UK GDPR and Art. 31 (2) (b) nDSG.
    
* Social Media and other Platform Communication. To enable you to share information or content, log into, or sign on to the Services through various social media platforms, social networking services, or other third-party features or integrated services. With respect to enabling you to log into or sign onto the Services, TMG relies on the legal basis "performance of a contract" (Art. 6 (1) (b) of the GDPR and UK GDPR and Art. 31 (2) (b) nDSG). Otherwise, TMG relies on the legal basis "legitimate interests" (Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR/UK GDPR and Art. 31 (1) nDSG). In this regard, TMG pursues its interest in enabling users to initiate certain communications with social media platforms, social networking services, or other third-party features or integrated services if this is what they wish to do.
    
* **Marketing and Advertising**. For marketing, advertising, and promotional purposes. For example, to send you promotional information about our Services, including newsletters, information about TMG events, webinars, presentations, sales, deals, discounts, and new offerings, as well as any other information that you sign up to receive. TMG relies on the legal basis "consent" Art. 6 (1) (a), Art. 7 GDPR and UK GDPR and Art. 31 (1) nDSG.

For the purposes of self-advertising / direct marketing through promotional emails and/or push messages, (user) surveys and individualized guides (exclusively TMG products). (The legal basis is TMG's legitimate interest in direct marketing for its own products, as well as Section 7 (3) of the German Act against Unfair Competition (UWG).

* **Research and Surveys**. To administer surveys and questionnaires, such as for market research, user satisfaction, or other similar purposes. TMG relies on the legal basis "consent" Art. 6 (1) (a), Art. 7 GDPR and UK GDPR and Art. 31 (1) nDSG.
    
* **Insight Development and Data Enhancement**. We may combine personal information collected through the Services with other information that we or third parties collect about you in other contexts. In most cases, the information that we may combine with the personal information collected through the Services for market research, such as demographic information, does not directly identify consumers. TMG relies on the legal basis "legitimate interests" (Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR/UK GDPR and Art. 31 (1) nDSG). In this regard, TMG pursues its interest in understanding how the service performs from a business perspective.
    
* **Access and storage of information on the users end device.** We may access or store information on your end device. TMG relies on the legal basis of "consent" Art. 5 (3) e-Privacy Directive and PECR Reg. 6(4) when this is not strictly necessary for the operation of our website as well as for the provision of telemedia services expressly requested by the user.
    
* **Planning and Managing Events**. For event planning and other management-related purposes, such as event registration and attendance, connecting you with other event attendees and TMG users, and contacting you about relevant events, presentations, and our Services. We may also use personal information for purposes of facilitating special events, sweepstakes, contests, and promotions, which may have their own specific rules to participate. TMG relies on the legal basis "consent" Art. 6 (1) (a), Art. 7 GDPR and UK GDPR and Art. 31 (1) nDSG.
    
* **Security and Protection of Rights**. To protect the Services and our business operations, our rights and those of our stakeholders and investors, to prevent and detect fraud, unauthorized activities and access, and other misuse of our Site, including where we believe necessary to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety or legal rights of any person or third-party, or violations of our Terms and Conditions. TMG relies on the legal basis "legitimate interests" (Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR/UK GDPR and Art. 31 (1) nDSG. The legitimate interest of TMG and the TMG users that the TMG service is not misused for contractual and / or illegal acts of third parties. Our legitimate interest is also the protection of our own systems of securing the IT of TMG and thus ultimately the protection of personal data of the users of TMG. With respect to sexual orientation, TMG additionally relies on the legal basis establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims (Art. 9 (2) (f) GDPR/UK GDPR).
    
* **Compliance and Legal Process**. To comply with applicable legal or regulatory obligations, including statutory retention obligations or as part of a judicial proceeding, to respond to a subpoena, warrant, court order, or other legal process, or as part of an investigation or request, whether formal or informal, from law enforcement or a governmental authority. TMG relies on the legal basis of (i) "compliance with legal obligations" (Art. 6 (1) (c) GDPR/UK GDPR as well as Art. 31 (2) (a) nDSG) if this obligation stems from EU or EU Member State law, or (ii) "legitimate interest" (Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR/UK GDPR as well as Art. 31(1) nDSG) if this obligation stems from other jurisdictions. Where legitimate interests are relevant, TMG pursues its interests in complying with the legal obligations to which TMG is subject. With respect to sexual orientation, TMG additionally relies on the legal basis establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims (Art. 9 (2) (f) GDPR/UK GDPR).
    
* **Auditing, Reporting, and Other Internal Operations**. To conduct financial, tax and accounting audits, audits, and assessments of our operations, including our privacy, security, and financial controls, as well as for risk and compliance purposes. We may also use personal information to maintain appropriate business records and enforce our policies and procedures. TMG relies on the legal basis "legitimate interests" (Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR/UK GDPR and Art. 31 (1) nDSG. The legitimate interest of TMG is to safeguard business operations and to regularly check whether reporting and compliance obligations are fulfilled.
    
* **General Business and Operational Support**. To assess and implement mergers, acquisitions, reorganizations, bankruptcies, and other business transactions such as financings, and to administer our business, accounting, auditing, compliance, recordkeeping, and legal functions. TMG relies on the legal basis of "legitimate interest" (Art. 6(1)(f) DSGVO and Art. 31(1) nDSG). In this context, TMG has an interest in disclosing and otherwise processing information about its assets and activities to potential buyers or acquirers and their external advisors in order to facilitate the sale of those assets and/or activities.

The purposes pursued by us in connection with the use of cookies and similar technologies, particularly concerning targeting and analytics are described in Section 6. Cookies, Targeting, and Analytics.

When the legal basis for processing is your consent, you are entitled to withdraw your consent at any time. However, this withdrawal will not affect the lawfulness of any processing carried out on the basis of your consent before your withdrawal. If the legal basis is a legitimate interest, you are also entitled, in general, to object to the processing of your personal data, at any time, for reasons arising from your specific situation. Further, you have the right to object at any time to processing of your personal data for direct marketing purposes. Article 21 GDPR / UK GDPR applies in this respect.

You can object to our use of your email address for promotional purposes or personal guidance, upon registration or later at any time.

**4\. Disclosures of Personal Information**

We may disclose the personal information we collect for the purposes described above, to provide you our Services, to respond to and fulfill your requests, as otherwise directed or consented to by you, and with the following recipients:

* **Brands, Affiliates, and Subsidiaries**. We may disclose the personal information we collect with our brands, corporate affiliates, and subsidiaries.
    
* **Business Partners**. In some circumstances, TMG may partner with other businesses to offer its Services, including to facilitate certain programs or special offerings, and we may disclose personal information to those business partners.
    
* **Vendors and Services Providers**. We may disclose the personal information we collect to vendors and service providers who perform functions on our behalf, such as IT and website hosting, payment processors, marketing and marketing research providers, customer support, data storage, data analytics providers, auditors, consultants, advisors and agents, and legal counsel.
    
* **Other TMG Users**. With other users of the Services in the context of specific features that are social in nature. For example, if you invite others to use our Services, or if you submit or make available information through our public-facing, interactive features, community forums, or discussion blogs, including when you post reviews or testimonials, certain personal information, may be available to, and searchable by, other users of the Services. For example, if you participate in Pets, other users of the Pets game feature will be able to see personal information such as your profile picture, gender, value, cash, assets, owned by and number of Pets.
    
* **Third-Party Marketing and Analytics Providers**. We may also disclose your personal information, such as device and browsing, and activities and usage information, to third-party marketing and data analytics providers, and other companies who provide marketing, advertising, campaign management, or analytics services on our behalf. For a detailed overview of the specific recipients.

We may also disclose your personal information in the following circumstances:

* **In Support of Business Transfers**. If we or our affiliates are or may be acquired by, merged with, or invested in by another company, or if any of our assets are or may be transferred to another company, whether as part of a bankruptcy or insolvency proceeding or otherwise, we may disclose or transfer the personal information we have collected from you with or to the other company in accordance with applicable laws. We may also disclose certain personal information as necessary prior to the completion of such a transaction or other corporate transaction such as a financing or restructuring, to lenders, auditors, and third-party advisors, including attorneys and consultants.
    
* **Compliance and Legal Obligations**. We may also disclose personal information to third parties to the extent required by applicable law and legal obligations. For example, we may disclose information in response to subpoenas, court orders, and other lawful requests by regulators, government entities, and law enforcement, including responding to national security or law enforcement disclosure requirements, or as otherwise required by law or legal process. In addition, and if applicable, we may disclose the names of sweepstakes and contests winners in accordance with applicable law.
    
* **Security and Protection of Rights**. Where we believe doing so is necessary to protect the Services, our rights and property, or the rights, property, and safety of others. For example, we may disclose personal information to (i) prevent, detect, investigate, and respond to fraud, unauthorized activities and access, illegal activities, and misuse of the Services, (ii) situations involving potential threats to the health, safety, or legal rights of any person or third party, or (iii) enforce, detect, investigate, and take action in response to violations of our Terms and Conditions. We may also disclose personal information related to litigation and other legal claims or proceedings in which we are involved, as well as for our internal accounting, auditing, compliance, recordkeeping, and legal functions.
    
* **Other Disclosures**. We may disclose personal information in other ways not described above that we notify you of or that we obtain your consent for, or that are otherwise authorized or required by law.

Notwithstanding anything else described in this Policy, we may use and disclose aggregated, deidentified, and other non-identifiable data related to our business and the Services for quality control, analytics, research, development, and other purposes. Where we use, disclose or process deidentified data (data that is no longer reasonably linked or linkable to an identified or identifiable natural person, household, or personal or household device) we will maintain and use the information in deidentified form and not to attempt to reidentify the information, except in order to determine whether our deidentification processes are reasonable and adequate pursuant to applicable privacy laws.

**5\. Transfers of personal data in the context of countries located outside the EEA/UK/CH**

Recipients of personal data may be located outside the EEA/UK/Swiss. Where personal data is transferred to locations outside the EEA/UK/Swiss (which includes transfers from us in the USA as a controller in scope of GDPR / UK GDPR / nDSG to recipients in the USA or other countries outside the EEA/UK/Swiss, which are not in scope of GDPR/UK GDPR/nDSG), we will, as required by law, ensure that your privacy rights are adequately protected either because the European Commission has decided that the country to which personal data are transferred ensures an adequate level of protection (Art. 45 GDPR / UK GDPR) or the transfer is subject to appropriate safeguards (e.g. standard data protection clauses of the European Union agreed on with the recipient) (Art. 46 GDPR / UK GDPR) unless GDPR / UK GDPR provides for an exception (Art. 49 GDPR / UK GDPR). In addition to this, we intend to, where necessary, agree on additional measures with recipients to ensure an adequate level of data protection. See also Art. 16 f. nDSG regarding the disclosure of personal data outside of Switzerland.

If necessary, we also conclude a corresponding "UK Addendum" with our contractual partners in accordance with the requirements of the Information Commissioner's Office (ICO) and a corresponding "CH Addendum" in accordance with the requirements of the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner (FDPIC).

Copies of appropriate safeguards (to the extent we rely on such) and a list of recipients located outside the EEA/UK/Swiss can be requested under [support@themeetgroup.com](mailto:support@themeetgroup.com). Please note that such copy may be redacted to the extent necessary to protect business secrets or other confidential information.

**6\. Cookies, Targeting, and Analytics**

We and our third-party service providers use cookies, pixels, local storage objects, log files, and other tracking mechanisms to automatically collect browsing, activity, device, and other similar information within our Services. We use this information to analyze and understand how users access, use, and interact with our Services, to identify and resolve bugs and errors in our Services, to assess secure, protect, optimize and improve the performance of our Services, as well as for marketing and analytics purposes, and to personalize content in our Services. Depending on your location, most of this will only take place if you have provided your consent using our CMP which you can find in your app settings to manage your consent / preferences regarding cookies, targeted advertising, and other similar tracking mechanisms within our Services, please see Section 7. Your Privacy Choices below. Many of these choices are browser and device specific, which means that you may need to set the preference for each browser and device you use to access our Services. In addition, if you delete or block cookies, you may need to reapply these preferences to each browser and/or device.

**Cookies**. "Cookies" are small text files stored on a user's device (such as a computer or smartphone) by a website they visit. Cookies are created by the website's server and sent to the user's browser, where it is stored for future reference. Some cookies allow us to make it easier for you to navigate our Services, while others are used, for example, to enable a faster log-in process, support the security and performance of the Services, or allow us to track aggregate and statistical information about user activity within the Services.

**Pixel Tags**. Pixel tags (sometime called web beacons or clear GIFs) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies. While cookies are stored locally on your device, pixel tags are embedded invisibly within web pages and online content. We may use these, in connection with our Services to, among other things, track the activities of users, and help us manage content and compile usage statistics. We may also use these in our emails to let us know when they have been opened or forwarded, so we can track response rates and gauge the effectiveness of our communications.

**Log Files**. We may collect certain activity information from log files. Log file information is automatically collected when you access our Sites. We record certain information from these log files, including web requests, IP address, browser type and version, language information, referring and exiting URLs, links clicked, pages viewed and other similar information.

**Third-Party Analytics**. We may use automated devices, applications, and tools, such as Google Analytics, which are operated by third-party companies, to evaluate usage of our Services. These third-party companies may use cookies, pixels, and other tracking technologies to collect usage data about our Services and provide us with reports and metrics that help us evaluate usage of our Services and enhance performance and user experiences. To learn more about Google's privacy practices, please review the Google Privacy Policy at [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). You can also download the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on to prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics at [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). A list of the third parties engaged by us in this respect can be found in our CMP which you can find in your app settings.

**Third-Party Advertising**. We work with third-party ad networks, marketing partners, mobile ad networks, and others ("third-party ad companies") to personalize content and display advertising within our Services, as well as to manage our advertising on third-party websites. We and these third-party ad companies may use cookies, pixels tags, SDKs (software development kits), and other tools to collect browsing and activity information within our Services (as well as on third-party sites and services), as well as IP address, unique ID, cookie and advertising IDs, and other online identifiers. We and these third-party ad companies use this information to provide you more relevant ads and content within our Services and on third-party sites, and to evaluate the success of such ads and content. A list of the third-party ad companies can be found in our CMP which you can find in your app settings.

**Cross-Device Use**. We and our third-party service providers may use the information we collect about you (whether directly from our Sites or Mobile App, through your device(s), or from third party sources) to help us and our third-party service providers identify other devices you use (e.g., a mobile phone, tablet, other computer, etc.). We and our third-party service providers may also use the cross-device use and other information we learn about you to serve targeted advertising or personalize content within our Services.

**Custom Lists and Matching**. We may share or make available certain customer list information (such as your name, email address and other contact information) with third parties so that we can better target ads and content to you across third-party websites, platforms and services. In some cases, these third parties may help us to enhance our customer lists with additional demographic or other similar information so we can better target our advertising and marketing campaigns.

**7\. Your Privacy Choices**

**Managing Your Preferences**. We make available several ways for you to manage your preferences and privacy choices, as described below:

* **Account and Profile**. You can review and update some of the personal information we maintain about you by logging into your account and updating your account and profile information.
    
* **Marketing Communications**. We may send periodic promotional emails, content, or other similar communications to you. You may opt-out of these communications by following the instructions provided to you in the communication. If you opt-out of receiving promotional content from us, we may still send you communications about your account or any services you have requested or received from us. Additionally, you can manage your communication preferences in your account and profile settings.
    
* **Push Notifications**. You can manage the type of push notifications you receive from us by adjusting your mobile device settings or by modifying the settings within our Mobile App. These are messages that we send you in the course of fulfilling the contract, as well as promotional information.

**Cookie and Tracking Preferences/Targeted Advertising/Analytics**. We also make available several ways for you to manage your preferences regarding cookies, targeted advertising, analytics, and other similar tracking mechanisms within our Services. Many of these choices are browser and device specific, which means that you may need to set the preference for each browser and device you use to access our Services. In addition, if you delete or block cookies, you may need to reapply these preferences to each browser and/or device. Further, opting out of cookies and advertising does not mean that you will no longer receive advertising content from us, and you may continue to receive generic or "contextual" ads from us.

* **Consent Management Platform (CMP).** To prevent cookies or other tracking mechanism which are not strictly necessary from tracking your activity on our Sites or in our Mobile App, you can use the consent management platform which is provided before the cookies and tracking mechanisms are used. Once a consent is given it can be withdrawn at any time with effect for the future. For more detailed information please review Section 15. Additional Privacy Information for Certain Jurisdictions, which includes additional information about privacy rights for residents of certain jurisdictions.
    
* **Cookie Settings**. To prevent cookies from tracking your activity on our Sites or visits across multiple websites, you can set your browser to block certain cookies or notify you when a cookie is set. You can also delete cookies. The "Help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your device from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to delete cookies. Visitors to our Sites who disable cookies will be able to browse the Site, but some features may not function.
    
* **Browser Signals**. To the extent required by applicable law, if our Sites detect that your browser is transmitting an opt-out preference signal, such as a "global privacy control" (or GPC) signal, we will apply that signal to opt that particular browser on your device out of targeting cookies on our Sites. If you come to our Sites from a different device or from a different browser on the same device, you will need to apply GPC for that browser and/or device as well.
    
* **Industry Ad Choice Programs**. You can also control how participating third-party ad companies use the information that they collect about your visits to our Sites and those of third parties, in order to display more relevant targeted advertising to you. For more information and assistance related to web tracking mechanisms, visit [www.YourOnlineChoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/).

Residents of certain jurisdictions may have additional rights to their personal information, as set forth below in Section 15. Additional Privacy Information for Certain Jurisdictions.

**8\. Storage Period of Personal Information**

We store your personal information for as long as it is necessary to pursue the purposes mentioned in Section 3 Purposes for Collection and Processing and Section 6 Cookies, Targeting, and Analytics or for as long as we have a legitimate interest in continued storage. In all other cases, we delete your personal information with the exception of information that we must continue to store in order to comply with statutory retention periods (e.g., resulting from tax or commercial law, such as concerning invoices). We restrict the processing of personal information that is only kept due to a retention obligation.

Information on the storage duration of cookies and other tracking mechanisms can be found in our CMP which you can find in your app settings.

**9\. External Links and Features**

Our Services may contain links to third-party websites or features or provide certain third-party connections or integrated services. Any access to and use of such linked websites or features is not governed by this Policy, but instead is governed by the privacy policies of those third parties. We are not responsible for the information practices of such third parties, including their collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information. You should review the privacy policies and terms for any third parties before proceeding to those websites or using those features.

**10\. User Generated Content**

We may offer public-facing interactive features, community forums, or discussion blogs in connection with our Services that enable you to share information about the Services, or other issues of interest (e.g., reviews, testimonials, and questions). You should be aware that any communications you submit or post to any such interactive features on the Services may be viewable and searchable by others, including TMG users and the public. By submitting or posting to such public-facing, interactive features you acknowledge that you have no expectation of privacy or confidentiality in the content you submit for such features, whether or not it contains personal information about you.

**11\. Security**

We have implemented reasonable precautions aimed to protect the information we collect from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Please be aware that despite our best efforts, no data security measures can guarantee security.

**12\. Children's Privacy**

Our Services are not designed for children, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of eighteen (18). If we learn that personal information has been collected on the Services from persons under the age of 18, then we will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. If you are a parent or legal guardian and you believe we have collected your child's information in violation of applicable law, please contact us using the contact information below.

**13\. Changes to this Policy**

This Policy is current as of the date set forth above. We may change, update, or modify this Policy from time to time, so please be sure to check back periodically. We will post any updates to this Policy here. If we make any changes to this Policy that materially affect our practices regarding our use of the personal information we have previously collected from you, we will endeavor to provide you with notice, such as by emailing you or by posting prominent notice on our Sites, in our Mobile App, or within the Services.

**14\. Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or our privacy practices, you may email us at [support@themeetgroup.com](mailto:support@themeetgroup.com) or contact us at:

The Meet Group, Inc.

100 Union Square Drive

New Hope, PA 18938

You can reach our data protection officer at:

ePrivacy GmbH represented by Prof. Dr. Christoph Bauer, Große Bleichen 21, 20354 Hamburg, [privacy@themeetgroup.com](mailto:privacy@themeetgroup.com)

For all requests concerning the security of your data, please contact our data protection officer at [privacy@themeetgroup.com](mailto:privacy@themeetgroup.com).

Our EU Representative pursuant to Art. 27 GDPR can be reached at: ParshipMeet Holding GmbH, Speersort 10, 20095 Hamburg, email: [privacy@parshipmeet.com](mailto:privacy@parshipmeet.com)

Our UK Representative's details pursuant to Art 27 UK GDPR are set out in Section 15.B. Additional Information for Residents of the UK

Our Swiss representative's details pursuant to Art. 14 nDSG (new Swiss Data Protection Act) are set out in Section 15.C. Additional Informatione for Residents of Switzerland.

Treforma AG c/o MLL Legal; Grabenstrasse 25; 6340 Baar; Switzerland; [meetgroup@dsg-mll.com](mailto:meetgroup@dsg-mll.com)

**15\. Additional Privacy Information for Certain Jurisdictions**

Residents of certain jurisdictions have additional rights under applicable privacy laws, as described in this section.

**A. GDPR**

If you are a resident of the European Union, you have the following rights under GDPR provided that the legal requirements therein are met:

**Right of access** - You may request information about the processing of your personal data and a copy of the personal data undergoing processing insofar as such copy does not adversely affect the rights and freedoms of others and no other exception applies.

**Right to rectification** - You may request correction of your personal data that is inaccurate and/or completion of such data which is incomplete.

**Right to erasure** - You may request deletion of your personal data, in particular where

* the personal data is no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which they were collected or otherwise processed,
    
* you have withdrawn your consent on which the processing was based and there is no other legal basis for the processing,
    
* you objected to the processing which is based on the legal basis "legitimate interests" and there are no overriding legitimate grounds for the processing or you objected to the processing for direct marketing purposes,
    
* your personal data has been unlawfully processed or
    
* your personal data has to be erased for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject.

The right to erasure, however, does not apply in particular where the processing of your personal data is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation or for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims.

**Right to restriction of processing** - You may request restriction of processing

* for the period in which we verify the accuracy of your personal data if you contested the accuracy of the personal data,
    
* where the processing is unlawful and you request restriction of processing instead of erasure of the data,
    
* where we no longer need the personal data, but you require the data for the establishment, exercise, or defence of legal claims, or
    
* if you objected to processing which is based on the legal basis "legitimate interests" until it has been verified whether our legitimate grounds override your interests, rights, and freedoms.

**Right to data portability** - You may request to receive your personal data, which you have provided to us, in a structured, commonly used machine-readable format and transmit those data to another controller without hindrance from us, where the processing is based on consent or the performance of a contract and the processing is carried out by automated means; in these cases, you may also request to have the personal data transmitted directly to another controller where this is technically feasible.

Furthermore, you have the following rights:

**Right to withdraw consent -** You may withdraw your consent at any time for the future where processing is based on your consent, without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal.

**Right to object -**

**You have the right to object, on grounds relating to your particular situation, at any time to processing of your personal data which is based on our or a third party's legitimate interest (Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR). We then will no longer process your personal data for the purpose to which you have objected, unless we are able to demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing which override your interests, rights, and freedoms or for the establishment, exercise, or defense of legal claims.**

**Further, you have the right to object at any time to processing of your personal data for direct marketing purposes. Where you object to processing for direct marketing purposes, we will process your personal data no longer for such purposes.**

* * *

**Right to lodge a complaint -** You may lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, in particular in the Member State of your habitual residence, place of work, or place of an alleged infringement if you consider that the processing of your personal data infringes the GDPR.

The data protection authority competent for us is:

Free and Hanseatic City of Hamburg, The Hamburg Commissioner for Data Protection and Freedom of Information, Ludwig-Erhard-Str. 22, 20459 Hamburg, email: [mailbox@datenschutz.hamburg.de](mailto:mailbox@datenschutz.hamburg.de)

**B. UK GDPR**

If you're located in the UK, under the UK GDPR and data protection laws, you have rights. Whether and to what extent the rights apply may depend upon the circumstances. To exercise any of these rights, please use the contact details provided below. The rights are:

**Your right to be informed** -- You have a right to receive concise, transparent, intelligible, and easily accessible information about your personal data and our use of it. This Policy is our way of informing you of that information but if you have any further questions or concerns, please use the contact information provided below.

**Your right of access** -- You have the right to ask us for copies of your personal data. This right always applies but there are some exemptions to its application, which means you may not always receive all the information you have requested. When you request your personal data, this is known as making a data subject access request (DSAR). We may need to ask you for identification documentation in order to verify your identity on receipt of a DSAR from you.

**Your right to rectification** -- You have the right to ask us to rectify personal data you think is inaccurate. You also have the right to ask us to complete information you think is incomplete.

**Your right to erasure** -- You have the right to ask us to erase your personal data in certain circumstances. We have the right to refuse to comply with a request for erasure if we are processing the personal data for one of the following reasons:

* To exercise the right of freedom of expression and information.
    
* To comply with a legal obligation.
    
* To perform a task in the public interest or exercise official authority.
    
* For archiving purposes in the public interest, scientific research, historical research or statistical purposes.
    
* For the exercise or defence of legal claims.

**Your right to restriction of processing** -- You have the right to ask us to restrict the processing of your personal data in certain circumstances. In such case, we will still hold the data but will not process it any further. This right is an alternative to the right to erasure. If one of the following conditions applies, you may exercise the right to restrict processing:

* The accuracy of the personal data is contested.
    
* Processing of the personal data is unlawful.
    
* We no longer need the personal data for processing, but the personal data is required for part of a legal process.
    
* The right to object has been exercised and processing is restricted pending a decision on the status of the processing.

**Your right to object to processing -- You have the right to object to processing in certain circumstances, including direct marketing. You can also object if the processing is on the basis of our legitimate interests (or those of a third party). We then will no longer process your personal data for the purpose to which you have objected, unless we are able to demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing which override your interests, rights, and freedoms or for the establishment, exercise, or defense of legal claims.**

**Your right to data portability** -- This right is the right to receive your personal data in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format but only applies if we are processing information based on your consent or for the performance of a contract and the processing is automated.

**Right to withdraw consent -** You may withdraw your consent at any time for the future where processing is based on your consent, without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal.

**Contact information**

If you would like to exercise any of your rights or have any questions regarding our use of your personal data, please use the information under Contact Us . Please also ensure that when you do so, you provide sufficient information to enable us to clearly identify you.

Note that we have appointed a UK Representative for you to contact on our behalf pursuant to Art. 27 UK GDPR: eHarmony UK Ltd., 6-10 Great Portland Street, London W1W 8QL, Great-Britain

**Transfers of personal information outside of the UK**

For details on the protection and safeguards applied to your personal data when it is transferred outside of the United Kingdom, please see Section 5 Transfers of personal data in the context of countries located outside the EEA/UK/CH, above.

**Right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority**

You have the right to file a complaint with a data protection authority.

You can contact the UK's data protection authority, the Information Commissioner's Office, at: Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF, Telephone Number: + 44 (0) 303 123 1113, Email: [casework@ico.org.uk](mailto:casework@ico.org.uk).

**C. Swiss Data Protection Law**

**Your right of access** -- You have the right to ask us for copies of your personal data. This right always applies but there are some exemptions to its application, which means you may not always receive all the information you have requested. When you request data, this is known as making a data subject access request (DSAR).

**Your right to rectification** -- You have the right to ask us to rectify personal data you think is inaccurate. You also have the right to ask us to complete information you think is incomplete.

**Your right to erasure** -- You have the right to ask us to erase your personal data in certain circumstances. We have the right to refuse to comply with a request for erasure if we are processing the personal data for one of the following reasons:

* To exercise the right of freedom of expression and information.
    
* To comply with a legal obligation.
    
* To perform a task in the public interest or exercise official authority.
    
* For archiving purposes in the public interest, scientific research, historical research or statistical purposes.
    
* For the exercise or defence of legal claims.

**Your right to restriction of processing** -- You have the right to ask us to restrict the processing of your personal data in certain circumstances. In such case, we will still hold the data but will not process it any further. This right is an alternative to the right to erasure. If one of the following conditions applies, you may exercise the right to restrict processing:

* The accuracy of the personal data is contested.
    
* Processing of the personal data is unlawful.
    
* We no longer need the personal data for processing, but the personal data is required for part of a legal process.
    
* The right to object has been exercised and processing is restricted pending a decision on the status of the processing.

**Your right to object to processing** -- You have the right to object to processing in certain circumstances. You can also object if the processing is for a task carried out in the public interest, the exercise of official authority vested in you, or our legitimate interests (or those of a third party).

**Your right to object to direct marketing** - You can also object at any time to the processing of your personal data for advertising purposes ("advertising objection"). Please take into account that, for organizational reasons, there may be an overlap between your revocation and the use of your data in the context of an already ongoing campaign.

**Your right to data portability** -- This right only applies if we are processing information based on your consent or for the performance of a contract and the processing is automated.

If you would like to exercise any of your rights, please use the information under Contact Us. Please also ensure that when you do so, you provide sufficient information to enable us to clearly identify you.

**Contact information**

If you would like to exercise any of your rights or have any questions regarding our use of your personal data, please use the information under Contact Us . Please also ensure that when you do so, you provide sufficient information to enable us to clearly identify you.

Note that we have appointed a Swiss to Art. 14 nDSG (new Swiss Data Protection Act): Treforma AG c/o MLL Legal; Grabenstrasse 25; 6340 Baar; Switzerland; [meetgroup@dsg-mll.com](mailto:meetgroup@dsg-mll.com)

**Transfers of personal information outside of Switzerland**

For details on the protection and safeguards applied to your personal data when it is transferred outside of Switzerland, please see Section 5 Transfers of personal data in the context of countries located outside the EEA/UK/CH, above.

**Right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority**

You have the right to file a complaint with a data protection authority.

You contact the competent data protection supervisory authority in Switzerland. This is the:

Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner (FDPIC).

You are welcome to contact them at:

[https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/de/home/deredoeb/kontakt/kontaktformular\_bgoe.html](https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/de/home/deredoeb/kontakt/kontaktformular_bgoe.html)

**The Meet Group Inc.**

Esta Política de Privacidad aplica a los usuarios residentes del Espacio Económico Europeo o del Reino Unido
============================================================================================================

_Última actualización: October 8, 2024_

The Meet Group, Inc., sus marcas, filiales y subsidiarias valoran la privacidad de sus usuarios. Esta Política de Privacidad (" **Política** ") describe la manera en que The Meet Group, Inc. (" **TMG** ," " **nosotros** ", " **nuestro** " o " **nos** ") recolecta, usa, comparte y procesa la información personal (también denominada "datos personales" en ciertas jurisdicciones) descrita en esta Política, así como los derechos y elecciones existentes en torno a dicha información personal.

Para obtener más información acerca de las elecciones de privacidad existentes en torno a la información personal, consulte la Sección 7, en el apartado "Elecciones de privacidad", así como la Sección 5, en el apartado "Información adicional acerca de la privacidad en ciertas jurisdicciones", mismo que incluye información adicional acerca de los derechos de privacidad de los residentes de ciertas jurisdicciones.

En el caso de los residentes de la Unión Europea o del Espacio Económico Europeo (EEE), consulte la Sección 15.A, en el apartado "Información adicional para los residentes de la Unión Europea o del Espacio Económico Europeo", mismo que incluye información adicional en torno a los derechos de dichos residentes en virtud del Reglamento General de Protección de Datos ("RGPD").

En el caso de los residentes del Reino Unido, consulte la Sección 15.B, en el apartado "Información adicional para los residentes del Reino Unido", mismo que incluye información adicional acerca de los derechos de dichos residentes en virtud de la incorporación del Reglamento General de Protección de Datos a las leyes del Reino Unido, de acuerdo con la Sección 3 de la Ley de Retirada de la Unión Europea de 2018 promulgada por el Reino Unido ("RGPD del Reino Unido").

En el caso de los residentes de Suiza, consulte la Sección 15.C, en el apartado "Información adicional para los residentes de Suiza", mismo que incluye información adicional acerca de los derechos de dichos residentes en virtud de la nueva Ley Federal de Protección de Datos de Suiza ("nDSG").

Crear un perfil en alguno de nuestros Servicios puede resultar en que cierta información personal, como el nombre de usuario, el nombre, la edad, el género y la orientación sexual, que, de acuerdo con la configuración de privacidad de cada usuario, sea vista por otros usuarios de dicho Servicio o por usuarios de nuestros otros Servicios, así como por usuarios de alguna de nuestras aplicaciones, y usuarios de otras aplicaciones y sitios web de terceros con los que compartimos nuestra plataforma. Estos usuarios adicionales son de naturaleza global. Nuestra lista de socios actuales se encuentra en el enlace [a continuación](https://talent.tagged.com/partner-policy-tagged.html).

El uso de nuestros Servicios está sujeto a nuestros [Términos y Condiciones](https://secure.tagged.com/terms_of_service.html), lo que incluye la terminología utilizada para regir las limitaciones en torno a los daños y perjuicios, así como la resolución de conflictos.

**Índice**

1. Alcance
    
2. Información personal recolectada
    
3. Fines de la recolección y procesamiento de la información
    
4. Comunicación de la información personal
    
5. Transferencia de los datos personales en el contexto de los países ajenos al EEE, al Reino Unido y a Suiza
    
6. Cookies, segmentación y análisis
    
7. Elecciones de privacidad
    
8. Período de almacenamiento de la información personal
    
9. Enlaces y funciones externas
    
10. Contenido generado por usuarios
    
11. Seguridad
    
12. Privacidad de menores
    
13. Cambios a esta Política
    
14. Contáctanos
    
15. Información adicional acerca de la privacidad en ciertas jurisdicciones

**1\. Alcance**

Salvo que se estipule lo contrario en el presente documento, esta Política aplica a la información personal recolectada y procesada por TMG dentro del siguiente contexto: las personas que visiten nuestro sitio web, mismo que alberga esta Política e incluye cualquiera de nuestros sitios que cuenten con un enlace o una publicación que dirija a esta Política (los " **Sitios** "); personas que descarguen y usen nuestra aplicación para teléfonos celulares (" **Aplicación Móvil** "; por ejemplo, la aplicación Tagged o la aplicación Pets); personas que se inscriban o participen en eventos, encuestas, estudios, promociones y concursos dirigidos por nosotros; y personas que se comuniquen o interactúen con nosotros o alguno de nuestros servicios disponibles a través de nuestros Sitios, nuestra Aplicación Móvil u otros servicios en línea (designados conjuntamente como " **Servicios** ").

**2\. Recolección de la información personal**

Como se describe a continuación, nosotros podemos recolectar directamente información personal del usuario, recolectarla por medio de terceros y recolectarla de manera automática a través del uso de nuestros Servicios.

**Información recolectada directamente del usuario** . Si bien la información personal que recolectamos varía en función del uso de nuestros Servicios y nuestras interacciones con cada usuario, generalmente recolectamos información relacionada a las siguientes categorías:

* **Información de contacto** . Al ser contactados por una persona, ya sea por medio de un mensaje o al crear una cuenta para conocer más acerca de nuestros Servicios, podemos recolectar el nombre, el correo electrónico, el número telefónico u otros identificadores similares de la persona en cuestión , así como los mensajes, los tipos de solicitud, y cualquier otra información que se nos comparta de manera voluntaria.
    
* **Información relacionada con las cuentas y a los perfiles** . Al crear una cuenta en alguno de nuestros servicios (por ejemplo, una cuenta de Tagged), podemos recolectar el nombre, el correo electrónico, el número telefónico, el domicilio (por ejemplo, el código postal), el nombre de usuario y su respectiva contraseña, la fecha de nacimiento, el género, la orientación sexual, la imagen de perfil y la foto, y la dirección de facturación, así como cualquier otra información que se nos proporcione para crear o dar mantenimiento a una cuenta, o cualquier otra información que se nos proporcione a través de una cuenta.

Si se inicia sesión por medio de algún proveedor externo, como Facebook, Apple o un mensaje SMS, no se ingresa un correo electrónico o contraseña al crear una cuenta. Una vez finalizado este proceso, se accede a nuestro Servicio mediante el correo electrónico registrado y la contraseña seleccionada (credenciales de acceso), o por medio de las credenciales de acceso que se utilicen con el proveedor externo.

**Creación de cuenta por medio de Facebook ("Inicio de sesión por medio de Facebook")**

Brindamos la opción de inicio de sesión unificado por medio de Facebook. Esta función permite crear una cuenta por medio de una cuenta existente de Facebook. Utilizar esta función resulta en que Facebook nos proporcione los siguientes datos de autentificación para su procesamiento con el fin de crear una cuenta: el correo electrónico, el nombre del perfil, el género, la fecha de nacimiento y la imagen de perfil almacenada. Lo antedicho conlleva una transferencia de datos.

Asimismo, iniciar sesión por medio de Facebook en nuestro sitio web o aplicación resultará en que Facebook recolecte datos asociados a scripts de terceros, ya sea con fines analíticos o para comunicárselos a terceros. La Política de Privacidad de Facebook señala los datos que pueden ser recolectados al utilizar el inicio de sesión por medio de Facebook. Entre estos datos se incluyen datos del dispositivo, el uso de nuestro Servicio, los sitios web visitados y los anuncios vistos. Lamentablemente, no es posible rehusarse al procesamiento de esta información si se utiliza esta función. No se recomienda utilizar el inicio de sesión por medio de Facebook si no se está de acuerdo con que Facebook recolecte información relacionada a nuestra oferta en línea para sus propios fines.

Es posible desvincular una cuenta de Tagged de una cuenta de Facebook en todo momento. En caso de realizarse esta operación, será necesario que se nos brinde la información de acceso previamente mencionada.

La Política de Privacidad de Facebook contiene más información acerca de sus fines y su alcance con respecto a la recolección y el subsecuente procesamiento de la información, así como los derechos del usuario y las configuraciones que puede utilizar para proteger su información. Dicha política se encuentra en el enlace a continuación: [http://www.facebook.com/policy.php](http://www.facebook.com/policy.php).

**Creación de cuenta e inicio de sesión por medio de Google**

Brindamos la opción de crear una cuenta y de iniciar sesión en nuestro Servicio por medio de una cuenta de Google si se utiliza un dispositivo Android. Si se utilizase esta función, Google Ireland Limited, con sede en Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Irlanda ("Google") nos brindará la información necesaria para la creación de una cuenta o para iniciar sesión (la dirección de correo electrónico, el nombre, el identificador de la cuenta de Google y la imagen de perfil de la cuenta de Google).

No determinamos el tipo de datos que Google puede recolectar a través del inicio de sesión por medio de Google. No se recomienda utilizar el inicio de sesión por medio de Google si no se está de acuerdo con que Google recolecte información relacionada a nuestra oferta en línea para sus propios fines.

La Política de Privacidad de Google contiene más información acerca de sus fines y su alcance con respecto a la recolección y el subsecuente procesamiento de la información, así como los derechos del usuario y las configuraciones que puede utilizar para proteger su información. Dicha Política de Privacidad se encuentra en el enlace a continuación: [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

**Creación de cuenta e inicio de sesión por medio de Apple**

Brindamos la opción de crear una cuenta y de iniciar sesión en nuestro Servicio por medio de una cuenta de Apple si se utiliza un dispositivo iOS. Si se utilizase esta función, Apple Inc., con sede en One Apple Park Way, Cupertino, California, EE.UU., 95014 ("Apple") nos brindará la información seleccionada por el usuario y la información necesaria para la creación de una cuenta o para iniciar sesión (por ejemplo, el correo electrónico generado por Apple, el nombre).

No determinamos el alcance de los datos que Apple puede recolectar a través del inicio de sesión por medio de Apple. No se recomienda utilizar el inicio de sesión por medio de Apple si no se está de acuerdo con que Apple recolecte información relacionada a nuestra oferta en línea para sus propios fines.

La Política de Privacidad de Apple contiene más información acerca de sus fines y su alcance con respecto a la recolección y el subsecuente procesamiento de la información, así como los derechos del usuario y las configuraciones que puede utilizar para proteger su información. Dicha Política de Privacidad se encuentra albergada en la liga a continuación: [https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/en/sign-in-with-apple/](https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/en/sign-in-with-apple/).

**Creación de cuenta e inicio de sesión por medio de autentificación telefónica**

Si se selecciona la opción de autentificación telefónica, es necesario que se nos proporcione un número de teléfono celular durante el proceso de creación de cuenta o al iniciar sesión por medio de este proceso. Nosotros enviamos un mensaje SMS con un código de verificación que debe ser ingresado en la aplicación para completar la creación de cuenta. De igual forma, nosotros enviamos un mensaje SMS con un código que debe ser ingresado para completar el inicio de sesión Asimismo, se realizará un proceso de verificación. Este servicio es proporcionado por Sinch America Inc., una corporación de Delaware, cuyo departamento legal tiene sede en 3500 Lenox Rd NE, Ste. 1875, Atlanta, GA 30326, Georgia, EE.UU.,

y este solo puede ofrecerse con el consentimiento del usuario.

La Política de Privacidad de Sinch contiene más información acerca de sus fines y su alcance con respecto a la recolección y el subsecuente procesamiento de la información. Dicha Política de Privacidad se encuentra albergada en la liga a continuación [https://www.sinch.com/privacy-notice/](https://www.sinch.com/privacy-notice/)

* **Compras, pagos y premios** . Nosotros podemos recolectar la siguiente información en el momento en el que se realice una compra o un pago por medio de nuestros Servicios (por ejemplo, mediante el uso de la función de nuestro juego Pets): el tipo de pago, información relacionada a la tarjeta de pago, información de facturación e información relacionada a la compra, y cualquier otra información de naturaleza financiera o comercial necesaria para el funcionamiento de nuestros Servicios.
    
* **Comunicación e interacciones** . Nosotros podemos recolectar, recibir y almacenar información de contacto, comunicaciones e interacciones, publicaciones, comentarios y, si es pertinente, nuestras respuestas, si se nos contacta por correo electrónico o llamada telefónica, o si establece cualquier tipo de comunicación o interacción, tanto con nosotros como con otros usuarios de TMG (lo que incluye suscribirse a nuestras listas de correo), enviar formularios por medio de nuestros Sitios o nuestra Aplicación Telefónica, interactuar con nuestras redes sociales, publicar una reseña o un testimonio, publicar contenido en algún grupo de discusión en línea, o ingresar cualquier tipo de información en algún campo de comentario, blog o foro público que le pertenezca a TMG o a alguna de sus filiales.
    
* **Información promocional** . En caso de que el usuario se suscriba a nuestras comunicaciones de mercadotecnia, nosotros podemos recolectar el nombre, el correo electrónico, la dirección, el número telefónico, las preferencias y, si es pertinente, información en torno a la cuenta y perfil del usuario cuestión, lo que incluye el uso de nuestros Servicios y sus funciones. En caso de participar en nuestras actividades especiales, ofertas, programas o promociones, nosotros podemos recolectar cierta información de contacto, la edad y cualquier otra información que la ley nos exija. Asimismo, en caso de que se obtenga un premio como parte de nuestras actividades, nosotros nos podremos ver en la necesidad de recolectar información de naturaleza fiscal y, si es pertinente, las exenciones correspondientes.
    
* **Respuestas y sugerencias** . Nosotros podemos recolectar respuestas, sugerencias y cualquier otra información enviada de manera voluntaria por medio de nuestras encuestas, cuestionarios o cualquiera de nuestros estudios, ya sean estas iniciativas en pro de la satisfacción del cliente o para otros fines similares.
    
* **Eventos e inscripciones** . También podemos recolectar información personal relacionada a la participación en nuestros eventos, así como solicitudes de otro tipo que recibamos en relación a nuestros Servicios. Por ejemplo nosotros podemos recolectar información relacionada a la inscripción y participación en eventos en los que funjamos como organizadores o patrocinadores.
    
* **Preferencias y otras solicitudes** . También podemos recolectar información relacionada a las preferencias del usuario, lo que incluye los métodos preferidos de contacto, las preferencias en torno al uso de nuestros Servicios, y cualquier otra preferencia o solicitud que nos sea comunicada.

No es obligatorio que se nos proporcione información personal en la mayoría de los casos. No obstante, el uso de ciertos Servicios o de las funciones de los mismos puede requerir que se nos proporcione información personal; por ejemplo, para la creación de una cuenta en Tagged. Nosotros lo señalaremos en caso de ser necesario. Lamentablemente, no será posible utilizar un Servicio si no se nos proporciona la información necesaria para utilizarlo.

**Información personal recolectada por medio de terceros** . También podemos recolectar y recibir información personal por parte de los siguientes proveedores externos: socios comerciales (en particular si se realiza una compra en una de sus tiendas virtuales de aplicaciones), otros usuarios de TMG, proveedores de servicios de mercadotecnia y análisis de datos, sistemas operativos y redes sociales, (en particular si se utiliza alguna de las antedichas funciones de inicio de sesión). Además, también podemos recolectar la siguiente información por medio de terceros:

* **Información de redes sociales y plataformas** . Es posible que el usuario comparta información o contenido, cree una cuenta o inicie sesión en nuestros Servicios por medio de diferentes redes sociales, plataformas sociales u otras funciones o servicios por parte de terceros. Conectarse a nuestros servicios por medio de cuentas de redes sociales u otras funciones o servicios puede resultar en que nosotros recibamos o recolectemos información personal previamente compartida a través de dicha red social, función o servicio. Por ejemplo, podemos recolectar información contenida en una cuenta y en un perfil, como el nombre, el correo electrónico, el identificador de usuario, la imagen de perfil, la lista de amigos e información similar que se encuentre disponible en dicho perfil. Se recomienda revisar las configuraciones de privacidad de cada red social, función o servicio para conocer a detalle la manera en que cada una de estas partes puede usar, comunicar o procesar la información personal.
    
* **Información relacionada a usuarios referidos** . Nosotros podemos ofrecer la opción de que los usuarios inviten a amigos o refieran a otros usuarios para que estos accedan o usen nuestros Servicios. Lo anterior conlleva que nosotros podamos recolectar y recibir información del usuario referente , así como de otros usuarios existentes o potenciales de TMG, y clientes que realicen actividades similares.

**Información personal recolectada de manera automática** . Nosotros y nuestros proveedores externos podemos recolectar u obtener información relacionada al uso de nuestros Servicios, y podemos utilizar cookies, pixeles de rastreo y otras tecnologías similares para estos fines. La información personal que podemos recolectar de manera automática incluye lo siguiente:

* **Información del dispositivo y de navegación** . Nosotros podemos recolectar el tipo de navegador, el nombre de dominio, el número de visualizaciones, los tiempos de acceso, las marcas de fecha y hora, el sistema operativo, el idioma, el tipo de dispositivo, el identificador único, el proveedor de servicios de internet, los enlaces de referidos y salidas, , el historial de clics e información similar relacionada al dispositivo o a la navegación.
    
* **Uso y actividad** . También podemos recolectar información relacionada a la actividad durante el uso de nuestros Servicios, lo que incluye información acerca de los enlaces visitados , las búsquedas, las funciones utilizadas, los artículos vistos, el tiempo de uso de nuestros servicios, las interacciones con nosotros y otros usuarios de nuestros Servicios e información similar relacionada al uso y la actividad.
    
* **Información relacionada a la ubicación** . También podemos recolectar u obtener información de caracter general relacionada a la ubicación, como es el caso de la dirección IP.

Para más información acerca de nuestro uso de cookies y otras tecnologías similares, consulte la Sección 6, "Cookies, segmentación y análisis".

**3\. Fines de la recolección y procesamiento de la información**

En la mayoría de los casos, nosotros podemos recolectar, utilizar, comunicar y procesar la información personal que recolectamos para los siguientes fines:

* **Servicios y soporte** . Para ofrecer y operar nuestros Servicios (por ejemplo, las funciones de los juegos Tagged o Pet), gestionar las cuentas de los usuarios, enviar comunicaciones en torno al uso de nuestros servicios, brindar soporte técnico o realizar otro tipo de operaciones con fines similares, así como responder a dudas, cumplir peticiones, facilitar el procesamiento de los pagos y las ejecución de las operaciones diarias. Esto implica que cierta información personal, como el identificador de usuario, el nombre y la información de contacto que, de acuerdo a la configuración de privacidad de cada usuario, sea vista por otros usuarios de dicho Servicio o por usuarios de nuestros otros Servicios, así como por usuarios de alguna de nuestras aplicaciones, y usuarios de otras aplicaciones y sitios web de terceros con los que compartimos nuestra plataforma. Para estos fines TMG opera con base en el "cumplimento de contrato" como fundamento jurídico (artículo 6 (1) (b) del RGPD y del RGPD del Reino Unido, y el artículo 31 (2) (b) de la nFADP). Con respecto al procesamiento de la información con el fin de que esta sea vista por otros usuarios de nuestros otros Servicios y aplicaciones, así como por usuarios de aplicaciones o sitios web de terceros con los que compartimos nuestra plataforma, TMG opera con base en el "cumplimento de contrato" como fundamento jurídico (el artículo 6 (1) (b) del RGPD y del RGPD del Reino Unido, y el artículo 31 (2) (b) de la nFADP).

Con respecto a la información relacionada a la ubicación, TMG opera con base en el consentimiento del usuario (el artículo 6 (1) (a) y el artículo 7 del RGPD).

Con respecto a la orientación sexual, TMG opera con base en el consentimiento explícito del usuario (el artículo 6 (1) (a), el artículo 7 y el artículo 9 (2) (a) del RGPD y el RGPD del Reino Unido) o con base en la excepción legal provista por el artículo 9 (2) (e) del RGPD y del RGPD del Reino Unido, siempre y cuando el usuario haya divulgado su orientación sexual de manera pública (por ejemplo, durante una transmisión en vivo).

* **Análisis y mejoras** . Para comprender las maneras en que los usuarios acceden y usan nuestros Servicios, así como para otros fines de estudio y análisis, lo que incluye tanto la evaluación y mejora del Sitio, de nuestros servicios y de nuestras operaciones comerciales, como la mejora de nuestros Servicios y sus funciones, así como para fines de control de calidad interno y capacitación. Para estos fines TMG opera con base en los "intereses legítimos" como fundamento jurídico (artículo 6 (1) (f) del RGPD y del RGPD del Reino Unido, y el artículo 31 (1) de la nFADP). En este aspecto, comprender el desempeño comercial de su servicio es del interés de TMG.

**Comunicación** . Para brindar respuestas, enviar materiales solicitados, y enviar tanto información como materiales relacionados a nuestra oferta y Servicios al usuario. También podemos utilizar esta información para enviar información de naturaleza administrativa al usuario; por ejemplo, información relacionada a nuestros Servicios, así como cambios a nuestros términos, condiciones y políticas. Para estos fines TMG opera con base en el "cumplimento de contrato" como fundamento jurídico (artículo 6 (1) (b) del RGPD y RGPD del Reino Unido, y el artículo 31 (2) (a) de la nFDAP); en caso de que no existiera un contrato celebrado entre el usuario y TMG, se operará con base en los "intereses legítimos" como fundamento jurídico (artículo 6 (1) (f) del RGPD y del RGPD del Reino Unido, y el artículo 31 (1) de la nFADP). En caso de que TMG operara bajo sus "intereses legítimos", proporcionar apoyo a sus usuarios y dar respuesta a sus solicitudes en pro de la satisfacción de los usuarios es del interés de TMG.

* **Personalización** . Para personalizar el contenido enviado o mostrarlo en nuestros Servicios, lo que incluye brindar personalización con base en la ubicación, así como otros tipos de experiencias y ofertas personalizadas. Para estos fines TMG opera con base en el "cumplimento de contrato" como fundamento jurídico (artículo 6 (1) (b) del RGPD y el RGPD del Reino Unido, y el artículo 31 (2) (b) de la nFADP.
    
* Redes sociales y otras plataformas. Posibilitar que el usuario comparta información y contenido, inicie sesión o cree una cuenta en nuestros Servicios por medio de diferentes redes o plataformas sociales, así como por otras funciones y servicios ofrecidos por terceros. TMG opera con base en el "cumplimiento de contrato" como fundamento jurídico para posibilitar el inicio de sesión y la creación de cuentas (artículo 6 (1) (b) del RGPD y del RGPD del Reino Unido, y el artículo 31 (2) (b) de la nFADP). De lo contrario, TMG opera con base en los "intereses legítimos" como fundamento jurídico (artículo 6 (1) (f) del RGPD y del RGPD del Reino Unido, y el artículo 31 (1) de la nFADP). En este sentido, posibilitar que el usuario cuente con la capacidad de entablar ciertas comunicaciones mediante redes o plataformas sociales, y otras funciones y servicios ofrecidos por terceros , es del interés de TMG.
    
* **Mercadotecnia y publicidad** . Para fines promocionales, de mercadotecnia y de publicidad. Por ejemplo, enviar información promocional acerca de nuestros Servicios al usuario, lo que incluye boletines informativos, información acerca de eventos de TMG, webinars, presentaciones, ventas, promociones, descuentos y nuevas ofertas, así como cualquier otro tipo de información a la que el usuario se haya suscrito. Para estos fines TMG opera con base en el "consentimiento" como fundamento jurídico (artículo 6 (1) (a) y el artículo 7 del RGPD y del RGPD del Reino Unido, y el artículo 31 (1) de la nFADP.

Para fines que involucren crear su propia publicidad y utilizar mercadotecnia directa por medio de correos electrónicos promocionales o mensajes push, encuestas dirigidas al usuario y guías personalizadas, siempre y cuando se trata solamente de productos de TMG. (El fundamento jurídico en cuestión es que la mercadotecnia directa en torno a sus productos es un legítimo interés de TMG, así como la Sección 7 (3) de la Ley de Lucha contra la Competencia Desleal (UWG) de Alemania.

* **Estudios y encuestas** . Proporcionar encuestas y cuestionarios, cuyos fines pueden incluir investigaciones de mercados, satisfacción de los usuarios u otros fines similares. Para estos fines TMG opera con base en el "consentimiento" como fundamento jurídico (artículo 6 (1) (a) y el artículo 7 de la RGPD y del RGPD del Reino Unido, y el artículo 31 (1) de la nFADP.
    
* **Desarrollo de la información y enriquecimiento de datos** . Nosotros podemos combinar la información recolectada mediante nuestros Servicios con información del usuario que sea recolectada en otros contextos, tanto por nosotros o por terceros. En la mayoría de los casos, podemos combinar información personal con información recolectada por medio de nuestros Servicios para fines de estudios de mercado, como es el caso de la información de caracter demográfico, misma que no revela la identidad de los consumidores. Para estos fines TMG opera con base en los "intereses legítimos" como fundamento jurídico (artículo 6 (1) (f) del RGPD y del RGPD del Reino Unido, y el artículo 31 (1) de la nFADP). En este aspecto, comprender el desempeño comercial de su servicio es del interés de TMG.
    
* **Acceso y almacenamiento de información en los dispositivos de los usuarios.** Nosotros podemos acceder o almacenar información en los dispositivos de los usuarios. Para estos fines TMG opera con base en el "consentimiento" , de acuerdo al artículo 5 (3) de la Directiva 2002/58/CE y a la regulación (6) 4 de las Regulaciones de la privacidad y las comunicaciones electrónicas, siempre y cuando esto no sea necesario para el funcionamiento de nuestro sitio web, así como el envío de telemedios que hayan sido solicitados por el usuario de manera explícita.
    
* **Planeación y gestión de eventos** . Para la planeación de eventos y otros fines administrativos, como la inscripción y asistencia a eventos, conectar a los visitantes de un evento y otros usuarios TMG, y contactar a los usuarios para transmitir información acerca de eventos importantes, presentaciones, y nuestros Servicios. También podemos utilizar la información personal con el fin de facilitar eventos especiales, concursos y promociones, cuya participación puede estar sujeta a las reglas de cada evento particular. Para estos fines TMG opera con base en el "consentimiento" como fundamento jurídico (artículo 6 (1) (a) y el artículo 7 de la RGPD y del RGPD del Reino Unido, y el artículo 31 (1) de la nFADP.
    
* **Seguridad y protección de los derechos** . Proteger nuestros Servicios y nuestras operaciones comerciales, nuestros derechos y los de nuestras partes interesadas e inversores, así como prevenir y detectar fraudes, acceso y actividades no autorizadas, y otros tipos de abusos en torno a nuestro Sitio, lo que incluye las instancias en la que consideremos necesario investigar, prevenir o emprender acciones con respecto a actividades ilícitas, fraudes potenciales o situaciones que puedan atentar contra la seguridad o derechos de cualquier persona o tercero, o el incumplimiento de nuestros términos y condiciones. Para estos fines TMG opera con base en los "intereses legítimos" como fundamento jurídico (artículo 6 (1) (f) del RGPD y del RGPD del Reino Unido, y el artículo 31 (1) de la nFDAP. Evitar que el abuso de los servicios de TMG posibilite actos contractuales o ilícitos por parte de terceros es del interés legítimo de TMG y de los usuarios de TMG. Proteger las TI de TMG y, por ende, proteger la información personal de los usuarios de TMG también es de nuestro legítimo interés. Con respecto a la orientación sexual, TMG también opera con base al fundamento jurídico que le permite presentar, ejercer o defender reclamaciones judiciales (el artículo 9 (2) (f) del RGPD y del RGPD del Reino Unido).
    
* **Conformidad normativa y procesos legales** . Para cumplir con las leyes o regulaciones aplicables, lo que incluye la retención de información reglamentaria, o cumplir con procedimientos judiciales, responder a citatorios, órdenes judiciales, mandatos judiciales u otros procesos legales, o cumplir con las exigencias de una investigación o solicitud, ya sea esta de carácter formal o informal, tanto por parte de organismos de seguridad como por parte de autoridades gubernamentales. Para estos fines TMG opera con base en el "cumplimento de obligaciones legales" como fundamento jurídico (artículo 6 (1) (c) del RGPD y el RGPD del Reino Unido , así como artículo 31 (2) (a) de la nFADP) en caso de que esta obligación dimane de la UE o de la ley de un estado miembro de la Unión Europea, o (ii) con base en el "interés legítimo" como fundamento jurídico (artículo 6 (1) (f) del RGPD y del RGPD del Reino Unido, así como el artículo 31(1) de la nFADP) si esta obligación dimana de otra jurisdicción. En caso de que se trate de un interés legítimo, cumplir con las obligaciones legales pertinentes es del interés de TMG. Con respecto a la orientación sexual, TMG también opera con base al fundamento jurídico que le permite presentar, ejercer o defender reclamaciones judiciales (el artículo 9 (2) (f) del RGPD y del RGPD del Reino Unido).
    
* **Auditorías, reportes y otras operaciones internas** . Realizar auditorías financieras, tributarias y contables, así como evaluaciones y auditorías en torno a nuestras operaciones, lo que incluye tanto nuestros controles financieros, de privacidad y de seguridad, así como para el cumplimiento en torno al riesgo y la conformidad normativa. También podemos utilizar la información personal para mantener registros comerciales adecuados y hacer valer tanto nuestras políticas como procedimientos Para estos fines TMG opera con base en los "intereses legítimos" como fundamento jurídico (artículo 6 (1) (f) del RGPD y del RGPD del Reino Unido, y el artículo 31 (1) de la nFDAP. Proteger las operaciones comerciales y revisar constantemente el cumplimiento de nuestras obligaciones en torno a los reportes y a la conformidad normativa son del interés de TMG
    
* **Soporte general de naturaleza comercial y operativa** . Evaluar y ejecutar fusiones, adquisiciones, reestructuraciones, declaraciones de quiebra y otras transacciones comerciales, como es el caso de los financiamientos, y administrar nuestras funciones comerciales, contables, legales, de auditoría, de conformidad normativa y de registro. Para estos fines TMG opera con base en los "intereses legítimos" como fundamento jurídico (artículo 6(1)(f) del RGPD y el artículo 31(1)de la nFDAP). En este contexto , el procesamiento y la comunicación de la información en torno a sus activos y actividades a compradores o adquirientes potenciales, así como a sus asesores externos, es del interés de TMG para facilitar la venta de dichos activos o actividades.

Nuestros fines en torno al uso de cookies y otras tecnologías similares, particularmente aquellas relacionadas a la segmentación y el análisis, se detallan en la Sección 6, en el apartado "Cookies, segmentación y análisis.

El usuario tiene el derecho de retirar su consentimiento cuando el fundamento jurídico es el consentimiento del mismo. No obstante, retirar el consentimiento de esta manera no afectará la legalidad de cualquier procesamiento efectuado previo a que el usuario retirara su consentimiento. En la mayoría de los casos, el usuario también tienen el derecho de rehusarse en todo momento a que su información personal sea procesada debido a razones de naturaleza personal si el "interés legítimo" es el fundamento jurídico en cuestión. Además, el usuario tiene el derecho a oponerse en todo momento a que su información personal sea procesada con fines de mercadotecnia directa. El artículo 21 del RGPD y del RGPD del Reino Unido aplica en este sentido.

El usuario puede rehusarse a que correo electrónico sea utilizado para fines promociones o para la orientación personal, durante o después de la creación de su cuenta.

**4\. Comunicación de la información personal**

Nosotros podemos comunicar la información personal que recolectamos con los fines descritos anteriormente, para proporcionar nuestros Servicios al usuario, responder y cumplir sus peticiones, así como en los casos que se nos haya otorgado consentimiento de manera explícita, y esta será compartida con las siguientes partes:

* **Marcas, afiliadas y subsidiarias** . Nosotros podemos divulgar la información personal que recolectemos por medio de nuestras marcas, afiliadas y subsidiarias.
    
* **Socios comerciales** . TMG puede asociarse en ciertas circunstancias con otros negocios para ofrecer sus servicios, lo que incluye facilitar ciertos programas u ofertas especiales, y podemos compartir información personal a dichos socios comerciales
    
* **Comerciantes y proveedores de servicios** . Nosotros podemos comunicar la información que recolectamos a comerciantes y proveedores de servicios que cumplen funciones en nuestra representación, como es el caso de los servicios de TI y de hosting, el procesamiento de pagos, la mercadotecnia y los estudios de mercado, la atención al cliente, el almacenamiento de datos, el análisis de datos, los servicios de auditoría, los servicios de consultoría, y la asesoría legal.
    
* **Otros usuarios de TMG** . Con otros usuarios en el contexto de funciones específicas de naturaleza social. Por ejemplo, si el usuario invita a personas a que usen nuestro Servicio, o si se publica información en alguna de nuestras funciones, foros comunitarios o blogs de discusión públicos, lo que incluye la publicación de reseñas o testimonios, es posible que cierta información personal se encuentre disponible y pueda ser encontrada por otros usuarios de nuestros Servicios. Por ejemplo, si el usuario participa en Pets, otros usuarios de dicho juego podrán ver la información personal de dicho usuario, como la imagen de perfil, el género, el valor, el efectivo, los activos y el número de Pets.
    
* **Proveedores externos de mercadotecnia y análisis de datos** . También podemos compartir información personal, como información en torno al dispositivo, a la navegación, a las actividades y el uso a proveedores externos de mercadotecnia y análisis de datos, así como a otras empresas que proporcionen servicios de mercadotecnia, publicidad, gestión de campañas y análisis de datos en nuestra representación. Para un resumen de las partes en cuestión, consulte la Plataforma de gestión de consentimiento en la aplicación.

También podemos compartir información personal bajo las siguientes circunstancias:

* **Apoyo a las transferencias comerciales** . En caso de que alguna de nuestras filiales esté o pueda verse involucrada en una adquisición, fusión o inversión que implique a otra empresa, o si alguno de nuestros activos es o puede ser transferido a otra empresa, independiente de si esto se relaciona a una declaración de quiebra, procedimiento de insolvencia u otra circunstancia, nosotros podemos comunicar o transferir la información personal que hayamos recolectado del usuario con dicha empresa en conformidad con las leyes aplicables. También podemos comunicar cierta información personal según sea necesario previo a que concluya una transacción de esta naturaleza u otra transacción de naturaleza corporativa, como un financiamiento o reestructuración, y esta puede ser comunicada a prestamistas, auditores y asesores externos, lo que incluye abogados y consultores.
    
* **Conformidad normativa y obligaciones legales** . También podemos comunicar información personal a terceros de acuerdo a los requisitos por las leyes y obligaciones legales aplicables. Por ejemplo, podemos compartir información en respuesta a citatorios, órdenes judiciales y otro tipo de solicitudes de caracter legal por parte de entidades regulatorias, entidades gubernamentales y organismos de seguridad, lo que incluye dar respuesta en conformidad con la seguridad nacional o el orden público, o en conformidad a la ley u otros procesos legales. Además, y en caso de ser pertinente, nosotros podemos comunicar los nombres de los ganadores de nuestros concursos de acuerdo a la ley aplicable.
    
* **Seguridad y protección de los derechos** . En los casos en los cuales lo consideremos necesario para proteger nuestros Servicios, nuestros derechos y nuestra propiedad, o los derechos, la propiedad y la seguridad de terceros. Por ejemplo, podemos compartir información personal para (i) prevenir, detectar, investigar y responder a fraudes, actividades y accesos no autorizados, actividades ilícitas y el abuso de nuestros servicios, (ii) situaciones que puedan atentar contra la salud, la seguridad o los derechos de cualquier persona o tercero, o (iii) hacer cumplir, detectar, investigar, y emprender acción en respuesta al incumplimiento de nuestros términos y condiciones. También podemos compartir información personal relacionada al litigio y a otras reclamaciones o procedimientos legales en los que nosotros estemos involucrados, así como para nuestras funciones contables, legales, de auditoría, de conformidad normativa y de registro.
    
* **Otras maneras de comunicar la información** . También podemos comunicar información personal que no hayan sido descritas en este documento, siempre y cuando se le notifique al usuario de ello, de maneras en las que el usuario ha dado su consentimiento, o de acuerdo a requisitos legales.

Pese a lo descrito en esta Política, nosotros podemos usar y compartir datos agregados que hayan sido anonimizados y que se relacionen con nuestra actividad comercial y Servicios para fines de control de calidad y análisis de datos, así como para estudios, desarrollo y otros fines. Nosotros usaremos y mantendremos estos datos de manera anonimizada (datos que ya no poseen un vínculo razonable o que ya no pueden ser vinculados a una persona natural u hogar, o a algún dispositivo personal o del hogar) siempre que utilicemos, compartamos o procesemos datos anonimizados, y no intentaremos restablecer este vínculo de identificación, salvo para determinar que nuestros procesos de anonimización son razonables y adecuados, de conformidad con las leyes de privacidad aplicables.

**5\. Transferencia de los datos personales en el contexto de los países ajenos al EEE, al Reino Unido y a Suiza**

Los receptores de la información personal pueden ser ajenos al EEE, al Reino Unido o a Suiza. En el caso en que se transfiera información personal a ubicaciones ajenas al EEE, al Reino Unido o a Suiza (lo que incluye transferencias iniciadas por nosotros desde los EE.UU. como controladores de datos, en apego al RGPD, al RGPD del Reino Unido y a la nFDAP, a otros receptores ubicados en los EE.UU. o en países ajenos al EEE, al Reino Unido o a Suiza, que, a su vez, no se encuentren en apego al RGPD, ni al RGPD del Reino Unido ni a la nFDAP), obraremos de acuerdo a la ley, nos aseguraremos que los derechos de privacidad del usuario se protejan adecuadamente, ya sea porque la Comisión Europea haya dictaminado que el país al que le será transferido la información del usuario garantiza un nivel de protección adecuado (artículo 45 del RGPD y del RGPD del Reino Unido) o debido a que la transferencia está sujeta a una protección adecuada (por ejemplo, cláusulas estándar de protección de datos que la Unión Europea haya acordado con el país receptor) (artículo 46 del RGPD y el RGPD del Reino Unido), salvo que el RGPD o el RGPD del Reino Unido ofrezca una excepción (artículo 49 del RGPD y del RGPD del Reino Unido). Además, y en caso de ser pertinente, pretendemos acordar medidas adicionales con los receptores para asegurar un nivel de protección de datos adecuado. Véase de igual forma el artículo 16 f de la nFDAP en torno a la comunicación de la información personal fuera de Suiza.

En caso de ser necesario, nosotros agregamos un "Addendum del Reino Unido" con nuestros socios contractuales, de acuerdo a los requisitos de la Oficina del Comisario de Información y un "Addendum CH", de acuerdo a los requisitos del Comisario Federal de Protección de Datos e Información de Suiza (FDPIC).

Es posible solicitar una copia de las protecciones pertinentes (en la que medida que las utilicemos) y una lista de los receptores ajenos al EEE, al Reino Unida y a Suiza al comunicarse con [support@themeetgroup.com](mailto:support@themeetgroup.com). Sépase que dicha copia puede contener información censurada, a fin de proteger secretos confirmaciones e información confidencial de otros tipos.

**6\. Cookies, segmentación y análisis**

Nosotros y nuestros proveedores externos utilizamos cookies, pixeles, objetos de almacenamiento local, archivos de registro y otros mecanismos de rastreo para recolectar información en torno a la navegación, la actividad, el dispositivo e información similar dentro de nuestros Servicios de manera automática. Nosotros utilizamos esta información para analizar y comprender la manera en que el usuario accede, usa e interactúa con nuestros Servicios, detectar e identificar errores en nuestros Servicios, evaluar, asegurar, proteger, optimizar y mejorar el desempeño de nuestros Servicios, así como para fines analíticos y de mercadotecnia, y la personalización del contenido de nuestros Servicios. En función de la ubicación del usuario, la mayoría de estas acciones solo darán lugar si este ha dado su consentimiento por medio de nuestra plataforma de gestión de consentimiento (CMP), misma que se puede encontrar en la configuración de la aplicación para gestionar el consentimiento y las preferencias el usuario en torno a las cookies, la mercadotecnia dirigida y otros mecanismos de rastreo similares dentro de nuestros servicios, mismos que pueden ser consultados en la Sección 7, en el apartado "Elecciones de privacidad". Gran parte de estas elecciones se hacen en función del navegador y del dispositivo, por lo que es posible que el usuario requiera seleccionar sus preferencias por cada navegador y dispositivo que utilice para acceder a nuestros Servicios. Además, eliminar o bloquear las cookies puede requerir que estas preferencias se apliquen una vez más a cada dispositivo y navegador.

**Cookies** . Las "cookies" son pequeños archivos de texto que un sitio web visitado por un usuario puede almacenar en su dispositivo (por ejemplo, una computadora o un teléfono inteligente). Las cookies son creadas por el servidor de dicho sitio web y enviadas al navegador del usuario con el fin de que estas se almacenen para uso futuro. Algunas cookies nos permiten facilitarle al usuario la navegación en nuestros Servicios, mientras que otras pueden servir para agilizar el inicio de sesión, actuar en pro de la seguridad y el desempeño de nuestros Servicios, o permitirnos monitorear información agregada y estadística relacionada a la actividad del usuario al utilizar nuestros Servicios.

**Pixeles de rastreo** . Los pixeles de rastreo (también conocidos como balizas web o GIF invisibles) son pequeños gráficos con un identificador único, cuya función es similar a la de las cookies. Mientras que las cookies se almacenan localmente en el dispositivo del usuario, los pixeles de rastreo se incrustan de manera invisible en las páginas web y el contenido en línea. Podemos utilizarlos de la mano de nuestros Servicios para monitorear la actividad del usuario, asistirnos en la gestión del contenido y recopilar los estadísticos en torno al uso. También podemos utilizarlos en nuestros correos electrónicos para saber si estos han sido abiertos o reenviados, con el fin de monitorear las tasas de respuesta y medir la efectividad de nuestras comunicaciones.

**Archivos de registro** . Podemos recolectar cierta información de los archivos de registro. La información en los archivos de registro se captura cuando el usuario navega por nuestros Sitios. Nosotros capturamos cierta información en dichos archivos de registro, como solicitudes web, la dirección IP, el tipo y versión del navegador, el idioma, los enlaces de referidos y salidas, el historia de clics, las páginas vistas e información similar.

**Análisis por parte de terceros** . Nosotros podemos utilizar dispositivos, aplicaciones y herramientas automatizadas operadas por empresas externas, como es el caso de Google Analytics, para evaluar el uso de nuestros Servicios. Estas empresas externas pueden utilizar cookies, pixeles y otras tecnologías de rastreo para recolectar información en torno al uso de nuestros Servicios y generar reportes e indicadores que nos ayuden a evaluar el uso de nuestros Servicios, así como mejorar el desempeño y la experiencia del usuario. Para mayor información acerca de las prácticas de Google en torno a la privacidad, revísese su Política de Privacidad, misma que se encuentra albergada en el enlace a continuación: [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). El usuario también puede descargar el complemento de inhabilitación de Google Analytics para evitar que su información sea utilizada por Google Analytics, misma que se puede descargar por medio del enlace a continuación: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). Se puede acceder a una lista que incluye a todos los terceros con los que tratamos para estos fines por medio del CMP, mismo que se encuentra la configuración de la aplicación.

**Publicidad por parte de terceros** . Colaboramos con redes de publicidad externas, socios de mercadotecnia, redes de publicidad para dispositivos móviles y otras entidades ("empresas de publicidad externas") para personalizar nuestro contenido y mostrar publicidad dentro de nuestros Servicios, así como para gestionar nuestra publicidad en sitios web de terceros. Nosotros y dichas empresas de publicidad externas podemos utilizar cookies, pixeles de rastreo, SDK (kits de desarrollo de software) y otras herramientas para recolectar información en torno a la navegación y la actividad dentro de nuestros servicios (y dentro de los sitios y servicios de terceros), así como la dirección IP, el identificador único, las cookies y los ID de publicidad, así como otros identificadores en línea. Nosotros y dichas empresas de publicidad externas utilizamos esta información para proporcionarle publicidad y contenido de mayor relevancia al usuario, tanto de nuestros Servicios como en sitios web de terceros, así como para evaluar el éxito de dicha publicidad y contenido. Se puede acceder a una lista que incluye a todas las empresas de publicidad externas con las que tratamos por medio del CMP, mismo que se encuentra la configuración de la aplicación.

**Uso interdispositivo** . Nosotros y nuestros proveedores externos podemos utilizar la información que recolectamos (ya sea directamente de nuestros Sitios o Aplicación Móvil, los dispositivos del usuario o por medio de terceros) para ayudar a que nosotros y nuestros proveedores externos identifiquen otro dispositivos que utilice dicho usuario (por ejemplo, un teléfono móvil, una tableta, otra computadora, entre otros). Nosotros y nuestros proveedores externos también podemos utilizar el uso interdispositivo y otra información obtenida a partir del usuario en pro de la publicidad dirigida o para personalizar el contenido de nuestros Servicios.

**Cotejo de listas personalizadas** . Podemos compartir o comunicar cierta información contenida en las listas de clientes (como el nombre, el correo electrónico y otra información de contacto) con terceros, con el fin de mejorar nuestra publicidad y contenido dirigido en sitios web, plataformas y servicios de terceros. En algunos casos, estos terceros pueden ayudarnos a enriquecer nuestras listas de clientes con información demográfica adicional u otra información similar, con el fin de que podamos enfocar nuestros campañas de publicidad y mercadotecnia de una mejor manera.

**7\. Elecciones de privacidad**

**Gestión de las preferencias** . Nosotros le ofrecemos al usuario diferentes maneras de gestionar sus elecciones y preferencias en torno a la privacidad, como se explica a continuación:

* **Cuenta y perfil** . El usuario puede revisar y actualizar cierta información almacenada por nosotros al iniciar sesión en su cuenta y actualizar la información tanto en su cuenta como en su perfil.
    
* **Comunicaciones de mercadotecnia** . Nosotros enviamos correos electrónicos, contenido u otro tipo de comunicaciones similares al usuario de manera periódica. El usuario puede darse de baja y no recibir más este tipo de comunicaciones al seguir las instrucciones incluidas en dicha comunicación. Si el usuario se da de baja del servicio en el que se le envía material promocional, nosotros podemos seguirle enviando comunicaciones en torno a la cuenta u otros servicios que haya solicitado o recibido de nosotros. Además, es posible gestionar las preferencias de comunicación por medio de la configuración de cuenta y de perfil.
    
* **Notificaciones push** . El usuario puede elegir el tipo de notificaciones push que desee recibir al ajustar la configuración de su dispositivo móvil o al modificar la configuración de nuestra Aplicación Móvil. Estos mensajes se envían como parte del cumplimiento de contrato, así como información promocional.

**Preferencias de rastreo, de cookies, de publicidad dirigida y de análisis** . También ofrecemos diversas maneras en las que el usuario puede gestionar sus preferencias en torno a las cookies, la publicidad dirigida, el análisis y otros mecanismos de rastreo similares en nuestros Servicios. Gran parte de estas elecciones se hacen en función del navegador y del dispositivo, por lo que es posible que el usuario requiera seleccionar sus preferencias por cada navegador y dispositivo que utilice para acceder a nuestros Servicios.Además, eliminar o bloquear las cookies puede requerir que estas preferencias se apliquen una vez más a cada dispositivo y navegador. Asimismo, darse de baja de las cookies y la publicidad no implica que el usuario dejará de recibir publicidad por parte de nosotros, ya que puede seguir recibiendo publicidad genérica o "contextual" por parte de nosotros.

* **Plataforma de gestión de consentimiento.** El usuario puede utilizar la plataforma de gestión de consentimiento, misma que es provista previo al uso de las cookies y los mecanismos rastreo, con el fin de evitar que los elementos no esenciales rastreen la actividad dentro de nuestros Sitios o nuestra Aplicación Móvil. Una vez que se otorgue consentimiento, este puede ser retirado en todo momento para tener efecto en el futuro. Para mayor información, consulte la Sección 15 en el apartado "Información adicional acerca de la privacidad en ciertas jurisdicciones", mismo que incluye información adicional acerca de los derechos de privacidad de los residentes de ciertas jurisdicciones.
    
* **Configuración de las cookies** . El usuario puede configurar su navegador para que este bloqueé ciertas cookies o notificarla cuando una nueva cookie instale con el fin de prevenir que las cookies rastreen su actividad en nuestros Sitios al visitar múltiples sitios web. También es posible eliminar las cookies La sección "Ayuda" ubicada en la barra de herramientas de la mayoría de los exploradores cuentan con indicaciones para evitar que el dispositivo en cuestión acepte nuevas cookies, para recibir notificaciones cuando se reciban nuevas cookies o para el borrado de cookies. Los visitantes en nuestros Sitios que deshabiliten las cookies podrán seguir navegando en el Sitio, pero algunas funciones pueden no funcionar.
    
* **Señales de navegadores** . Salvo que la ley aplicable disponga lo contrario, si nuestros Sitios detectan que un navegador transmite una señal de preferencia que rechaza cookies, como es el caso de una señal de "control de privacidad global" (o GPC), nosotros aplicaremos dicha señal para que el navegador en cuestión en ese dispositivo no reciba cookies en nuestros Sitios. En caso de que el usuario acceda a nuestros Sitios desde un dispositivo o navegador diferente, será necesario también aplicar el GPC para dicho explorador y dispositivo.
    
* **Programas de elección de publicidad de la industria** . El usuario también puede controlar el uso que le dan las empresas de publicidad externas a la información que recolectan en torno a las visitas a nuestros Sitios y a los sitios de dichos terceros, con la intención de mostrar publicidad dirigida de mayor relevancia. Visítese [www.YourOnlineChoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/) para más información y asistencia en torno a los mecanismos de rastreo web.

Es posible que los residentes de cierta jurisdicciones cuenten con derechos adicionales en torno a la información personal, de acuerdo a los dispuesto en la Sección 15, en el apartado "Información adicional acerca de la privacidad en ciertas jurisdicciones".

**8\. Período de almacenamiento de la información personal**

Nosotros almacenamos la información personal por el tiempo necesario para lograr los fines mencionados en la Sección 3, "Fines para la recolección y el procesamiento de la información", y la Sección 6, "Cookies, segmentación y análisis", o por el tiempo que nosotros tengamos un interés legítimo para almacenarla. Nosotros borramos la información en el resto de los casos, salvo la información que debemos almacenar para cumplir con la retención de información reglamentaria, (por ejemplo, debido a leyes tributarias o comerciales, como es el caso de las facturas). Nosotros restringimos el procesamiento de la información personal que se almacena por una obligación de retención.

La información acerca de la duración del almacenamiento de las cookies y otros mecanismos de rastreo se puede encontrar en nuestro CMP, mismo que se encuentra disponible en la configuración de la aplicación.

**9\. Enlaces y funciones externas**

Nuestros Servicios pueden incluir enlaces a sitios web o funciones de terceros, o ofrecer ciertas conexiones por medio de terceros o servicios. Este Política no rige el acceso y uso de dichos sitios web o funciones, ya que esto se rige por medio de la Política de Privacidad de los terceros en cuestión Nosotros no no hacemos responsable por las prácticas de información de dihos terceros, lo que incluye la recolección, el uso y la comunicación de la información personal. Se recomienda revisar las políticas de privacidad y los términos de cualquier tercero antes de acceder a sus sitios web o utilizar dichas funciones.

**10\. Contenido generado por usuarios**

Nosotros podemos ofrecer funciones, foros comunitarios o blogs de discusión públicos en relación a nuestros Servicios para brindarle a los usuarios la posibilidad de compartir información acerca de nuestros Servicios u otras cuestiones de interés (por ejemplo, reseñas, testimonios y preguntas). Debe tenerse en cuenta que cualquier comunicación enviada o publicada a través de cualquier función interactiva en nuestros Servicios puede ser vista y encontrada por otros, lo que incluye a los usuarios de TMG y al público en general. El usuario no puede tener expectativa alguna de privacidad o confidencialidad al enviar o publicar contenido a través de dichas funciones públicas, independientemente de si dicho contenido contiene o no información personal.

**11\. Seguridad**

Hemos tomado precauciones razonables para proteger la información que recolectados de posible pérdida, abuso, así como el acceso, la comunicación, la alteración y la destrucción no autorizadas. Sépase que, pese a nuestros mejores esfuerzos, no hay medidas de seguridad de datos que garanticen seguridad.

**12\. Privacidad infantil**

Nuestros Servicios no están diseñados para niños, y nosotros no recolectamos intencionalmente información personal de personas menores de dieciocho años (18). En caso de enterarnos de haber recolectado información personal de personas menores de 18 años por medio de nuestros servicios, se tomarán las medidas necesarias para eliminar dicha información. En caso de que un padre o tutor legal sospeche que hemos recolectado la información de su hijo en contra la ley aplicable, le pedimos nos contacte por medio de la información de contacto provista en este documento.

**13\. Cambios a esta Política**

Esta Política se encuentra vigente en función de la fecha previamente compartida. Nosotros podemos cambiar, actualizar o modificar esta Política de manera regular, por lo que es necesario revisarla de manera periódica. Todas las actualizaciones a esta Política se publicarán aquí.En caso de que se efectúe algún cambio a esta política que tenga un impacto material en nuestras prácticas en torno al uso de la información recolectada previamente de un usuario, nosotros enviaremos un aviso, ya sea por correo electrónico, o por medio de un aviso visible en nuestros Sitios, nuestra Aplicación Móvil o nuestros Servicios.

**14\. Información de contacto**

Para cualquier duda o aclaración en torno a esta Política o nuestras prácticas de privacidad, le pedimos que se nos contacte por medio del siguiente correo electrónico [support@themeetgroup.com](mailto:support@themeetgroup.com) o a la siguiente dirección:

The Meet Group, Inc.

100 Union Square Drive

New Hope, PA 18938

Nuestro delegado de protección de datos se encuentra en:

ePrivacy GmbH, con el Prof. Dr. Christoph Bauer como representante, Große Bleichen 21, 20354 Hamburgo, [privacy@themeetgroup.com](mailto:privacy@themeetgroup.com)

Para cualquier solicitud en torno a la seguridad de datos, contacte a nuestro delegado de protección de datos en [privacy@themeetgroup.com](mailto:privacy@themeetgroup.com).

Nuestro representante de la UE, de acuerdo al artículo 27 del RGPD, puede ser contactado en: ParshipMeet Holding GmbH, Speersort 10, 20095 Hamburgo, correo electrónico: [privacy@parshipmeet.com](mailto:privacy@parshipmeet.com)

La información acerca de nuestro representante del Reino Unido, de acuerdo al artículo 27 del RGPD del Reino Unido, vienen descritos en la Sección 15.B, "Información adicional para los residentes del Reino Unido

La información acerca de nuestro representante de Suiza, de acuerdo al artículo 14 de la nFDAP (la nueva Ley Federal de Protección de Datos de Suiza) vienen descritos en la Sección 15.C,"Información adicional para los residentes de Suiza".

Treforma AG c/o MLL Legal; Grabenstrasse 25; 6340 Baar; Suiza; [meetgroup@dsg-mll.com](mailto:meetgroup@dsg-mll.com)

**15\. Información adicional acerca de la privacidad en ciertas jurisdicciones**

Los residentes de cierta jurisdicciones cuentan con derechos adicionales de acuerdo a las leyes de privacidad aplicables, como se ha detallado en la Sección

**A: RGPD**

Los residentes de la Unión Europea cuentan con los siguientes derechos de acuerdo al RGPD, siempre y cuando se cumplan los requisitos legales de cada derecho:

**Derecho de acceso** - El usuario puede solicitar información acerca del procesamiento de su información personal y una copia de la información personal que está siendo procesada hasta la fecha, siempre y cuando dicha copia no afecte los derechos y libertades de los demás, y en ausencia de alguna otra excepción.

**Derecho de rectificación** - El usuario puede solicitar la corrección de su información personal que sea imprecisa o de completar información que se encuentre incompleta.

**Derecho al olvido** - El usuario puede solicitar la eliminación de su información personal, en especial

* cuando la información personal ya no es necesaria para el cumplimiento de los fines por los que se recolectó o procesó;
    
* ya se ha presentado el retiro del consentimiento en función del procesamiento y no existe un fundamento jurídico que justifique su procesamiento;
    
* se rehusó al procesamiento basado en los "intereses legítimos" como fundamento jurídico y no existe justificación legal que anule el rechazo al procesamiento con fines de mercadotecnia directa;
    
* los datos personales han sido procesados de manera ilícita
    
* o la información personal debe ser eliminada para cumplir con obligaciones legales que nos incumben.

Sin embargo, el derecho al olvido no aplica si el procesamiento de la información personal es necesario para cumplir con una obligación legal para presentar, ejercer o defender reclamaciones judiciales.

**Derecho a restringir el procesamiento** - El usuario puede solicitar se restrinja del procesamiento

* por el período de tiempo en el que nosotros comprobados la exactitud de su información personal si se disputó su exactitud;
    
* si el procesamiento es ilícito y se solicita que se restrinja el procesamiento en lugar de que esta información se elimine;
    
* nosotros ya no necesitamos la información persona, pero el usuario la requiere para presentar, ejercer o defender un reclamo jurídico, o
    
* si se objeta al procesamiento que opera bajo los "intereses legítimos" como fundamento legal hasta que se compruebe si nuestra justificación legal anula sus intereses, derechos y libertades.

**Derecho a la portabilidad de los datos** - El usuario puede solicitar que se le envíe la información que nos brindó originalmente, en formato informático común, y que dichos datos le sean transmitidos a otro controlador de datos sin obstaculización alguna de nuestra parte, siempre y cuando el procesamiento parta del consentimiento el cumplimiento de un contrato, y que el procesamiento se realice por medios automatizados; en estos casos, el usuario también puede solicitar que su información personal le sea enviada a otro controlador de datos con el que esto sea posible.

Además, el usuario cuenta con los siguientes derechos:

**Derecho a retirar el consentimiento -** El usuario puede retirar su consentimiento en todo momento cuando el procesamiento parta del consentimiento del mismo, sin que esto surja efecto alguno en la legalidad del procesamiento previo que se retirara dicho consentimiento.

**Derecho a oposición -**

**El usuario tiene derecho a oponerse en todo momento, con una justificación basada en sus circunstancias individuales, al procesamiento de sus datos personales cuando este se base en el legítimo interés de un tercero (artículo 6 (1) (f) RGPD). Nosotros dejaremos de procesar la información personal del usuario debido al fin al que este se ha opuesto, salvo que nosotros podamos presentar una justificación legal pertinente que anule los intereses, derechos y libertades del usuario, así como para presentar, ejercer o defender una reclamación jurídica.**

**Además, el usuario tiene el derecho a oponerse en todo momento a que su información personal sea procesada con fines de mercadotecnia directa. Si el usuario se opone al procesamiento con fines de mercadotecnia directa, dejaremos de procesar dicha información personal para esos fines.**

* * *

**Derecho a interponer una queja -** El usuario puede interponer una queja a una autoridad de supervisión, en especial en el estado miembro correspondiente a su residencia, lugar de trabajo o lugar de una supuesta infracción en caso de que el usuario considere que el procesamiento de su información personal transgrede el RGPD.

Nuestra autoridad de protección competente es:

Ciudad Libre y Hanseática de Hamburgo, el comisario de protección de datos y libertas de la información, , Ludwig-Erhard-Str. 22, 20459 Hamburgo, correo electrónico: [mailbox@datenschutz.hamburg.de](mailto:mailbox@datenschutz.hamburg.de)

**B. UK GDPR**

Los residentes de Reino Unido cuentan con los siguientes derechos de acuerdo al RGPD del Reino Unido y a las leyes de protecciones de datos: El alcance y aplicabilidad de estos derechos puede variar en función de las circunstancias. El usuario debe utilizar la información de contacto provista en este documento para ejercer cualquiera de estos derechos: Los derechos son:

**Derecho a estar informado** -- El usuario tiene el derecho a recibir información concisa, transparente, inteligible y de fácil uso acerca de su información personal y el uso que le damos a ella. Mediante esta Política informamos al usuario de esta información. Para dudas o aclaraciones, el usuario deberá utilizar la información de contacto provista en este documento.

**Derecho al acceso** -- El usuario tiene el derecho de solicitarnos copias de su información personal. Este derecho siempre es aplicable, pero hay algunas excepciones con respecto a su aplicación, lo que significa que no siempre se recibirá la información solicitada. Al momento de solicitar esta información, esto se conoce como una solicitud de acceso del sujeto a los datos (DSAR). Nosotros podemos solicitarle documentación de identificación al usuario para verificar su identidad tras la recepción de una DSAR.

**Derecho a la rectificación** -- El usuario tiene el derecho de solicitarnos que rectifiquemos información personal que considere imprecisa. También tiene el derecho de solicitar que completemos información que considere incompleta.

**Derecho al olvido** -- El usuario tiene el derecho de solicitarnos que eliminemos su información personal bajo ciertas circunstancias. Nosotros tenemos el derecho a negarnos a cumplir una solicitud de olvido si estamos procesando información personal por una de las siguientes razones:

* Ejercer el derecho de la libre expresión e información.
    
* Cumplir con una obligación legal.
    
* Desempeñar una labor de interés público o el ejercicio de una autoridad oficial.
    
* Fines de archivo de interés público, de interés de estudio científico, de investigación histórica o por fines estadísticos.
    
* Ejercer o defender un reclamo jurídico.

**Derecho a restringir el procesamiento** -- El usuario tiene el derecho de restringir que nosotros procesemos su información personal bajo ciertas circunstancias. De ser así, nosotros conservaremos la información, pero dejaremos de procesarla. Este derecho es una alternativa al derecho de olvido. El usuario puede ejercer su derecho a restringir el procesamiento si una de las siguientes condiciones aplica:

* Se disputa la exactitud de la información personal.
    
* El procesamiento de la información personal es ilícito.
    
* Ya no necesitamos procesar dicha información personal, pero esta se requiere como parte de un proceso legal.
    
* Se ha ejercido el derecho de oposición y el procesamiento se encuentra restringido, en espera de una decisión en torno al estatus del procesamiento.

**Derecho de oposición al procesamiento -- El usuario tiene el derecho a oponerse al procesamiento en ciertas circunstancias, en las que se incluye la mercadotecnia directa. El usuario también se puede oponer al procesamiento si este opera con base a nuestros intereses legítimos (o los de un tercero) Nosotros dejaremos de procesar la información personal del usuario debido al fin al que este se ha opuesto, salvo que nosotros podamos presentar una justificación legal pertinente que anule los intereses, derechos y libertades del usuario, así como para presentar, ejercer o defender una reclamación jurídica.**

**Derecho a la portabilidad de datos** -- El usuario tiene el derecho a recibir su información personal de manera estructura, en un formato informático común, pero esto solo aplica si estamos procesando dicha información debido al consentimiento del usuario, o en cumplimiento de un contrato y el procesamiento es automatizado.

**Derecho a retirar el consentimiento -** El usuario puede retirar su consentimiento en todo momento cuando el procesamiento parta del consentimiento del mismo, sin que esto surja efecto alguno en la legalidad del procesamiento previo que se retirara dicho consentimiento.

**Información de contacto**

En caso de que el usuario desee ejercer cualquiera de sus derechos o tenga alguna duda en torno al uso de su información personal, se le pide que utilice la información en la sección "Contáctenos". Se le pide al usuario proporcionar suficiente información al momento de utilizar este recurso para poderlo identificar de manera clara.

Sépase que contamos con un representante del Reino Unido designado para que sea contacto en nuestra representación, de acuerdo al artículo 27 del RGPD del Reino Unido: eHarmony UK Ltd., 6-10 Great Portland Street, Londres W1W 8QL, Gran Bretaña

**Transferencia de la información personal fuera del Reino Unido**

Para información en torno a la protección y las salvaguardas aplicadas a la información personal del usuario al transferirla fuera del Reino Unido, consulte la Sección 5, "Transferencias de información personal en el contexto de países ajenos al EEE, el Reino Unido y Suiza".

**Derecho a interponer una queja por medio de una autoridad de supervisión**

El usuario tiene el derecho a interponer una queja a una autoridad de protección de datos.

El usuario puede contactar a la autoridad de protección de datos del Reino Unido, la Oficina del Comisario de Información: Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF, Número telefponico: + 44 (0) 303 123 1113, Correo electrónico: [casework@ico.org.uk](mailto:casework@ico.org.uk).

**C. Ley de protección de datos de Suiza**

**Derecho al acceso** -- El usuario tiene el derecho de solicitarnos copias de su información personal. Este derecho siempre es aplicable, pero hay algunas excepciones con respecto a su aplicación, lo que significa que no siempre se recibirá la información solicitada. Al momento de solicitar esta información, esto se conoce como una solicitud de acceso del sujeto a los datos (DSAR).

**Derecho a la rectificación** -- El usuario tiene el derecho de solicitarnos que rectifiquemos información personal que considere imprecisa. También tiene el derecho de solicitar que completemos información que considere incompleta.

**Derecho al olvido** -- El usuario tiene el derecho de solicitarnos que eliminemos su información personal bajo ciertas circunstancias. Nosotros tenemos el derecho a negarnos a cumplir una solicitud de olvido si estamos procesando información personal por una de las siguientes razones:

* Ejercer el derecho de la libre expresión e información.
    
* Cumplir con una obligación legal.
    
* Desempeñar una labor de interés público o el ejercicio de una autoridad oficial.
    
* Fines de archivo de interés público, de interés de estudio científico, de investigación histórica o por fines estadísticos.
    
* Ejercer o defender un reclamo jurídico.

**Derecho a restringir el procesamiento** -- El usuario tiene el derecho de restringir que nosotros procesemos su información personal bajo ciertas circunstancias. De ser así, nosotros conservaremos la información, pero dejaremos de procesarla. Este derecho es una alternativa al derecho de olvido. El usuario puede ejercer su derecho a restringir el procesamiento si una de las siguientes condiciones aplica:

* Se disputa la exactitud de la información personal.
    
* El procesamiento de la información personal es ilícito.
    
* Ya no necesitamos procesar dicha información personal, pero esta se requiere como parte de un proceso legal.
    
* Se ha ejercido el derecho de oposición y el procesamiento se encuentra restringido, en espera de una decisión en torno al estatus del procesamiento.

**Derecho de oposición al procesamiento** -- El usuario tiene el derecho a oponerse al procesamiento en ciertas circunstancias. El usuario también se puede oponer al procesamiento si este se efectúa en virtud de una labor de interés público, el ejercicio de una autoridad oficial conferida, o nuestros intereses legítimos (o los de un tercero).

**Derecho de oposición a la mercadotecnia directa** - El usuario también se puede oponer en todo momento al procesamiento de su información personal para fines publicitarios ("oposición a la publicidad"). Es necesario que se tome en cuenta que, por motivos organizaciones, puede existir un traslape entre la revocación solicitada por el usuario y el uso de los datos en el contexto en una campaña activa.

**Derecho a la portabilidad de los datos** -- Este derecho solo aplica si la información se procesa debido al consentimiento del usuario, o para cumplir un contrato y el proceso sea automatizado.

En caso de que el usuario desee ejercer cualquiera de sus derechos, se le pide que utilice la información en la sección "Contáctenos". Se le pide al usuario proporcionar suficiente información al momento de utilizar este recurso para poderlo identificar de manera clara.

**Información de contacto**

En caso de que el usuario desee ejercer cualquiera de sus derechos o tenga alguna duda en torno al uso de su información personal, se le pide que utilice la información en la sección "Contáctenos". Se le pide al usuario proporcionar suficiente información al momento de utilizar este recurso para poderlo identificar de manera clara.

Sépase que contamos con un representante de Suiza, de acuerdo al artículo 14 de la nFDAP (la nueva Ley Federal de Protección de Datos de Suiza): Treforma AG c/o MLL Legal; Grabenstrasse 25; 6340 Baar; Suiza; [meetgroup@dsg-mll.com](mailto:meetgroup@dsg-mll.com)

**Transferencias de información personal fuera de Suiza**

Para información en torno a la protección y las salvaguardas aplicadas a la información personal del usuario al transferirla fuera de Suiza, consulte la Sección 5, "Transferencias de información personal en el contexto de países ajenos al EEE, el Reino Unido y Suiza".

**Derecho a interponer una queja por medio de una autoridad de supervisión**

El usuario tiene el derecho a interponer una queja a una autoridad de protección de datos.

El usuario tiene el derecho a interponer una queja a una autoridad de protección de datos de Suiza. Esta autoridad es:

El Comisario Federal de Protección de Datos e Información de Suiza (FDPIC).

El usuario puede contactarlo al visitar el enlace a continuación:

[https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/de/home/deredoeb/kontakt/kontaktformular\_bgoe.html](https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/de/home/deredoeb/kontakt/kontaktformular_bgoe.html)

**The Meet Group Inc.**

Política de Privacidade para utilizadores com residência no Espaço Económico Europeu ou no Reino Unido
======================================================================================================

_Última atualização: October 8, 2024_

O The Meet Group, Inc., as suas marcas, filiais e subsidiárias valorizam a sua privacidade. Esta Política de Privacidade (" **Política** ") descreve como o The Meet Group, Inc. (" **TMG** ", " " **nós** ," " **nosso** ," ou " **\-nos** ) recolhe, utiliza, divulga e trata os dados pessoais (também referidos como informações pessoais em algumas jurisdições) descritos nesta Política , bem como os direitos e as escolhas disponíveis em relação aos mencionados dados pessoais.

Para obter mais informações sobre as opções de privacidade disponíveis em relação aos seus dados pessoais, consulte a Secção 7. As suas escolhas de privacidade , bem como a Secção 15. Privacidade adicional Informação para certas jurisdições, que inclui mais informações sobre os direitos de privacidade para os residentes em determinadas jurisdições.

Se residir na UE/Espaço Económico Europeu (EEE), consulte a Secção 15.A. Informação adicional para residentes na UE/EEE sobre os seus direitos ao abrigo do Regulamento Geral de Proteção de Dados Pessoais ("GDPR").

Se residir no Reino Unido, consulte a Secção 15.B. Informação adicional para residentes no Reino Unido para sobre os seus direitos ao abrigo do Regulamento Geral de Proteção de Dados Pessoais conforme incorporado no direito do Reino Unido em virtude da secção 3 da Lei da União Europeia (Retirada) do Reino Unido de 2018 ("RGPD UK").

Se residir na Suíça, consulte a Secção 15.C. Informações adicionais para residentes na Suíça sobre os seus direitos ao abrigo da nova Lei Suíça de Proteção de Dados ("nDSG").

Quando cria um perfil num dos nossos Serviços, alguns dos seus dados pessoais como o nome de utilizador, nome, idade, sexo e orientação sexual de acordo com as suas definições de privacidade podem ser igualmente visualizáveis pelos utilizadores do respetivo Serviço e dos nossos outros Serviços e outras aplicações que possuímos e outras aplicações e sites que não nos pertençam com os quais partilhemos a nossa plataforma em direto. Estes outros utilizadores estão localizados em todo o mundo. Para obter uma lista dos nossos atuais parceiros de direto, clique [aqui](https://talent.tagged.com/partner-policy-tagged.html).

A sua utilização dos nossos Serviços está sujeita às nossas [Termos de Serviço](https://secure.tagged.com/terms_of_service.html) Condições, incluindo os termos aplicáveis que regulam as limitações de danos e a resolução de litígios.

**Índice**

1. Âmbito
    
2. Dados pessoais recolhidos
    
3. Finalidades de recolha e tratamento
    
4. Divulgações de dados pessoais
    
5. Transferências de dados pessoais no âmbito dos países fora do EEE/UK/CH
    
6. «Cookies», direcionamento e análise
    
7. As suas escolhas de privacidade
    
8. Período de conservação dos dados pessoais
    
9. Hiperligações e funcionalidades externas
    
10. Conteúdo produzido pelo utilizador
    
11. Segurança
    
12. Privacidade das crianças
    
13. Alterações a esta Política
    
14. Contact Us
    
15. Informações de privacidade adicionais para determinadas jurisdições

**1\. Âmbito**

Exceto descrição em contrário abaixo, esta Política aplica-se aos dados pessoais que o TMG recolhe e trata relacionados com: visitantes do nosso site onde esta Política estiver publicada, incluindo qualquer dos nossos sites que tenha uma ligação ou publique esta Política (os " **Sites** "); pessoas que descarregam e utilizam a nossa aplicação móvel (" **Aplicação móvel** ", por exemplo, a aplicação Tagged ou a a aplicação Pets); pessoas que se registam ou participam nos nossos eventos, inquéritos, pesquisas, promoções e sorteios realizados por nós; e pessoas que comunicam ou colaboram de outra forma ou interagem connosco ou com os serviços disponíveis através dos nossos Sites, Aplicação móvel ou outros serviços online (referidos coletivamente como os " **Serviços** ").

**2\. Dados pessoais recolhidos**

Conforme descrito mais adiante, podemos recolher dados pessoais diretamente de si, de fontes de terceiros e automaticamente através da sua utilização dos nossos Serviços.

**Dados pessoais recolhidos diretamente de si** . Embora os dados pessoais que recolhemos variem consoante a sua utilização dos nossos Serviços e as nossas interações consigo, de uma forma geral, podemos recolher as seguintes categorias de dados pessoais diretamente de si:

* **Dados de contacto** . Quando você nos contactar, incluindo se nos enviar uma mensagem ou se registar para saber mais sobre os nossos Serviços, podemos recolher o seu nome, endereço de e-mail, número de telefone ou outros identificadores semelhantes, bem como a sua mensagem, a natureza da sua consulta e qualquer outra informação que tenha decidido proporcionar.
    
* **Dados sobre a conta e o perfil** . Quando você se registar para abrir uma conta associada aos nossos Serviços (p. ex, uma conta Tagged), podemos recolher o seu nome, endereço de e-mail, número de telefone, morada (p. ex., código postal), nome de utilizador e senha, data de nascimento e género, orientação sexual, imagem e fotografia de perfil e morada de faturação , bem como qualquer outra informação proporcionada relativamente à criação ou manutenção da sua conta ou que, de outra forma, nos envie através da sua conta.

Se tiver escolhido realizar um início de sessão através de fornecedores terceiros, como o Facebook ou a Apple ou então de SMS, não introduz um endereço de e-mail, nem uma senha no processo de registo. Os utilizadores acedem então ao nosso Serviço usando o endereço de e-mail que forneceram e a senha que selecionaram (credenciais de início de sessão), ou, alternativamente, usando as credenciais de início de sessão do fornecedor terceiro .

**Registo através do Facebook ("início de sessão do Facebook")**

Oferecemos um início de sessão único através do Facebook. Esta opção permite-lhe fazer o registo através da sua conta do Facebook. Se utilizar a função, nós recebemos e processamos os seguintes dados de autenticação do Facebook para o registo: o endereço de e-mail, nome de perfil, sexo, data de nascimento e fotografia de perfil guardada. Os dados são transferidos deste modo.

Quando inicia a sessão no nosso site ou na aplicação usando o Facebook, este também recolhe dados de «scripts» de terceiros, faz o seu tratamento para as finalidades analíticas do Facebook ou encaminha-os para terceiros. A Política de Privacidade do Facebook descreve os dados que podem ser recolhidos quando você utiliza o início de sessão desta plataforma. Isto inclui dados sobre o seu dispositivo, a sua utilização do nosso Serviço, os «sites» que visitou e os anúncios que visualizou. Infelizmente, você não pode, de uma forma técnica, recusar este tratamento em associação com o nosso Serviço. Se não quiser que o Facebook recolha dados sobre si relacionados com a sua utilização da nossa oferta online e que os utilize para as suas próprias finalidades , não deve usar o início de sessão através do Facebook.

Pode desassociar a sua conta Tagged da conta do Facebook em qualquer momento. Neste caso, precisamos que proporcione os dados de acesso mencionados acima.

A informação adicional sobre a finalidade e o alcance da recolha e do tratamento e utilização suplementar dos seus dados pelo Facebook, bem como sobre os seus direitos e opções de configuração para proteger os dados está disponível em Política de Privacidade do Facebook: [http://www.facebook.com/policy.php](http://www.facebook.com/policy.php).

**Registo / início de sessão através do Google**

Se utilizar um dispositivo Android, dispõe da opção de registo ou de início da sessão no nosso Serviço através da sua conta Google. Se fizer isto, a Google Ireland Limited, Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Irlanda (" Google ") irá proporcionar-nos os dados necessários para o registo ou o início de sessão (endereço de e-mail, nome, ID da Conta Google e fotografia de perfil da Conta Google ).

Não controlamos o âmbito dos dados recolhidos pela Google quando utilizar o início de sessão Google. Se não quiser que a Google recolha dados sobre si relacionados com a sua utilização da nossa oferta online e que os use nas suas próprias finalidades, não deve usar o início de sessão do Google.

A informação adicional sobre a finalidade e o âmbito da recolha e do tratamento e utilização suplementar dos seus dados pela Google, bem como sobre os seus direitos e opções de configurações para proteger os dados está disponível na Política de Privacidade do Google: [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

**Registo / início de sessão através do Apple Sign-In**

Se utilizar um dispositivo final iOS, dispõe da opção de registo ou de início de sessão no nosso Serviço através da Apple. Se decidir fazer isto, a Apple Inc., One Apple Park Way, Cupertino, Califórnia, EUA, 95014 ("Apple") irá proporcionar-nos a informação que você tiver selecionado e necessária para o registo ou o início de sessão (p. ex., endereço de «e-mail» gerado pela Apple, o nome).

Não controlamos o âmbito dos dados recolhidos pela Apple quando utilizar o início de sessão Apple. Se não quiser que a Apple recolha dados sobre si relacionados com a sua utilização da nossa oferta online e que os use nas suas próprias finalidades, não deve usar o início de sessão Apple.

A informação adicional sobre a finalidade e o âmbito da recolha e do tratamento e utilização suplementar dos seus dados pela Apple, bem como sobre os seus direitos e opções de configuração para proteger os dados está disponível em Política de Privacidade Apple: [https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/en/sign-in-with-apple/](https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/en/sign-in-with-apple/).

**Quando fizer o registo / início de sessão através de autenticação telefónica**

Ao fazer o registo / início da sessão através de autenticação telefónica, dispomos da opção de autenticar com o seu número de telemóvel, pelo que precisa de nos fornecer o seu número de telemóvel. Em seguida, iremos enviar-lhe um SMS com um código de verificação que tem de introduzir na aplicação para completar o processo de registo. Quando quiser iniciar a sessão, iremos enviar-lhe um SMS com um código que pode usar para iniciar a sessão na sua conta. Para além disso, também ocorre um processo de verificação. Este serviço é prestado pela Sinch America Inc., uma sociedade do Delaware, Departamento Jurídico, 3500 Lenox Rd NE, Ste. 1875, Atlanta, GA 30326, Georgia, Estados Unidos da América

e que somente é possível se nos conceder o seu consentimento prévio.

Mais informação sobre a finalidade e o âmbito do tratamento dos seus dados pela Sinch podem ser encontrados na política de privacidade da Sinch: [https://www.sinch.com/privacy-notice/](https://www.sinch.com/privacy-notice/)

* **Compras, pagamentos e recompensas** . Quando fizer uma compra ou pagamento através dos nossos Serviços (p. ex., com ligação a uma função do nosso jogo Pets) , podemos recolher dados como a forma de pagamento, dados do cartão de pagamento , faturação, informações sobre a compra e qualquer outra informação financeira ou comercial necessária para prestar os nossos Serviços.
    
* **Comunicações e interações** . Quando envia e-mails, telefona ou comunica ou interage, sob qualquer outra forma, connosco ou com outros utilizadores do TMG, incluindo se subscrever as nossas listas de correio, preencher os formulários nos nossos «Sites» ou Aplicação móvel, se interagir com as nossas páginas das redes sociais, publicar uma análise ou testemunho, enviar conteúdo em qualquer grupo de discussão «online» ou introduzir, de qualquer outro modo, informações em campos de comentários orientados para o público , blogues ou fóruns da comunidade patrocinados ou associados ao TMG, podemos recolher, receber e manter registos do seu contacto detalhes, comunicações e interações, das suas publicações ou envios e das nossas respostas, se for aplicável.
    
* **Informação promocional** . Se aceitar receber as nossas comunicações de «marketing» , podemos recolher o seu nome, endereço de «e-mail», número de telefone, preferências e, se for relevante, informações sobre a sua conta e perfil, incluindo os serviços e as funcionalidades que utiliza. Se participar nas nossas atividades especiais, ofertas, programas ou promoções, também podemos recolher determinados dados de contacto, a idade e qualquer outra informação que possa ser exigida por lei. Se ganhar uma promoção, também podemos ter de recolher determinada informação fiscal e/ou de renúncias e isenções, dependendo do prémio.
    
* **Respostas e opinião** . Se participar em inquéritos, questionários ou atividades de investigação ou iniciativas conduzidas por nós, para efeitos da satisfação do utilizador ou outras semelhantes, podemos recolher as suas respostas e opiniões e qualquer outra informação que tenha decidido proporcionar.
    
* **Eventos e detalhes de registo** . Também podemos recolher dados pessoais relacionados com a sua participação nos nossos eventos, bem como com outros pedidos que nos envie referentes aos nossos Serviços. Por exemplo, se se registar ou participar num evento que venhamos a organizar ou patrocinar, podemos recolher dados relacionados com o seu registo e participação nesse evento.
    
* **Preferências e outros pedidos** . Também podemos recolher dados sobre as suas preferências, incluindo as preferências de comunicação, preferências relacionadas com a sua utilização dos nossos Serviços e quaisquer outras preferências ou pedidos que você fizer ao interagir connosco.

De uma forma geral, não é obrigado a proporcionar-nos os seus dados pessoais. No entanto, a utilização de determinados Serviços ou aspetos dos nossos Serviços pode exigir a entrega de dados pessoais como, p. ex., o registo para uma conta Tagged. Se for este o caso, iremos indicar-lhe isto. Se não quiser proporcionar-nos os dados necessários , infelizmente não poderá utilizar o Serviço correspondente .

**Dados pessoais recolhidos de terceiros** . Também podemos recolher e receber certos dados pessoais sobre si de fontes terceiras, como de parceiros comerciais, especialmente quando utilizar fornecedores de loja de aplicações para as compras, outros utilizadores TMG, fornecedores de análise de dados e «marketing», sistemas operativos e plataformas de redes sociais , nomeadamente ao utilizar as funções de início de sessão descritas acima. Além disso, podemos recolher os seguintes dados de fontes terceiras :

* **Informações de registo em redes e plataformas sociais** . Enquanto estiver a usar os nossos Serviços, pode optar por partilhar informações ou conteúdos, entrar ou iniciar a sessão nos Serviços através de várias plataformas de redes sociais, serviços de redes sociais ou outras funcionalidades ou serviços integrados de terceiros. Quando fizer a ligação aos nossos Serviços usando as suas contas de redes sociais ou outros serviços e funções integradas semelhantes, podemos recolher ou receber os seus dados pessoais que tiver proporcionado àquela conta, serviço ou função de redes sociais . Por exemplo, podemos recolher dados a partir da sua conta e perfil, como o nome, «e-mail», ID de utilizador, fotografia de perfil, lista de amigos e outras informações semelhantes disponíveis no seu perfil. Deve consultar as suas definições de privacidade em cada plataforma, funcionalidade ou serviço de redes sociais integrados para compreender melhor como os seus dados pessoais podem ser utilizados, divulgados ou tratados de qualquer outra forma por estes terceiros.
    
* **Informações de recomendação** . Podemos oferecer-lhe a possibilidade de convidar amigos ou indicar outros utilizadores para aceder ou usar os nossos Serviços. Ao fazermos isto , podemos recolher e receber certos dados pessoais sobre si, incluindo de outros utilizadores atuais ou potenciais do TMG e clientes que participam de forma semelhante nestas atividades.

**Dados pessoais recolhidos automaticamente** . Nós e os nossos prestadores de serviços terceiros podem recolher ou encaminhar automaticamente dados pessoais sobre si relativos à sua utilização dos nossos Serviços, incluindo através do uso de «cookies», «pixel tags» e outras tecnologias semelhantes. Os dados pessoais que podemos recolher automaticamente incluem:

* **Informação do dispositivo e de navegação** . Quando utilizar os nossos Serviços, podemos recolher informação sobre o tipo de navegador, nome de domínio, visualizações de página, tempos de acesso, carimbos de data/hora, sistema operativo, idioma, tipo de dispositivo, ID único , prestador de serviços de Internet, URL de referência e saída, dados de fluxo de cliques, sistema operativo, idioma e informação do dispositivo e de navegação semelhante.
    
* **Atividades e utilização** . Também podemos recolher dados sobre a atividade relacionada com a sua utilização dos Serviços, como informações sobre hiperligações clicadas, pesquisas, funcionalidades utilizadas, itens visualizados, tempo gasto nos Serviços, as suas interações connosco e terceiros nos Serviços e outras informações semelhantes de atividade e utilização.
    
* **Informação de localização** . Também podemos recolher ou obter informação de localização geral sobre si, como através do seu endereço IP.

Para mais informação sobre a nossa utilização de «cookies» e outras tecnologias semelhantes , consulte a Secção 6. «Cookies», direcionamento e análise abaixo.

**3\. Finalidades da recolha e tratamento**

De uma forma geral, podemos recolher, usar, divulgar e tratar as categorias de dados pessoais que recolhemos para as seguintes finalidades:

* **Serviços e assistência** . De forma a prestar e explorar os nossos Serviços (p. ex., funções do jogo Tagged ou Pets), gerir a sua conta, comunicar consigo sobre a utilização dos Serviços, proporcionar a resolução de problemas, assistência técnica ou para efeitos de assistência semelhantes e para responder às suas perguntas, satisfazer os seus pedidos, processar pagamentos e, sob qualquer outra forma, executar as nossas operações quotidianas. Quando você criar um perfil num dos nossos Serviços, alguns dos seus dados pessoais como nome de utilizador, nome, idade, sexo e orientação sexual ,de acordo com as suas definições de privacidade, podem ser igualmente visualizáveis para os utilizadores do respetivo Serviço e dos nossos outros Serviços e outras aplicações que possuímos e outras aplicações e «sites» que não nos pertençam com os quais partilhemos a nossa plataforma em direto. O TMG fundamenta-se na base jurídica " execução de um contrato " (Art.º 6.º (1) (b) do RGPD e do RGPD do Reino Unido e art.º 31.º (2) (b) do nDSG). Na medida em que tratamos os seus dados pessoais para os tornar visíveis aos utilizadores dos nossos restantes Serviços e outras aplicações que possuímos e outras aplicações e «sites» que não nos pertençam com os quais partilhemos a nossa plataforma ao vivo, o TMG fundamenta-se na base jurídica "execução de um contrato " (Art.º 6.º (1) (b) do RGPD e do RGPD do Reino Unido e art.º 31.º (2) (b) do nDSG).

Quanto aos dados de localização, o TMG baseia-se no seu consentimento (Art.º 6.º (1) (a), Art.º 7.º do RGPD).

No que diz respeito à orientação sexual, o TMG fundamenta-se no seu consentimento explícito (art.º 6.º (1) (a), art.º 7.º, art.º 9.º (2) (a) do RGPD/RGPD do Reino Unido) ou na exceção no art.º 9.º (2) (e) do RGPD/RGPD do Reino Unido, desde que você tenha revelado publicamente a sua orientação sexual (p. ex., numa transmissão em direto).

* **Análise e melhoria** . Para compreender melhor como os utilizadores acedem e usam os Serviços e noutras finalidades de estudo e análise , tais como avaliar e melhorar o «Site», os nossos Serviços, e operações comerciais, nomeadamente para desenvolver os nossos Serviços e funções e em finalidades de controlo da qualidade interna e formação. O TMG fundamenta-se na base jurídica " interesses legítimos" (art.º 6.º (1) (f) RGPD/RGPD do Reino Unido e art.º 31.º (1) do nDSG). A este respeito, o TMG persegue o seu interesse de compreender o desempenho do serviço sob uma perspetiva de negócio.

**Comunicação** . Para responder às suas perguntas, enviar-lhe os materiais pedidos , bem como informações e materiais relativos aos nossos Serviços e ofertas. Também podemos usar esta informação para lhe enviar informações administrativas , por exemplo, informações sobre os Serviços e as alterações das nossas condições e políticas. O TMG fundamenta-se na base jurídica " execução de um contrato " (art.º 6.º (1) (b) RGPD/RGPD do Reino Unido e art.º 31.º (2) (a) do nDSG) ou - quando não existir contrato entre o utilizador relevante e os "interesses legítimos" do TMG (art.º 6.º (1) (f) RGPD/RGPD do Reino Unido e art.º 31.º (1) do nDSG). Quando se basear nos "interesses legítimos", o TMG considera os seus interesses de proporcionar assistência, bem como de dar resposta a pedidos para garantir a satisfação do utilizador.

* **Costumização e personalização** . Para personalizar o conteúdo que podemos enviar ou visualizar nos Serviços, nomeadamente para proporcionar a costumização da localização e para, de qualquer outra forma, personalizar as suas experiências e ofertas. O TMG fundamenta-se na base jurídica " execução de um contrato" (art.º 6.º (1) (b) do RGPD e do RGPD do Reino Unido e art.º 31.º (2) (b) nDSG.
    
* Comunicação por redes sociais e outras plataformas. Para lhe permitir partilhar informações ou conteúdos, entrar ou iniciar a sessão nos Serviços através de várias plataformas de redes sociais, serviços de redes sociais ou outras funcionalidades de terceiros ou serviços integrados. Para lhe permitir entrar ou iniciar a sessão nos Serviços, o TMG fundamenta-se a base jurídica "execução de um contrato" (art.º 6.º (1) (b) do RGPD e RGPD do Reino Unido e art.º 31.º (2) (b) do nDSG). Caso contrário, o TMG fundamenta-se na base jurídica "interesses legítimos" (art.º 6.º (1) (f) RGPD/RGPD do Reino Unido e art.º 31.º (1) do nDSG). A este respeito, o TMG considera o seu interesse em permitir que os utilizadores iniciem determinadas comunicações com plataformas de redes sociais, serviços de redes sociais ou outras funções ou serviços integrados de terceiros, caso pretendam.
    
* **«Marketing» e publicidade** . Para efeitos de «marketing», publicidade e promocionais. Por exemplo, para lhe enviar informação promocional sobre os nossos Serviços, incluindo «newsletters», informações sobre eventos TMG, «webinars», apresentações, vendas, promoções, descontos, e novas ofertas, bem como qualquer outra informação que você subscreva para receber. O TMG fundamenta-se na base jurídica "consentimento" do art.º 6.º (1) (a), art.º 7.º do RGPD e RGPD do Reino Unido e art.º 31.º (1) do nDSG.

Para efeitos de auto-publicidade/«marketing» direto através «e-mails» promocionais e/ou mensagens «push», pesquisas (utilizadores) e guias individualizados (exclusivamente produtos TMG). (A base jurídica é o interesse legítimo do TMG no «marketing» direto dos seus próprios produtos, como bem como a secção 7 (3) da Lei Alemã contra a Concorrência Desleal (UWG).

* **Estudo e inquéritos** . Para gerir inquéritos e questionários, como para pesquisa de mercado, satisfação do utilizador ou outras finalidades semelhantes. O TMG fundamenta-se na base jurídica "consentimento" do art.º 6.º (1) (a), art.º 7.º do RGPD e RGPD do Reino Unido e art.º 31.º (1) do nDSG.
    
* **Desenvolvimento do conhecimento e melhoria de dados** . Podemos combinar dados pessoais recolhidos através dos Serviços com outras informações recolhidas por nós ou terceiros sobre si noutros contextos. Na maioria dos casos, a informação com a qual podemos combinar os dados pessoais recolhidos através dos Serviços para a pesquisa de mercado , tal como a informação demográfica, não identifica diretamente os consumidores. O TMG fundamenta-se na base jurídica " interesses legítimos" (art.º 6.º (1) (f) RGPD/RGPD do Reino Unido e art.º 31.º (1) do nDSG). A este respeito, o TMG considera o seu interesse em compreender o desempenho do serviço sob uma perspetiva empresarial.
    
* **Acesso e armazenamento de informações no dispositivo final do utilizador.** Podemos aceder ou armazenar informações no seu dispositivo final. O TMG fundamenta-se na base jurídica do "consentimento" do art.º 5.º (3) Diretiva de e-Privacidade e PECR Reg. 6.º (4) quando isto não for estritamente necessário para o funcionamento do nosso «site», bem como para a prestação de serviços de telemedia expressamente solicitados pelo utilizador.
    
* **Planeamento e gestão de eventos** . Para o planeamento de eventos e outras finalidades relacionadas com a gestão, como o registo e a comparência em eventos , fazer a sua conexão a outros participantes do evento e utilizadores do TMG e entrar em contacto consigo sobre eventos relevantes, apresentações e os nossos Serviços. Também podemos utilizar dados pessoais para proporcionar eventos especiais, sorteios, concursos e promoções, que podem ter as suas próprias regras específicas de participação. O TMG fundamenta-se na base jurídica "consentimento" do art.º 6.º (1) (a), art.º 7.º do RGPD e RGPD do Reino Unido e art.º 31.º (1) do nDSG.
    
* **Segurança e salvaguarda dos direitos** . Para proteger os Serviços e as nossas operações comerciais, os nossos direitos e os dos nossos acionistas e investidores, para prevenir e detetar fraudes, atividades e acesso não autorizadas e outra utilização indevida do nosso «Site», nomeadamente quando considerarmos necessário investigar, prevenir ou tomar medidas relativamente a atividades ilegais, suspeita de fraude, situações que envolvam ameaças potenciais para a segurança ou os direitos legais de qualquer pessoa ou terceiros ou violações das nossas Condições. O TMG fundamenta-se na base jurídica "interesses legítimos" (art.º 6.º(1) (f) do RGPD/RGPD do Reino Unido e do art.º 31.º (1) do nDSG. O interesse legítimo do TMG e dos utilizadores do TMG em que o serviço TMG não seja utilizado indevidamente para atos contratuais e/ou ilegais de terceiros. O nosso interesse legítimo é igualmente a proteção dos nossos próprios sistemas de salvaguarda da TI do TMG e, portanto, em última análise, a proteção de dados pessoais dos utilizadores do TMG. No que diz respeito à orientação sexual, o TMG fundamenta-se adicionalmente da base jurídica para a instauração, exercício ou defesa de processos judiciais (art.º 9.º (2) (f) do RGPD/RGPD do Reino Unido).
    
* **Conformidade e procedimento legal** . Para cumprir a lei ou as obrigações regulamentares aplicáveis, incluindo as obrigações legais de retenção ou como parte de um processo judicial, para responder a uma intimação, mandado, ordem judicial ou outro procedimento legal, ou como parte de uma investigação ou requerimento, seja formal ou informal, de uma autoridade de aplicação da lei ou governamental. O TMG fundamenta-se na base jurídica de (i) " cumprimento de obrigações legais" (art.º 6.º (1) (c) do RGPD/RGPD do Reino Unido bem como o art.º 31.º (2) (a) do NdSG) se esta obrigação emanar da legislação da UE ou dos Estados-Membros da UE, ou (ii) no "interesse legítimo" (art.º 6.º (1) (f) do RGPD/RGPD do Reino Unido, bem como do art.º 31.º (1) do NdsG) se esta obrigação emanar de outras jurisdições. Se os interesses legítimos forem relevantes, o TMG considera os seus interesses no cumprimento das obrigações legais às quais esteja sujeito. No que diz respeito à orientação sexual, o TMG fundamenta-se adicionalmente na base jurídica para a instauração, exercício ou defesa de processos judiciais (art.º 9.º (2) (f) do RGPD/RGPD do Reino Unido).
    
* **Auditoria, relatórios e outras operações internas** . Para levar a cabo auditorias financeiras, fiscais e contabilísticas, auditorias e avaliações das nossas operações, nomeadamente da privacidade, segurança e controlos financeiros, bem como para efeitos de risco e conformidade. Também podemos usar os dados pessoais para manter registos comerciais apropriados e implementar as nossas políticas e procedimentos. O TMG fundamenta-se na base jurídica "interesses legítimos" (art.º 6.º(1) (f) do RGPD/RGPD do Reino Unido e do art.º 31.º (1) do nDSG. O interesse legítimo do TMG é proteger as operações comerciais e verificar regularmente se as obrigações de relato e conformidade são cumpridas.
    
* **Assistência geral comercial e operacional** . Para avaliar e implementar fusões, aquisições, reorganizações, falências e outras transações comerciais, como financiamentos, e para administrar a empresa e levar a cabo a contabilidade, auditoria, conformidade, manutenção de registos e as funções legais. O TMG fundamenta-se na base jurídica do "interesse legítimo " (art.º 6.º (1) (f) de DSGVO e art.º 31.º (1) do nDSG). Neste contexto, o TMG tem um interesse em divulgar e tratar informações sobre os seus ativos e atividades para compradores ou adquirentes potenciais e aos seus consultores externos, para facilitar a venda desses ativos e/ou atividades.

As finalidades que perseguimos relativamente ao uso de «cookies» e tecnologias semelhantes, particularmente no que diz respeito ao direcionamento e análise estão descritas na Secção 6. «Cookies», direcionamento e análise.

Quando a base jurídica para o tratamento for o seu consentimento, usufrui do direito de o retirar em qualquer momento. No entanto, esta retirada não afeta a legalidade de qualquer tratamento realizado com base no seu consentimento antes da referida retirada. Se a base legal for o interesse legítimo , você também usufrui do direito, de uma forma geral, de se opor ao tratamento dos dados pessoais, em qualquer momento, por razões decorrentes da sua situação específica. Além disso, você usufrui do direito de se opor em qualquer momento ao tratamento dos seus dados pessoais para efeitos de «marketing» direto. O artigo 21.º do RGPD / RGPD do Reino Unido aplica-se a este respeito.

Pode opor-se à nossa utilização do seu endereço de «e-mail» para fins promocionais ou orientação pessoal, no ato do registo ou posteriormente em qualquer momento.

**4\. Divulgação de dados pessoais**

Podemos divulgar os dados pessoais que recolhemos para as finalidades descritas acima, para lhe prestar os nossos Serviços, para responder e satisfazer os seus pedidos, conforme indicado ou, de outra forma, consentido por si e com os seguintes destinatários:

* **Marcas, filiais e subsidiárias** . Podemos divulgar os dados pessoais que recolhemos através das nossas marcas, filiais e subsidiárias.
    
* **Parceiros comerciais** . Nalgumas circunstâncias, o TMG pode estabelecer parcerias com outras empresas para prestar os seus Serviços, incluindo para proporcionar certos programas ou ofertas especiais, e pode divulgar dados pessoais a esses parceiros comerciais.
    
* **Fornecedores e prestadores de serviços** . Podemos divulgar dados pessoais que recolhemos aos fornecedores e prestadores de serviços que desempenham funções no nosso nome, como alojamento de TI e do «site», processamento de pagamentos , fornecedores de estudos de «marketing» e «marketing», assistência ao cliente , armazenamento de dados, fornecedores de análise de dados, auditores, consultores, assessores e agentes e consultores jurídicos.
    
* **Outros utilizadores TMG** . Com outros utilizadores dos Serviços no contexto de funções específicas que sejam de natureza social. Por exemplo, se convidar outras pessoas para utilizar os nossos Serviços ou se enviar ou disponibilizar informação através do nosso público, funcionalidades interativas , fóruns da comunidade ou blogues de discussão, incluindo quando você publicar avaliações ou depoimentos, determinados dados pessoais, podem estar disponíveis e ser pesquisáveis por outros utilizadores dos Serviços. Por exemplo, se participar em Pets, outros utilizadores da funcionalidade do jogo Pets poderão visualizar dados pessoais como a sua fotografia de perfil, sexo, valor, dinheiro, ativos detidos e número de Pets.
    
* **Fornecedores de marketing e análise de terceiros** . Também podemos divulgar os seus dados pessoais, como o dispositivo e navegação, e atividades e informações de utilização, a prestadores de marketing e análise de dados de fornecedores terceiros e a outras empresas que prestam serviços de marketing, publicidade, gestão de campanhas ou de análise em nosso nome. Para um resumo detalhado dos destinatários específicos, consulte a nossa plataforma de gestão de consentimento na aplicação.

Também podemos divulgar os seus dados pessoais nas seguintes circunstâncias:

* **Para apoiar as transferências empresariais** . Se o TMG ou as suas filiais forem ou puderem ser adquiridos, fundidos ou receber investimento de outra empresa ou se algum dos seus ativos for ou puder ser transferido para outra empresa, seja como parte de um processo de falência ou insolvência ou por qualquer outro motivo, podemos divulgar ou transferir os dados pessoais que tenham sido recolhidos de si com ou para a outra empresa de acordo com a legislação aplicável. Também podemos divulgar determinados dados pessoais conforme necessário antes da conclusão da referida transação ou outra transação empresarial, como um financiamento ou reestruturação, a credores, auditores e consultores de terceiros, incluindo advogados e consultores.
    
* **Conformidade e obrigações legais** . Também podemos divulgar dados pessoais a terceiros na medida exigida pela lei aplicável e pelas obrigações legais. Por exemplo, podemos divulgar dados em resposta a intimações, ordens judiciais e outros requerimentos legítimos de reguladores, entidades governamentais e autoridades policiais, incluindo a resposta a requisitos de divulgação por segurança nacional ou de aplicação da lei , ou conforme exigido pela lei ou por um processo legal. Para além disso, e se for aplicável, podemos divulgar os nomes de vencedores de sorteios e concursos de acordo com a lei aplicável.
    
* **Segurança e salvaguarda dos direitos** . Quando considerarmos que isto é necessário para salvaguardar os Serviços, os nossos direitos e propriedade ou os direitos, propriedade e segurança de terceiros. Por exemplo, podemos divulgar dados pessoais para (i) prevenir, detetar, investigar e responder a fraudes, atividades e acesso não autorizados, atividades ilegais e uso indevido dos Serviços, (ii) situações que envolvem potenciais ameaças para a saúde, segurança ou direitos legais de qualquer pessoa ou terceiro, ou (iii) impor, detetar, investigar e tomar medidas em resposta a violações das nossas Condições. Também podemos divulgar dados pessoais relacionados com litígios e outras ações legais ou processos nos quais estejamos envolvidos, também relacionados com a nossa contabilidade interna, auditoria, conformidade, manutenção de registos e funções legais.
    
* **Outras divulgações** . Podemos divulgar dados pessoais sob outras formas não descritas anteriormente que lhe tenhamos notificado ou para as quais tenhamos obtido o seu consentimento ou que, de outro modo, sejam autorizadas ou requeridas por lei.

Independentemente do descrito nesta Política, podemos usar e divulgar dados agregados, não identificados e outros dados não identificáveis relacionados com o nosso negócio e os Serviços de controlo de qualidade, análises, investigação, desenvolvimento e outras finalidades. Quando usarmos, divulgarmos ou tratarmos dados não identificados (dados que já não podem ser razoavelmente associados ou vinculados a uma pessoa singular, agregado familiar ou dispositivo pessoal ou doméstico identificados ou identificáveis), iremos conservar e utilizar a informação de forma não identificada e não para tentar voltar a identificar os dados, exceto para determinar se os nossos processos de não identificação são razoáveis e adequados de acordo com as leis de privacidade aplicáveis.

**5\. Transferências de dados pessoais para países localizados fora do EEE/UK/CH**

Os destinatários dos dados pessoais podem estar localizados fora do EEE/Reino Unido/Suíça. Quando os dados pessoais forem transferidos para locais fora do EEE/Reino Unido/Suíça (o que inclui as nossas transferências nos EUA como responsável pelo tratamento no âmbito do RGPD/RGPD do Reino Unido/nDSG para destinatários nos EUA ou noutros países fora do EEA/Reino Unido/Suíça, que não estejam no âmbito do RGPD/RGPD do Reino Unido/nDSG), iremos, conforme exigido por lei, garantir que os seus direitos de privacidade são também protegidos adequadamente por a Comissão Europeia ter determinado que o país para o qual os dados pessoais são transferidos assegura um nível adequado de proteção (art.º 45.º RGPD /RGPD do Reino Unido) ou que a transferência está sujeita a salvaguardas apropriadas (p. ex., cláusulas-tipo de proteção de dados da União Europeia acordadas com o destinatário) (art.º 46.º do RGPD / RGPD do Reino Unido ) exceto se o RGPD / RGPD do Reino Unido prever uma exceção (art.º 49.º RGPD / RGPD do Reino Unido ). Além disso, pretendemos, quando for necessário, chegar a um acordo sobre as medidas adicionais com os destinatários para garantir um nível adequado de proteção dos dados . Consulte também art.º 16.º f. do nDSG relativamente à divulgação de dados pessoais fora da Suíça.

Se for necessário, também realizamos uma "Adenda UK" com os nossos parceiros contratuais de acordo com os requisitos do Gabinete do Comissário de Informação (ICO) e uma "Adenda CH"correspondente de acordo com os requisitos do Comissário Federal Suíço de Informação e Proteção de Dados (FDPIC).

As cópias das medidas de salvaguarda apropriadas (desde que sejam utilizadas por nós) e uma lista dos destinatários localizados fora do EEE/Reino Unido/Suíça podem ser solicitadas em [support@themeetgroup.com](mailto:support@themeetgroup.com). Tenha em conta que esta cópia pode ser editada conforme necessário para proteger segredos comerciais ou outra informação confidencial.

**6\. «Cookies», direcionamento e análise**

Nós e os nossos prestadores de serviços terceiros utilizam «cookies», pixeis, objetos de armazenamento local, ficheiros de registo e outros mecanismos de seguimento para recolher automaticamente informação sobre a navegação, a atividade, o dispositivo e outros dados semelhante no âmbito dos nossos Serviços. Utilizamos esta informação para analisar e compreender a forma como os utilizadores realizam o acesso, a utilização e a interação com os nossos Serviços, de modo a identificar e resolver problemas e erros nos mesmos, avaliar a segurança, proteger, otimizar e melhorar o desempenho dos nossos Serviços, bem como para efeitos de «marketing» e análise, e de personalização do conteúdo nos ditos Serviços. Dependendo da sua localização, a maior parte destas ações unicamente terá lugar se você tiver dado o seu consentimento através da nossa CMP, disponível nas definições da aplicação, para gerir o consentimento/preferências sobre «cookies», publicidade direcionada e outros mecanismos de seguimento semelhantes no âmbito dos nossos Serviços; consulte a Secção 7. As suas escolhas de privacidade abaixo. Muitas destas escolhas são específicas do navegador e do dispositivo , o que significa que pode ter de definir a preferência para cada navegador e dispositivo que utilizar para aceder aos nossos Serviços. Além disso, se apagar ou bloquear «cookies», pode ter de voltar a aplicar estas preferências em cada navegador e/ou dispositivo.

**«Cookies»** . Os «cookies» são pequenos ficheiros de texto armazenados no dispositivo de um utilizador (como um computador ou «smartphone») por um «site» que este visita. Os «cookies» são criados pelo servidor do «site» e enviados ao navegador do utilizador, onde são armazenados para referência futura. Alguns« cookies» permitem-nos simplificar a navegação pelos nossos Serviços, enquanto outros são usados, por exemplo, para permitir um processo de início de sessão mais rápido, apoiar a segurança e o desempenho dos Serviços ou permitir-nos seguir informação de agregados e estatística sobre a atividade do utilizador nos Serviços.

**«Pixel Tags»** . As «pixel tags» (por vezes designadas como «web beacons» ou GIF transparentes) são pequenos gráficos com um identificador único, com uma função semelhante aos «cookies». Enquanto os «cookies» são armazenados localmente no seu dispositivo, as «pixel tags» são incorporados de forma invisível nas páginas Web e no conteúdo «online». Podemos utilizá-las, em conjunto com os nossos Serviços para, entre outras coisas, monitorizar as atividades dos utilizadores e nos ajudar a gerir o conteúdo e compilar as estatísticas de utilização. Também podemos utilizá-las nos nossos «e-mails» para saber quando foram abertos ou reencaminhados, para que possamos monitorizar as taxas de resposta e avaliar a eficácia das nossas comunicações.

**Ficheiros de registo** . Podemos recolher determinadas informações sobre a atividade a partir dos ficheiros de registo. As informações do ficheiro de registo são recolhidas automaticamente quando acede aos nossos «Sites». Gravamos determinadas informações destes ficheiros de registo, incluindo informação sobre os pedidos Web, endereço IP, tipo e versão do navegador, idioma, URL de referência e saída, «links» clicados, páginas visualizadas e outra informação semelhante.

**Análises de terceiros** . Podemos usar dispositivos automatizados, aplicações e ferramentas, como o Google Analytics, que são explorados por empresas terceiras, para avaliar a utilização dos nossos Serviços. Estas empresas terceiras podem utilizar «cookies», pixeis e outras tecnologias de seguimento para recolher dados de utilização dos nossos Serviços e proporcionar-nos relatórios e métricas que nos ajudam a avaliar o uso dos nossos Serviços e a melhorar o desempenho e a experiência do utilizador. Para saber mais sobre as práticas de privacidade da Google, consulte a respetiva Política de Privacidade em [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). Também pode descarregar o complemento de desativação do navegador da Google Analytics para impedir que os seus dados sejam utilizados pela Google Analytics em [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). Pode encontrar uma lista de terceiros contratados por nós para estas finalidades no nosso CMP disponibilizado nas definições da sua aplicação.

**Publicidade de terceiros** . Trabalhamos com redes de anúncios de terceiros, parceiros de «marketing», redes de anúncios móveis e outros ("empresas terceiras de anúncios") para personalizar o conteúdo e apresentar publicidade no âmbito dos nossos Serviços, bem como para gerir a nossa publicidade em «sites» de terceiros. Nós e estas empresas de publicidade terceiras podemos usar «cookies», «pixel tags», SDK («kits» de desenvolvimento de «software») e outras ferramentas para recolher informações de atividade e navegação nos nossos Serviços (bem como sobre «sites» e serviços de terceiros), bem como o endereço IP, ID exclusivo, ID de «cookie» e de publicidade e outros identificadores «online». Nós e as empresas de publicidade terceiras utilizamos esta informação para lhe proporcionar anúncios e conteúdo mais relevantes no âmbito dos nossos Serviços e em «sites» de terceiros e para avaliar os bons resultados destes anúncios e conteúdos. Pode encontrar uma lista das empresas de publicidade terceiras no nosso CMP disponível nas definições da sua aplicação.

**Utilização entre dispositivos** . Nós e os nossos prestadores de serviços terceiros podemos usar a informação recolhida sobre si (seja diretamente a partir dos nossos «Sites» ou da Aplicação móvel, através do(s) seu(s) dispositivo(s), ou de fontes de terceiros) para identificar outros dispositivos que utilizas (p. ex., um telemóvel, «tablet», outro computador, etc.). Nós e os nossos prestadores de serviços terceiros também podem aproveitar as informações sobre o uso entre dispositivos e outras recolhidas sobre si para transmitir publicidade direcionada ou personalizar o conteúdo no âmbito dos nossos Serviços.

**Listas personalizadas e correspondência** . Podemos partilhar ou disponibilizar determinadas informações da lista de clientes (como o nome, endereço de «e-mail» e outras informações de contacto) com terceiros para podermos direcionar melhor a publicidade e o conteúdo para si em «sites», plataformas e serviços de terceiros. Nalguns casos, estes terceiros podem ajudar-nos a melhorar as nossas listas de clientes com informações demográficas adicionais ou outras informações semelhantes para que possamos direcionar melhor as nossas campanhas de publicidade e «marketing».

**7\. As suas escolhas de privacidade**

**Gerir as suas preferências** . Disponibilizamos várias maneiras para que você possa gerir as suas preferências e escolhas de privacidade, conforme descrito abaixo:

* **Dados sobre a conta e o perfil** . Pode rever e atualizar alguns dos dados pessoais que conservamos sobre si, iniciando a sessão na sua conta e atualizando as informações da conta e do perfil.
    
* **Comunicações de «marketing»** . Podemos enviar-lhe «e-mails», conteúdo ou outras comunicações semelhantes promocionais periódicas. Pode optar por não receber estas comunicações se seguir as instruções que lhe proporcionamos na comunicação. Se decidir não receber o nosso conteúdo promocional, podemos ainda enviar-lhe comunicações sobre a sua conta ou quaisquer serviços que tenha solicitado ou recebido de nós. Além disso, pode gerir as suas preferências de comunicação nas definições da sua conta e perfil.
    
* **Notificações «push»** . Pode gerir o tipo de notificações «push» que lhe enviamos ajustando as definições do seu dispositivo móvel ou modificando-as na aplicação móvel. São mensagens que enviamos no decurso do cumprimento do contrato, bem como informações promocionais.

**Preferências de «cookies» e seguimento/publicidade direcionada/análise** . Também disponibilizamos várias formas para gerir as suas preferências de «cookies», publicidade direcionada, análises e outros mecanismos semelhantes de monitorização nos nossos Serviços. Muitas destas opções são específicas do navegador e do dispositivo , o que significa que pode ter de definir a preferência para cada navegador e dispositivo que utilizar para aceder aos nossos Serviços. Além disso, se apagar ou bloquear os «cookies», pode ter de voltar a aplicar estas preferências em cada navegador e/ou dispositivo. Por outro lado, desativar os «cookies» e a publicidade não significa que vai deixar de receber o nosso conteúdo publicitário, pelo que pode continuar a receber o nosso conteúdo de publicidade genérica ou "contextual".

* **Plataforma de Gestão do Consentimento (CMP).** Para impedir os «cookies» ou outros mecanismos de seguimento que não sejam estritamente necessários para a monitorização da sua atividade nos nossos «Sites» ou na nossa Aplicação móvel, pode usar a plataforma de gestão do consentimento disponibilizada antes de os «cookies» e os mecanismos de seguimento serem utilizados. Depois de o consentimento ter sido dado, pode ser retirado em qualquer momento com efeitos para o futuro. Para obter informação mais detalhada consulte a Secção 15. Privacidade adicional Informação para certas jurisdições, que inclui mais informações sobre os direitos de privacidade para os residentes em determinadas jurisdições.
    
* **Definições de «cookies»** . Para impedir que os «cookies» monitorizem a sua atividade nos nossos «Sites» ou nas visitas em vários «sites», pode definir o seu navegador para bloquear determinados «cookies» ou receber uma notificação quando um «cookie» for definido. Também pode apagar os «cookies». A parte "Ajuda" da barra de ferramentas ativada na maioria dos navegadores irá dizer-lhe como impedir que o seu dispositivo aceite novos «cookies», como fazer para receber uma notificação do navegador quando receber um novo «cookie» ou como apagar os «cookies». Os visitantes dos nossos «Sites» que desativem os «cookies» podem navegar pelos mesmos, mas algumas funcionalidades podem não estar operacionais.
    
* **Sinais do navegador** . Conforme exigido pela lei aplicável, se os nossos «Sites» detetarem que o seu navegador está a transmitir um sinal de preferência de desativação, como um sinal de "controlo de privacidade global" (ou GPC), , iremos aplicar este sinal para ativar esse navegador específico no seu dispositivo sem «cookies» de segmentação nos nossos «Sites». Se aceder aos nossos «Sites» a partir de um dispositivo diferente ou de um navegador diferente no mesmo dispositivo, também irá precisar de aplicar o GPC para esse navegador e/ou dispositivo.
    
* **Programas de escolha de anúncios da indústria** . Também pode controlar como empresas de publicidade terceiras participantes usam a informação que recolhem sobre as suas visitas aos nossos «Sites» e aos de terceiros para lhe mostrar publicidade direcionada mais relevante. Para mais informações e assistência relacionadas com os mecanismos de seguimento na Internet, visite [www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/).

Os residentes em certas jurisdições podem ter direitos adicionais sobre os seus dados pessoais, conforme previsto abaixo na Secção 15. Informações de privacidade adicionais para determinadas jurisdições

**8\. Período de conservação dos dados pessoais**

Conservamos os seus dados pessoais pelo tempo necessário para realizar as finalidades mencionadas na Secção 3 Finalidades de recolha e tratamento e na Secção 6 «Cookies», direcionamento e análise ou enquanto tivermos um interesse legítimo na conservação continuada. Em todos os outros casos, apagamos os seus dados pessoais com exceção das informações que devemos continuar a conservar para cumprir os períodos de retenção legais (p. ex., emanantes do direito fiscal ou comercial, como no referente a faturas). Restringimos o tratamento de dados pessoais que apenas são conservados devido a uma obrigação de retenção.

A informação sobre a duração da armazenamento de «cookies» e de outros mecanismos de seguimento está disponível na nossa CMP que pode encontrar nas definições da sua aplicação.

**9\. Hiperligações e funcionalidades externas**

Os nossos Serviços podem conter hiperligações para «sites» ou funcionalidades de terceiros ou proporcionar determinadas ligações de terceiros ou serviços integrados. Qualquer acesso e utilização desses «sites» ou funcionalidades ligados não se rege por esta Política, mas antes pelas políticas de privacidade de terceiros. Não somos responsáveis pelas práticas de informação destes terceiros, incluindo pela sua recolha, utilização e divulgação dos dados pessoais. Deve consultar as políticas de privacidade e as condições para quaisquer terceiros antes de visitar estes «sites» ou usar estas funcionalidades.

**10\. Conteúdo produzido pelo utilizador**

Podemos oferecer funcionalidades interativas orientadas para o público, fóruns da comunidade ou blogues de discussão relacionados com os nossos Serviços que lhe permitem partilhar informações sobre os Serviços ou outras questões de interesse (p. ex. comentários, depoimentos e perguntas). Deve estar ciente de que quaisquer comunicações que envia ou publica em quaisquer destas funcionalidades interativas nos Serviços podem ser visualizados e pesquisáveis por terceiros, incluindo os utilizadores do TMG e o público. Ao submeter ou publicar nessas funcionalidades interativas orientadas para o público, reconhece que não tem qualquer expetativa de privacidade ou confidencialidade no conteúdo que envia para tais funcionalidades, contenham ou não dados pessoais sobre si.

**11\. Segurança**

Implementámos precauções razoáveis para proteger os dados recolhidos de perda, utilização e acesso indevido, divulgação, alteração e destruição não autorizada. Deve estar ciente de que, apesar dos nossos melhores esforços, não existem medidas que garantam uma segurança total dos dados.

**12\. Privacidade das crianças**

Os nossos Serviços não foram concebidos para crianças e não recolhemos de forma consciente dados pessoais de crianças com menos de 18 anos(18). Se tivermos conhecimento de que foram recolhidos dados pessoais nos Serviços de pessoas com menos de 18 anos, tomaremos então as medidas apropriadas para eliminar estes dados. Se você for o progenitor ou tutor legal e considerar que recolhemos os dados do seu filho em infração da lei aplicável, deve contactar-nos através da informação de contacto abaixo.

**13\. Alterações a esta Política**

Esta Política está em vigor a partir da data indicada acima. Podemos alterar, atualizar ou modificar esta Política ocasionalmente, pelo que deve verificá-la de forma periódica. Quaisquer atualizações a esta Política serão publicadas aqui. Se realizarmos qualquer alteração nesta Política que afete materialmente as nossas práticas de utilização dos dados pessoais recolhidos anteriormente de si, faremos o possível para lhe dar conhecimento, mediante o envio de um «e-mail» ou a publicação de um aviso em destaque nos nossos «Sites», na nossa Aplicação móvel ou nos Serviços.

**14\. Contacto**

Se tiver alguma dúvida ou preocupação relativamente a esta Política ou às nossas práticas de privacidade, pode enviar-nos um «e-mail» [através de support@themeetgroup.com](mailto:support@themeetgroup.com) ou contactar-nos em:

The Meet Group, Inc.

100 Union Square Drive

New Hope, PA 18938

Pode contactar o nosso responsável pela proteção de dados em:

ePrivacy GmbH representada pelo Prof. Dr. Christoph Bauer, Große Bleichen [21, 20354 Hamburgo, privacy@themeetgroup.com](mailto:privacy@themeetgroup.com)

Em todos os pedidos relativos à segurança dos seus dados, deve contactar o nosso responsável pela proteção dos dados através de [privacy@themeetgroup.com](mailto:privacy@themeetgroup.com).

O nosso Representante da UE nos termos do art.º 27 do RGPD pode ser contactado através de: ParshipMeet Holding GmbH, Speersort 10, 20095 Hamburgo, e-mail: [privacy@parshipmeet.com](mailto:privacy@parshipmeet.com)

Os detalhes do nosso Representante no Reino Unido de acordo com o art.º 27.º do RGPD do Reino Unido estão definidos na Secção 15.B. Informação adicional para Residentes do Reino Unido

Os detalhes do nosso representante suíço nos termos do art.º 14.º do nDSG (nova lei suíça de proteção de dados) estão definidos na Secção 15.C. Informações adicionais para residentes na Suíça.

Treforma AG c/o MLL Legal; Grabenstrasse 25; 6340 Baar; Suíça; [meetgroup@dsg-mll.com](mailto:meetgroup@dsg-mll.com)

**15\. Informações de privacidade adicionais para determinadas jurisdições**

Os residentes em determinadas jurisdições têm direitos adicionais ao abrigo das leis de privacidade aplicáveis, conforme descrito nesta secção.

**A. RGPD**

Se residir na União Europeia, usufrui dos seguintes direitos ao abrigo do RGPD desde que os requisitos legais no mesmo sejam satisfeitos:

**Direito de acesso** - Pode solicitar informação sobre o tratamento dos seus dados pessoais e uma cópia dos dados pessoais em tratamento na medida em que a referida cópia não afete negativamente os direitos e as liberdades de terceiros, sem que qualquer outra exceção se aplique.

**Direito de retificação** - Pode solicitar a correção dos seus dados pessoais que sejam imprecisos e/ou a completude dos dados que estejam incompletos.

**Direito de apagamento** - Pode pedir a eliminação dos seus dados pessoais, em particular

* quando os dados pessoais já não forem necessários para as finalidades para as quais foram recolhidos ou tratados de outra forma,
    
* tiver retirado o seu consentimento pelo qual o tratamento se regia e não houver outra base jurídica para o tratamento,
    
* se tiver oposto ao tratamento que se rege pela base jurídica dos "interesses legítimos" e não existirem fundamentos legítimos que se sobreponham ao tratamento ou se tiver oposto ao tratamento para efeitos de «marketing» direto,
    
* os seus dados pessoais tiverem sido tratados ilegalmente ou
    
* os seus dados pessoais tiverem de ser apagados para o cumprimento de uma obrigação legal a que estejamos sujeitos.

No entanto, o direito de apagamento não se aplica, em particular, quando o tratamento dos seus dados pessoais for necessário para o cumprimento de uma obrigação legal ou para a instauração, exercício ou defesa de ações legais.

**Direito de limitação do tratamento** - Pode solicitar a limitação do tratamento

* no período durante o qual verificamos a exatidão dos seus dados pessoais se tiver contestado a exatidão dos mesmos,
    
* quando o tratamento for ilegal e solicitar a limitação do tratamento em vez do apagamento os dados,
    
* quando já não precisarmos dos dados pessoais, mas você precisa dos dados para a instauração, exercício ou defesa de processos judiciais, ou
    
* se se tiver oposto ao tratamento que se rege pela base jurídica "interesses legítimos" até que tenha sido verificado se os nossos fundamentos legítimos prevalecem sobre os seus interesses, direitos e liberdades.

**Direito de portabilidade de dados** - Pode solicitar a receção dos dados pessoais, que nos tenha proporcionado, num formato estruturado, comummente utilizado e legível por máquina e transmitir estes dados para outro responsável pelo tratamento sem impedimentos da nossa parte, quando o tratamento for baseado no consentimento ou na execução de um contrato e for realizado por meios automatizados; nestes casos, você também pode solicitar que os dados pessoais sejam transmitidos diretamente a outro responsável pelo tratamento desde que isto seja viável tecnicamente.

Além disso, dispõe dos seguintes direitos:

**Direito de retirada do consentimento -** Pode retirar o seu consentimento em qualquer momento para o futuro quando o tratamento tiver sido baseado no seu consentimento, sem afetar a legalidade do tratamento com base no consentimento prévio à retirada.

**Direito de oposição-**

**Você usufrui do direito de se opor, por motivos relacionados com a sua situação particular, e, em qualquer momento ao tratamento dos seus dados pessoais que seja baseado no nosso interesse legítimo ou de terceiros (art.º 6.º (1) (f) GDPR). Depois, iremos deixar de tratar os seus dados pessoais para o efeito ao qual se opôs, exceto se formos capazes de demonstrar fundamentos legítimos convincentes para o tratamento que se sobreponham aos seus interesses, direitos e liberdades ou para a instauração, exercício ou defesa de processos judiciais.**

**Além disso, usufrui do direito de se opor em qualquer momento ao tratamento dos seus dados pessoais para efeitos de «marketing» direto. Quando se opuser ao tratamento para efeitos de «marketing» direto, deixaremos de tratar os seus dados pessoais para essas finalidades.**

* * *

**Direito de apresentar uma reclamação -** Pode apresentar uma reclamação a uma autoridade supervisora, em particular no Estado-Membro da sua residência habitual, local de trabalho ou local de uma alegada infração se considerar que o tratamento dos seus dados pessoais viola o RGPD.

A nossa autoridade competente de proteção de dados é:

Cidade Livre e Hanseática de Hamburgo, o Comissário para a Proteção dos Dados e para a Liberdade de Informação de Hamburgo, Ludwig-Erhard-Str. 22, 20459 [Hamburgo, «e-mail»: mailbox@datenschutz.hamburg.de](mailto:mailbox@datenschutz.hamburg.de)

**B. RGPD do Reino Unido**

Se você estiver localizado no Reino Unido, ao abrigo do RGPD do Reino Unido e das leis de proteção de dados, usufrui igualmente de direitos. A aplicabilidade dos direitos pode depender das circunstâncias. Para exercer qualquer um destes direitos, deve usar os dados de contacto proporcionados abaixo. Os direitos são:

**Direito de informação** -- Você usufrui do direito de receber informações concisas, transparentes, inteligíveis e facilmente acessíveis sobre os seus dados pessoais e a nossa utilização dos mesmos. Esta Política é a nossa forma de lhe prestar essa informação, mas se tiver mais perguntas ou preocupações, deve usar os dados de contacto proporcionados abaixo.

**Direito de acesso** -- Você usufrui do direito de nos solicitar cópias dos seus dados pessoais. Este direito é sempre aplicável, embora haja algumas isenções à sua aplicação, o que significa que nem sempre poderá receber toda a informação que tiver solicitado. Ao solicitar os seus dados pessoais, está a realizar aquilo que se designa como um pedido de acesso do titular dos dados (DSAR). Podemos ter de lhe pedir os seus documentos de identificação para verificar a sua identidade quando recebermos um DSAR.

**Direito de retificação** -- Você usufrui do direito de nos solicitar a retificação dos dados pessoais que considerar imprecisos. Usufrui igualmente do direito de nos pedir que completemos os dados que considerar incompletos.

**Direito de apagamento** — Você usufrui do direito de nos solicitar o apagamento dos seus dados pessoais em determinadas circunstâncias. Temos o direito de recusar o cumprimento de um pedido de apagamento se estivermos a tratar os dados pessoais por uma das seguintes razões:

* Para exercer o direito de liberdade de expressão e informação.
    
* Para cumprir uma obrigação legal.
    
* Para desempenhar uma tarefa de interesse público ou exercer autoridade oficial.
    
* Para efeitos de arquivo de interesse público, investigação científica, investigação histórica ou fins estatísticos.
    
* Para o exercício ou defesa em processos judiciais.

**Direito de limitação do tratamento** -- Você usufrui do direito de solicitar que limitemos o tratamento dos seus dados pessoais em determinadas circunstâncias. Neste caso, iremos continuar a conservar os dados, mas não faremos um tratamento adicional. Este direito é uma alternativa ao direito de apagamento. Se uma das seguintes condições se aplicar, pode exercer o direito de limitação do tratamento:

* A exatidão dos dados pessoais for contestada.
    
* O tratamento dos dados pessoais for ilegal.
    
* Caso já não precisemos dos dados pessoais para o tratamento, mas os dados pessoais são necessários como parte de um processo judicial.
    
* O direito de oposição foi exercido e o tratamento está limitado na pendência de uma decisão sobre o estado do tratamento.

**Direito de oposição ao tratamento -- Você usufrui do direito de se opor ao tratamento em determinadas circunstâncias, incluindo o «marketing» direto. Também se pode opor ao tratamento com base no nosso interesse jurídico (ou os de um terceiro). Depois, iremos deixar de tratar os seus dados pessoais para o efeito ao qual se opôs, exceto se formos capazes de demonstrar fundamentos legítimos convincentes para o tratamento que se sobreponham aos seus interesses, direitos e liberdades ou para a instauração, o exercício ou a defesa de processos judiciais.**

**Direito de portabilidade de dados** — Você usufrui do direito de receber os seus dados pessoais num formato estruturado, usado comummente e legível por máquina mas que só se aplica se estivermos a tratar informações com base no seu consentimento ou para a execução de um contrato e se o tratamento for automatizado.

**Direito de retirada do consentimento -** Pode retirar o seu consentimento em qualquer momento para o futuro quando o tratamento tiver sido baseado no seu consentimento, sem afetar a legalidade do tratamento com base no consentimento prévio à retirada.

**Informação de contacto**

Se quiser exercer algum dos seus direitos ou tiver alguma questão sobre a nossa utilização dos seus dados pessoais, utilize a informação disponível em Contacto. Assegure-se também de que, quando fizer isto, proporciona informação suficiente para nos permitir a sua identificação clara.

Tenha em conta que nomeamos um Representante do Reino Unido que poderá contactar em nosso nome de acordo com o art.º 27.º do RGPD do Reino Unido: eHarmony UK Ltd., 6-10 Grande Portland Street, Londres W1W 8QL, Grã-Bretanha

**Transferências de dados pessoais para fora do Reino Unido**

Para obter mais informação sobre a proteção e as salvaguardas aplicadas aos seus dados pessoais quando são transferidos para fora do Reino Unido, consulte a Secção 5 Transferências de dados pessoais no contexto de países localizado fora do EEE/UK/CH, acima.

**Direito de apresentação de uma reclamação a uma autoridade supervisora**

Você usufrui do direito de apresentar uma reclamação a um regulador de proteção de dados.

Pode contactar a autoridade de proteção de dados do Reino Unido, o Gabinete do Comissário para a Informação, em: Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF, número de telefone: + 44 (0) 303 123 1113, «E-mail»: [casework@ico.org.uk](mailto:casework@ico.org.uk).

**C. Lei suíça de proteção de dados**

**Direito de acesso** -- Você usufrui do direito de nos solicitar cópias dos seus dados pessoais. Este direito é sempre aplicável, embora haja algumas isenções à sua aplicação, o que significa que nem sempre poderá receber toda a informação que tiver solicitado. Ao solicitar os seus dados pessoais, está a realizar aquilo que se designa como um pedido de acesso do titular dos dados (DSAR).

**Direito de retificação** -- Você usufrui do direito de nos solicitar a retificação dos dados pessoais que considerar imprecisos. Usufrui igualmente do direito de nos pedir que completemos os dados que considerar incompletos.

**Direito de apagamento** — Você usufrui do direito de nos solicitar o apagamento dos seus dados pessoais em determinadas circunstâncias. Temos o direito de recusar o cumprimento de um pedido de apagamento se estivermos a tratar os dados pessoais por uma das seguintes razões:

* Para exercer o direito de liberdade de expressão e informação.
    
* Para cumprir uma obrigação legal.
    
* Para desempenhar uma tarefa de interesse público ou exercer autoridade oficial.
    
* Para efeitos de arquivo de interesse público, investigação científica, investigação histórica ou fins estatísticos.
    
* Para o exercício ou defesa em processos judiciais.

**Direito de limitação do tratamento** -- Você usufrui do direito de solicitar que limitemos o tratamento dos seus dados pessoais em determinadas circunstâncias. Neste caso, iremos continuar a conservar os dados, mas não faremos um tratamento adicional. Este direito é uma alternativa ao direito de apagamento. Se uma das seguintes condições se aplicar, pode exercer o direito de limitação do tratamento:

* A exatidão dos dados pessoais for contestada.
    
* O tratamento dos dados pessoais for ilegal.
    
* Caso já não precisemos dos dados pessoais para o tratamento, mas os dados pessoais são necessários como parte de um processo judicial.
    
* O direito de oposição foi exercido e o tratamento está limitado na pendência de uma decisão sobre o estado do tratamento.

**Direito de oposição ao tratamento** -- Você usufrui do direito de se opor ao tratamento em determinadas circunstâncias. Também pode opor-se se o tratamento for para uma tarefa realizada no interesse público, no exercício da autoridade oficial de que seja investido ou nos nossos interesses legítimo (ou do de terceiros).

**Direito de oposição ao «marketing» direto** - Você também usufrui do direito de se opor em qualquer altura ao tratamento dos seus dados pessoais para efeitos de publicidade ("objeção à publicidade"). Deve levar isto em conta: por motivos organizacionais, pode haver uma sobreposição entre a sua revogação e a utilização dos seus dados no contexto de uma campanha já em curso.

**Direito de portabilidade de dados** -- Este direito apenas é aplicável se estivermos a tratar informação com base no seu consentimento ou para a execução de um contrato e o tratamento for automatizado.

Se quiser exercer algum dos seus direitos, use a informação em Contacto. Assegure-se também de que, quando fizer isto, proporciona a informação suficiente para nos permitir a sua identificação clara.

**Informação de contacto**

Se quiser exercer algum dos seus direitos ou tiver alguma questão sobre a nossa utilização dos seus dados pessoais, utilize a informação disponível em Contacto. Assegure-se também de que, quando fizer isto, proporciona informação suficiente para nos permitir a sua identificação clara.

Deve ter em conta que nomeámos um representante segundo o art.º 14.º nDSG (a nova lei de proteção de dados da Suíça): Treforma AG a/c MLL Legal; Grabenstrasse 25; 6340 Baar; Suíça; [meetgroup@dsg-mll.com](mailto:meetgroup@dsg-mll.com)

**Transferências de dados pessoais para fora da Suíça**

Para obter mais informação sobre a proteção e as salvaguardas aplicadas aos seus dados pessoais quando são transferidos para fora da Suíça, consulte a Secção 5 Transferências de dados pessoais no contexto de países localizado fora do EEE/UK/CH acima.

**Direito de apresentação de uma reclamação a uma autoridade supervisora**

Você usufrui do direito de apresentar uma reclamação a um regulador de proteção de dados.

Pode contactar a autoridade supervisora de proteção de dados competente na Suíça. Que é:

Comissário Federal de Informação e Proteção de Dados (FDPIC).

Pode contactá-lo através de:

[https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/de/home/deredoeb/kontakt/kontaktformular\_bgoe.html](https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/de/home/deredoeb/kontakt/kontaktformular_bgoe.html)

**The Meet Group Inc.**

Datenschutzrichtlinie für Benutzer mit Wohnsitz im Europäischen Wirtschaftsraum oder im Vereinigten Königreich
==============================================================================================================

_Stand: October 8, 2024_

Für The Meet Group, Inc., ihre Marken, verbundenen Unternehmen und Tochtergesellschaften hat Ihre Privatsphäre einen hohen Stellenwert. In dieser Datenschutzrichtlinie („ **Richtlinie** “) wird erläutert, wie The Meet Group, Inc. („ **TMG** “, „ **wir** “, „ **unser** “ in allen gebeugten Formen oder „ **uns** “) die in dieser Richtlinie beschriebenen personenbezogenen Daten erfasst, verwendet, offenlegt und anderweitig verarbeitet, sowie die Rechte und Wahlmöglichkeiten, die Sie in Bezug auf diese personenbezogenen Daten haben.

Weitere Informationen zu den Wahlmöglichkeiten, die Sie in Bezug auf Ihre personenbezogenen Daten haben, finden Sie in Abschnitt 7. „Ihre Wahlmöglichkeiten zum Datenschutz“ sowie in Abschnitt 15. „Zusätzliche Informationen zum Datenschutz für bestimmte Rechtsordnungen“, der zusätzliche Informationen über Datenschutzrechte für Einwohner bestimmter Rechtsgebiete enthält.

Wenn Sie in der EU/dem Europäischen Wirtschaftsraum (EWR) ansässig sind, lesen Sie bitte Abschnitt 15.A. „Zusätzliche Informationen für Einwohner der EU/des EWR“, um sich über Ihre Rechte gemäß der Datenschutz-Grundverordnung („DSGVO“) zu informieren.

Wenn Sie im Vereinigten Königreich ansässig sind, lesen Sie bitte Abschnitt 15.B. „Zusätzliche Informationen für Einwohner des Vereinigten Königreichs“, um sich über Ihre Rechte im Rahmen der General Data Protection Regulation zu informieren, die gemäß Abschnitt 3 des britischen European Union (Withdrawal) Act 2018 in das britische Recht aufgenommen wurde („UK GDPR“).

Wenn Sie in der Schweiz ansässig sind, lesen Sie bitte Abschnitt 15.C. „Zusätzliche Informationen für Einwohner der Schweiz“, um sich über Ihre Rechte gemäß dem neuen Schweizer Datenschutzgesetz („nDSG“) zu informieren.

Wenn Sie ein Profil in einem unserer Dienste erstellen, können einige Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten wie Benutzername, Name, Alter, Geschlecht und sexuelle Orientierung in Übereinstimmung mit Ihren Datenschutzeinstellungen auch für Benutzer des jeweiligen Dienstes und unserer anderen Dienste sowie anderer Anwendungen, die uns gehören, und anderer Anwendungen und Websites, die uns nicht gehören und mit denen wir unsere Live-Plattform teilen, sichtbar sein. Diese anderen Benutzer können weltweit ansässig sein. Eine Liste unserer gegenwärtigen Live-Partner finden Sie [hier](https://talent.tagged.com/partner-policy-tagged.html).

Ihre Nutzung unserer Dienste unterliegt unseren [Allgemeinen Geschäftsbedingungen](https://secure.tagged.com/terms_of_service.html), einschließlich der darin enthaltenen geltenden Bestimmungen über Schadensersatzbeschränkungen und die Beilegung von Streitigkeiten.

**Inhaltsverzeichnis**

1. Geltungsbereich
    
2. Erfasste personenbezogene Daten
    
3. Zwecke der Erfassung und Verarbeitung
    
4. Offenlegung personenbezogener Daten
    
5. Übermittlung personenbezogener Daten in Bezug auf Länder außerhalb des EWR/des Vereinigten Königreichs/der Schweiz
    
6. Cookies, Targeting und Analysen
    
7. Ihre Wahlmöglichkeiten zum Datenschutz
    
8. Aufbewahrungsdauer für personenbezogene Daten
    
9. Externe Links und Funktionen
    
10. Von Benutzern generierte Inhalte
    
11. Sicherheit
    
12. Privatsphäre von Kindern
    
13. Änderungen an dieser Richtlinie
    
14. Contact Us
    
15. Zusätzliche Informationen zum Datenschutz für bestimmte Rechtsordnungen

**1\. Geltungsbereich**

Sofern nachstehend nicht anders beschrieben, gilt diese Richtlinie für die personenbezogenen Daten, die TMG erfasst und verarbeitet, und zwar in Bezug auf: Besucher unserer Website, auf der diese Richtlinie veröffentlicht ist, einschließlich aller unserer Websites, die auf diese Richtlinie verlinken oder sie veröffentlichen (die „ **Websites** “); Personen, die unsere Mobilanwendung („ **Mobil-App** “, z. B. die Tagged-App oder die Pets-App) verwenden; Personen, die sich für unsere Veranstaltungen, Umfragen, Forschungsprojekte, Werbeaktionen und Gewinnspiele anmelden oder daran teilnehmen; und Personen, die mit uns kommunizieren oder anderweitig mit uns oder den Diensten, die über unsere Websites, die Mobil-App oder andere Online-Dienste verfügbar sind, interagieren (zusammenfassend als die „ **Dienste** “ bezeichnet).

**2\. Erfasste personenbezogene Daten**

Wie nachstehend dargelegt, können wir personenbezogene Daten direkt von Ihnen, aus Drittquellen und automatisch durch Ihre Nutzung unserer Dienste erfassen.

**Personenbezogene Daten, die direkt von Ihnen erfasst werden** . Welche personenbezogenen Daten wir im Einzelnen erfassen, hängt von Ihrer Nutzung unserer Dienste und unseren Interaktionen mit Ihnen ab, aber im Allgemeinen können wir folgende Kategorien personenbezogener Daten direkt von Ihnen erfassen:

* **Kontaktangaben** . Wenn Sie mit uns in Kontakt treten, beispielsweise wenn Sie uns eine Nachricht senden oder sich für weitere Informationen zu unseren Diensten anmelden, können wir Ihren Namen, Ihre E-Mail-Adresse, Ihre Telefonnummer oder andere ähnliche Identifikatoren sowie Ihre Nachricht, die Art Ihrer Anfrage und alle anderen von Ihnen bereitgestellten Informationen erfassen.
    
* **Konto- und Profilinformationen** . Wenn Sie sich für ein Konto in Verbindung mit unseren Diensten registrieren (z. B. für ein Tagged-Konto), können wir Ihren Namen, Ihre E-Mail-Adresse, Telefonnummer, Adresse (z. B. Postleitzahl), Ihren Benutzernamen und Ihr Passwort, Geburtsdatum, Geschlecht, Ihre sexuelle Orientierung, Ihr Profilbild und -foto, Ihre Rechnungsadresse sowie alle anderen Informationen erfassen, die Sie uns in Verbindung mit der Erstellung oder Pflege Ihres Kontos zur Verfügung stellen oder anderweitig über Ihr Konto übermitteln.

Wenn Sie eine Anmeldung über Drittanbieter wie Facebook oder Apple oder auch SMS gewählt haben, geben Sie bei der Registrierung weder eine E-Mail-Adresse noch ein Passwort ein. Die betreffenden Benutzer greifen auf unseren Dienst zu, indem sie die von ihnen angegebene E-Mail-Adresse und das von ihnen gewählte Passwort (Anmeldeinformationen) verwenden oder alternativ die Anmeldeinformationen des Drittanbieters nutzen.

**Registrierung über Facebook („Facebook-Anmeldung“)**

Wir bieten Single Sign-On über Facebook an. Dadurch erhalten Sie die Möglichkeit, sich über Ihr Facebook-Konto zu registrieren. Wenn Sie die Funktion nutzen, erhalten und verarbeiten wir für die Registrierung folgende Authentifizierungsdaten von Facebook: E-Mail-Adresse, Profilname, Geschlecht, Geburtsdatum und das dort gespeicherte Profilbild. Die diesbezüglichen Daten werden also übertragen.

Wenn Sie sich über Facebook auf unserer Website oder in unserer App anmelden, erfasst Facebook auch Daten von Drittanbieter-Skripten, verarbeitet sie für Facebook-Analysezwecke oder leitet sie an Dritte weiter. In der Datenschutzrichtlinie von Facebook wird dargelegt, welche Daten erfasst werden können, wenn Sie die Facebook-Anmeldung verwenden.Dazu gehören Daten über Ihr Gerät, Ihre Nutzung unseres Dienstes, die von Ihnen besuchten Websites und die von Ihnen angesehene Werbung. Leider können Sie diese Verarbeitung im Zusammenhang mit unserem Service technisch nicht ablehnen. Wenn Sie nicht möchten, dass Facebook Daten über Sie im Zusammenhang mit Ihrer Nutzung unseres Online-Angebots erfasst und für eigene Zwecke verwendet, sollten Sie die Facebook-Anmeldung nicht nutzen.

Sie können Ihr Tagged-Konto jederzeit von Ihrem Facebook-Konto trennen. In diesem Fall müssen Sie uns die vorgenannten Zugangsdaten bereitstellen.

Weitere Informationen über Zweck und Umfang der Datenerfassung und die weitere Verarbeitung und Nutzung Ihrer Daten durch Facebook sowie über Ihre Rechte und Einstellungsoptionen zum Schutz Ihrer Daten finden Sie in der Datenschutzrichtlinie von Facebook: [http://www.facebook.com/policy.php](http://www.facebook.com/policy.php).

**Registrierung/Anmeldung über Google**

Wenn Sie ein Android-Endgerät verwenden, bieten wir Ihnen die Möglichkeit, sich über Ihr Google-Konto bei unserem Dienst zu registrieren oder anzumelden. In diesem Fall stellt uns Google Ireland Limited, Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Irland („Google“) die für die Registrierung oder Anmeldung erforderlichen Daten (E-Mail-Adresse, Name, Google-Konto-ID und Google-Konto-Profilbild) zur Verfügung.

Wir haben keinen Einfluss auf den Umfang der Daten, die Google über die Google-Anmeldung erfasst. Wenn Sie nicht möchten, dass Google Daten über Sie im Zusammenhang mit Ihrer Nutzung unseres Online-Angebots erfasst und für eigene Zwecke verwendet, sollten Sie die Google-Anmeldung nicht nutzen.

Weitere Informationen über Zweck und Umfang der Datenerfassung und die weitere Verarbeitung und Nutzung Ihrer Daten durch Google sowie über Ihre Rechte und Einstellungsoptionen zum Schutz Ihrer Daten finden Sie in der Datenschutzrichtlinie von Google: [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

**Registrierung/Anmeldung über „Mit Apple anmelden“**

Wenn Sie ein iOS-Endgerät verwenden, bieten wir Ihnen die Möglichkeit, sich über Apple bei unserem Service zu registrieren oder anzumelden. In diesem Fall stellt uns Apple Inc., One Apple Park Way, Cupertino, California, USA, 95014 („Apple“) die von Ihnen ausgewählten Informationen zur Verfügung, die für die Registrierung oder Anmeldung erforderlich sind (z. B. von Apple generierte E-Mail-Adresse, Name).

Wir haben keinen Einfluss auf den Umfang der Daten, die Apple über die Apple-Anmeldung erfasst. Wenn Sie nicht möchten, dass Apple Daten über Sie im Zusammenhang mit Ihrer Nutzung unseres Online-Angebots erfasst und für eigene Zwecke verwendet, sollten Sie die Apple-Anmeldung nicht nutzen.

Weitere Informationen über Zweck und Umfang der Datenerfassung und die weitere Verarbeitung und Nutzung Ihrer Daten durch Apple sowie über Ihre Rechte und Einstellungsoptionen zum Schutz Ihrer Daten finden Sie in der Datenschutzrichtlinie von Apple: [https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/de/sign-in-with-apple/](https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/en/sign-in-with-apple/).

**Bei der Registrierung/Anmeldung per telefonischer Authentifizierung**

Wir geben Ihnen die Möglichkeit, sich im Rahmen der Registrierung/Anmeldung per telefonischer Authentifizierung mit Ihrer Mobiltelefonnummer zu authentifizieren, die Sie uns entsprechend mitteilen müssen. Wir senden Ihnen dann eine SMS mit einem Verifizierungscode, den Sie in der App eingeben müssen, um die Registrierung abzuschließen. Wenn Sie sich anmelden möchten, senden wir Ihnen eine SMS mit einem Code, mit dem Sie sich bei Ihrem Konto anmelden können. Darüber hinaus findet ein Verifizierungsverfahren statt. Dieser Dienst wird von Sinch America Inc. angeboten, einer Gesellschaft nach dem Recht des Bundesstaates Delaware und erreichbar unter: Legal Department, 3500 Lenox Rd NE, Ste. 1875, Atlanta, GA 30326, Georgia, USA,

und ist nur mit Ihrer vorherigen Einwilligung möglich.

Weitere Informationen über den Zweck und den Umfang der Verarbeitung Ihrer Daten durch Sinch finden Sie in der Datenschutzrichtlinie von Sinch: [https://www.sinch.com/privacy-notice/](https://www.sinch.com/privacy-notice/)

* **Käufe, Zahlungen und Belohnungen** . Wenn Sie einen Kauf oder eine Zahlung über unsere Dienste tätigen (z. B. in Verbindung mit unserer Pets-Spielfunktion), können wir Informationen wie Zahlungsart, Bankkartendetails, Rechnungs- und Kaufinformationen sowie andere finanzielle oder geschäftsbezogene Informationen erfassen, die für die Ermöglichung unserer Dienste erforderlich sind.
    
* **Kommunikation und Interaktionen** . Wenn Sie per E-Mail, telefonisch oder auf andere Weise mit uns oder anderen TMG-Benutzern kommunizieren oder interagieren, insbesondere wenn Sie sich in unsere Mailing-Listen eintragen, Formulare auf unseren Websites oder in unserer Mobil-App ausfüllen, mit unseren Social-Media-Seiten interagieren, eine Bewertung oder ein Testimonial veröffentlichen, Inhalte in Online-Diskussionsgruppen übermitteln oder anderweitig Informationen in öffentliche Kommentarfelder, Blogs oder Community-Foren eingeben, die von TMG gesponsert werden oder mit TMG verbunden sind, können wir Aufzeichnungen über Ihre Kontaktdaten, Mitteilungen und Interaktionen, Ihre Beiträge oder Einsendungen und gegebenenfalls unsere Antworten erfassen, empfangen und pflegen.
    
* **Werbeinformationen** . Wenn Sie zustimmen, Marketingmitteilungen von uns zu erhalten, können wir Ihren Namen, Ihre E-Mail-Adresse, Ihre Telefonnummer, Ihre Präferenzen und gegebenenfalls Informationen über Ihr Konto und Ihr Profil erfassen, einschließlich der von Ihnen genutzten Dienste und Funktionen. Wenn Sie an speziellen Aktivitäten, Angeboten, Programmen oder Aktionen teilnehmen, die wir anbieten, können wir außerdem bestimmte Kontaktdaten, Ihr Alter und weitere Informationen erfassen, die gegebenenfalls gesetzlich vorgeschrieben sind. Wenn Sie eine Werbeaktion gewinnen, müssen wir je nach Preis auch bestimmte Steuerinformationen und/oder Verzichtserklärungen und Freistellungen erfassen.
    
* **Antworten und Feedback** . Wenn Sie an von uns durchgeführten Umfragen, Fragebögen oder Forschungsaktivitäten oder -initiativen teilnehmen, z. B. zur Zufriedenheit der Benutzer oder zu anderen ähnlichen Zwecken, können wir Ihre Antworten und Ihr Feedback sowie alle sonstigen von Ihnen bereitgestellten Informationen erfassen.
    
* **Details zu Veranstaltungen und Registrierung** . Wir können zudem personenbezogene Daten im Zusammenhang mit Ihrer Teilnahme an unseren Veranstaltungen sowie mit anderen Anfragen erfassen, die Sie im Zusammenhang mit unseren Diensten an uns richten. Wenn Sie sich beispielsweise für eine von uns ausgerichtete oder gesponserte Veranstaltung anmelden oder daran teilnehmen, können wir Informationen im Zusammenhang mit Ihrer Anmeldung zu und Ihrer Teilnahme an einer solchen Veranstaltung erfassen.
    
* **Präferenzen und andere Wünsche** . Wir können zudem Informationen über Ihre Präferenzen erfassen, einschließlich Kommunikationspräferenzen, Präferenzen in Bezug auf Ihre Nutzung unserer Dienste und andere Präferenzen oder Wünsche, die Sie uns bei der Interaktion mit uns mitteilen.

Im Allgemeinen sind Sie nicht verpflichtet, uns Ihre personenbezogenen Daten mitzuteilen. Für die Nutzung bestimmter Dienste oder Aspekte unserer Dienste, wie z. B. die Registrierung für ein Tagged-Konto, kann jedoch die Angabe personenbezogener Daten erforderlich sein. Wenn dies der Fall ist, weisen wir Sie darauf hin. Wenn Sie uns die erforderlichen Angaben nicht übermitteln möchten, können Sie den entsprechenden Dienst leider nicht nutzen.

**Personenbezogene Daten, die von Dritten erfasst werden** . Wir können zudem bestimmte personenbezogene Daten über Sie aus Drittquellen erfassen und erhalten, wie z. B. von Geschäftspartnern, insbesondere bei der Nutzung von App-Store-Anbietern für Einkäufe, von anderen TMG-Benutzern, von Datenanalyse- und Marketinganbietern, von Betriebssystemen und Social-Media-Plattformen, insbesondere bei der Nutzung der oben beschriebenen Anmeldefunktionen. Darüber hinaus können wir folgende personenbezogenen Daten aus Drittquellen erfassen:

* **Informationen im Zusammenhang mit der Registrierung über Social Media und anderen Plattformen** . Im Rahmen der Nutzung unserer Dienste können Sie über verschiedene Social-Media-Plattformen, Social-Networking-Dienste oder andere Funktionen oder integrierte Dienste von Drittanbietern Informationen oder Inhalte teilen, sich bei den Diensten anmelden oder sich bei diesen registrieren. Wenn Sie über Ihre Social-Media-Konten oder andere ähnliche integrierte Dienste und Funktionen eine Verbindung mit unseren Diensten herstellen, können wir personenbezogene Daten über Sie erfassen oder erhalten, die Sie dem betreffenden Social-Media-Konto bzw. dem Dienst oder der Funktion zur Verfügung gestellt haben. So können wir beispielsweise Informationen aus Ihrem Konto und Profil erfassen, wie Ihren Namen, Ihre E-Mail-Adresse, Ihre Benutzer-ID, Ihr Profilbild, Ihre Freundesliste und andere ähnliche Informationen, die auf Ihrem Profil verfügbar sind. Sie sollten Ihre Datenschutzeinstellungen auf den einzelnen Social-Media-Plattformen, Funktionen oder integrierten Diensten überprüfen, um mehr darüber zu erfahren, wie Ihre personenbezogenen Daten von diesen Parteien verwendet, offengelegt oder anderweitig verarbeitet werden können.
    
* **Informationen im Zusammenhang mit Empfehlungen** . Wir können Ihnen die Möglichkeit bieten, Freunde einzuladen oder anderen Benutzern den Zugang zu unseren Diensten oder deren Nutzung zu empfehlen. Dabei können wir bestimmte personenbezogene Daten über Sie erfassen und erhalten, auch von anderen gegenwärtigen oder potenziellen TMG-Benutzern und -Kunden, die diese Aktivitäten ebenfalls ausüben.

**Automatisch erfasste personenbezogene Daten** . Wir und unsere externen Dienstleister können automatisch personenbezogene Daten über Sie im Zusammenhang mit Ihrer Nutzung unserer Dienste erfassen oder ableiten, insbesondere durch den Einsatz von Cookies, Zählpixeln und anderen ähnlichen Technologien.Insbesondere können wir folgende personenbezogenen Daten automatisch erfassen:

* **Geräte- und Browserinformationen** . Wenn Sie unsere Dienste nutzen, erfassen wir möglicherweise Browsertyp, Domainname, Seitenaufrufe, Zugriffszeiten, Datums-/Zeitstempel, Betriebssystem, Sprache, Gerätetyp, eindeutige Kennung, Internetdienstanbieter, verweisende und verlassende URLs, Clickstream-Daten, Sprache und ähnliche Geräte- und Browserinformationen.
    
* **Aktivitäten und Nutzung** . Darüber hinaus können wir Informationen zu Aktivitäten im Zusammenhang mit Ihrer Nutzung der Dienste erfassen, z. B. Informationen über angeklickte Links, Suchvorgänge, genutzte Funktionen, angezeigte Elemente, die in den Diensten verbrachte Zeit, Ihre Interaktionen mit uns und anderen innerhalb der Dienste und weitere ähnliche Informationen zu Ihren Aktivitäten und Ihrer Nutzung der Dienste.
    
* **Informationen zum Standort** . Wir können zudem allgemeine Informationen über Ihren Standort erfassen oder ableiten, z. B. über Ihre IP-Adresse.

Weitere Informationen über unseren Einsatz von Cookies und anderen ähnlichen Technologien finden Sie im nachstehenden Abschnitt 6. „Cookies, Targeting und Analysen“.

**3\. Zwecke der Erfassung und Verarbeitung**

Im Allgemeinen können wir die von uns erfassten Kategorien personenbezogener Daten zu folgenden Zwecken erfassen, verwenden, offenlegen und anderweitig verarbeiten:

* **Dienste und Kundenbetreuung** . Um unsere Dienste bereitzustellen und zu betreiben (z. B. Tagged oder die Pets-Spielfunktion), Ihr Konto zu verwalten, mit Ihnen über Ihre Nutzung der Dienste zu kommunizieren, Fehler zu beheben, technischen Support zu leisten oder für ähnliche Kundenbetreuungszwecke und um auf Ihre Anfragen zu antworten, Ihre Wünsche zu erfüllen, die Zahlungsabwicklung zu vereinfachen und anderweitig unsere alltäglichen Abläufe durchzuführen. Dies schließt ein, dass einige Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten wie Ihre Benutzer-ID, Ihr Benutzername und die in Ihren Datenschutzeinstellungen ausgewählten Kontaktdaten für Benutzer des jeweiligen Dienstes oder unserer anderen Dienste sowie anderer Anwendungen, die uns gehören, und anderer Anwendungen und Websites, die uns nicht gehören und mit denen wir unsere Live-Plattform teilen, sichtbar gemacht werden. TMG stützt sich auf die Rechtsgrundlage „Erfüllung eines Vertrags“ (Art. 6 (1) (b) der DSGVO und UK GDPR sowie Art. 31 (2) (b) nDSG). Soweit wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten verarbeiten, um sie für Benutzer unserer anderen Dienste und anderer Anwendungen, die uns gehören, sowie anderer Anwendungen und Websites, die uns nicht gehören und mit denen wir unsere Live-Plattform teilen, sichtbar zu machen, stützt sich TMG auf die Grundlage der „Erfüllung eines Vertrags“ (Art. 6 (1) (b) der DSGVO und UK GDPR sowie Art. 31 (2) (b) nDSG).

Hinsichtlich der Daten zum Standort stützt sich TMG auf Ihre Einwilligung (Art. 6 (1) (a), Art. 7 DSGVO).

Hinsichtlich der sexuellen Orientierung stützt sich TMG auf Ihre ausdrückliche Einwilligung (Art. 6 (1) (a), Art. 7, Art. 9 (2) (a) DSGVO/UK GDPR) oder auf die Ausnahme in Art. 9 (2) (e) DSGVO/UK GDPR, sofern Sie Ihre sexuelle Orientierung öffentlich mitgeteilt haben (z. B. in einem Livestream).

* **Analysen und Verbesserung** . Um besser zu verstehen, wie Benutzer auf die Dienste zugreifen und diese nutzen, sowie für andere Forschungs- und Analysezwecke, wie z. B. zur Bewertung und Verbesserung der Website, unserer Dienste und unserer Geschäftsabläufe, einschließlich der Entwicklung unserer Dienste und ihrer Funktionen, sowie für interne Qualitätskontrollen und Schulungszwecke.TMG stützt sich auf die Rechtsgrundlage „berechtigte Interessen“ (Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO/UK GDPR und Art. 31 (1) nDSG). In diesem Zusammenhang hat TMG ein Interesse daran, die Leistung des Dienstes aus wirtschaftlicher Sicht zu verstehen.

**Kommunikation** . Um Ihre Fragen zu beantworten, Ihnen angefordertes Material sowie Informationen und Materialien zu unseren Diensten und Angeboten zukommen zu lassen. Wir können diese Daten auch verwenden, um Ihnen administrative Informationen zu senden, z. B. Informationen über die Dienste und Änderungen unserer Bedingungen und Richtlinien. TMG stützt sich auf die Rechtsgrundlage „Erfüllung eines Vertrags“ (Art. 6 (1) (b) DSGVO/UK GDPR und Art. 31 (2) (a) nDSG) oder – wenn kein Vertrag zwischen dem betreffenden Benutzer und TMG besteht – „berechtigte Interessen“ (Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO/UK GDPR und Art. 31 (1) nDSG). Sofern TMG sich auf „berechtigte Interessen“ beruft, verfolgt TMG ihre Interessen an der Bereitstellung von Kundenbetreuung sowie an der Beantwortung von Anfragen, um die Zufriedenheit der Benutzer sicherzustellen.

* **Anpassung und Personalisierung** . Zur Anpassung von Inhalten, die wir senden oder in den Diensten anzeigen, insbesondere zur Anpassung an den jeweiligen Standort und zur sonstigen Personalisierung Ihrer Erfahrungen und Angebote. TMG stützt sich auf die Rechtsgrundlage „Erfüllung eines Vertrags“ (Art. 6 (1) (b) der DSGVO und UK GDPR sowie Art. 31 (2) (b) nDSG).
    
* Social Media und andere Plattformkommunikation. Damit Sie über verschiedene Social-Media-Plattformen, Social-Networking-Dienste oder andere Funktionen oder integrierte Dienste von Drittanbietern Informationen oder Inhalte teilen, sich bei den Diensten anmelden oder sich bei diesen registrieren können. Hinsichtlich Ihrer Möglichkeit, sich bei den Diensten anzumelden oder für diese zu registrieren, stützt sich TMG auf die Rechtsgrundlage „Erfüllung eines Vertrags“ (Art. 6 (1) (b) der DSGVO und UK GDPR sowie Art. 31 (2) (b) nDSG). Ansonsten stützt sich TMG auf die Rechtsgrundlage „berechtigte Interessen“ (Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO/UK GDPR und Art. 31 (1) nDSG). In diesem Zusammenhang hat TMG ein Interesse daran, den Benutzern die Möglichkeit zu geben, auf eigenen Wunsch bestimmte Kommunikationsvorgänge mit Social-Media-Plattformen, Social-Networking-Diensten oder anderen Funktionen oder integrierten Diensten von Drittanbietern zu initiieren.
    
* **Marketing und Werbung** . Zu Marketing-, Werbe- und Verkaufsförderungszwecken. Zum Beispiel, um Ihnen Werbeinformationen über unsere Dienste zukommen zu lassen, insbesondere Newslettern, Informationen über TMG-Veranstaltungen, Webinare, Präsentationen, Verkäufe, Angebote, Preisnachlässe und neue Angebote sowie andere Informationen, für deren Erhalt Sie sich angemeldet haben. TMG stützt sich auf die Rechtsgrundlage „Einwilligung“ (Art. 6 (1) (a) der DSGVO und UK GDPR sowie Art. 31 (1) nDSG).

Zum Zwecke der Eigenwerbung/des Direktmarketings durch E-Mails und/oder Push-Nachrichten, (Benutzer-)Umfragen und individuelle Anleitungen (ausschließlich TMG-Produkte). (Rechtsgrundlage ist das berechtigte Interesse von TMG am Direktmarketing für eigene Produkte sowie Paragraf 7 Absatz 3 des Gesetzes gegen den unlauteren Wettbewerb (UWG).)

* **Forschung und Umfragen** . Zur Durchführung von Umfragen und Fragebögen, beispielsweise zur Marktforschung, zur Ermittlung der Benutzerzufriedenheit oder zu anderen ähnlichen Zwecken. TMG stützt sich auf die Rechtsgrundlage „Einwilligung“ (Art. 6 (1) (a) der DSGVO und UK GDPR sowie Art. 31 (1) nDSG).
    
* **Entwicklung von Einblicken und Datenanreicherung** . Wir können über die Dienste erfasste personenbezogene Daten mit anderen Informationen kombinieren, die wir oder Dritte in anderen Kontexten über Sie erfassen. In den meisten Fällen identifizieren die Informationen, die wir mit den über die Dienste für die Marktforschung erfassten personenbezogenen Daten kombinieren, wie z. B. demografische Informationen, die Verbraucher nicht direkt. TMG stützt sich auf die Rechtsgrundlage „berechtigte Interessen“ (Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO/UK GDPR und Art. 31 (1) nDSG). In diesem Zusammenhang hat TMG ein Interesse daran, die Leistung des Dienstes aus wirtschaftlicher Sicht zu verstehen.
    
* **Zugriff auf Informationen und deren Speicherung auf dem Endgerät des Benutzers** . Wir können auf Informationen auf Ihrem Endgerät zugreifen oder Informationen darauf speichern. TMG stützt sich auf die Rechtsgrundlage „Einwilligung“, Art. 5 (3) der Datenschutzrichtlinie für elektronische Kommunikation und PECR Reg. 6 (4), sofern dies für den Betrieb unserer Website sowie für die Bereitstellung von Telemediendiensten, die vom Benutzer ausdrücklich gewünscht werden, nicht unbedingt erforderlich ist.
    
* **Planung und Verwaltung von Veranstaltungen** . Für die Planung von Veranstaltungen und andere verwaltungsbezogene Zwecke, wie z. B. die Anmeldung zu und die Teilnahme an Veranstaltungen, die Herstellung von Kontakten zwischen Ihnen und anderen Veranstaltungsteilnehmern und TMG-Benutzern sowie die Kontaktaufnahme mit Ihnen zu relevanten Veranstaltungen, Präsentationen und unseren Diensten. Wir können personenbezogene Daten auch für die Durchführung von besonderen Veranstaltungen, Preisausschreiben, Wettbewerben und Werbeaktionen verwenden, für die eigene spezifische Teilnahmebedingungen gelten können. TMG stützt sich auf die Rechtsgrundlage „Einwilligung“ (Art. 6 (1) (a) der DSGVO und UK GDPR sowie Art. 31 (1) nDSG).
    
* **Sicherheit und Schutz der Rechte** . Zum Schutz der Dienste und unseres Geschäftsbetriebs, unserer Rechte und der Rechte unserer Stakeholder und Anleger, zur Verhinderung und Erkennung von Betrug, unbefugten Aktivitäten und unbefugtem Zugriff sowie sonstigem Missbrauch unserer Website, insbesondere in Fällen, in denen wir dies für erforderlich halten, um rechtswidrige Aktivitäten, mutmaßlichen Betrug, Situationen, die eine potenzielle Bedrohung für die Sicherheit oder die Rechte einer Person oder eines Dritten darstellen, oder Verstöße gegen unsere Nutzungsbedingungen zu untersuchen, zu verhindern oder entsprechende Maßnahmen zu ergreifen. TMG stützt sich auf die Rechtsgrundlage „berechtigte Interessen“ (Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO/UK GDPR und Art. 31 (1) nDSG). Konkret haben TMG und die Benutzer von TMG ein Interesse daran, dass der Dienst von TMG nicht für vertrags- und/oder rechtswidrige Handlungen von Dritten missbraucht wird. Unser berechtigtes Interesse umfasst auch den Schutz unserer eigenen Systeme zur Sicherung der IT-Systeme von TMG und damit letztlich den Schutz der personenbezogenen Daten der Benutzer von TMG. Hinsichtlich der sexuellen Ausrichtung stützt sich TMG zusätzlich auf die Rechtsgrundlage zur Geltendmachung, Ausübung oder Verteidigung von Rechtsansprüchen (Art. 9 (2) (f) DSGVO/UK GDPR).
    
* **Compliance und Rechtsverfahren** . Zur Erfüllung geltender rechtlicher oder aufsichtsrechtlicher Verpflichtungen, insbesondere gesetzlicher Aufbewahrungspflichten oder im Rahmen eines Gerichtsverfahrens, als Reaktion auf eine Vorladung, eine richterliche Anordnung, einen Gerichtsbeschluss oder ein anderes rechtliches Verfahren oder im Rahmen einer Ermittlung oder eines formellen oder informellen Ersuchens von Strafverfolgungsbehörden oder einer Regierungsbehörde. TMG stützt sich auf die Rechtsgrundlage (i) „Erfüllung einer rechtlichen Verpflichtung“ (Art. 6 (1) (c) DSGVO/UK GDPR sowie Art. 31 (2) (a) nDSG), sofern sich diese Verpflichtung aus dem Recht der EU oder eines EU-Mitgliedstaats ergibt, oder (ii) „berechtigtes Interesse“ (Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO/UK GDPR sowie Art. 31 (1) nDSG), sofern sich diese Verpflichtung aus anderen Rechtsordnungen ergibt. Soweit berechtigte Interessen geltend gemacht werden, verfolgt TMG ihr Interesse an der Erfüllung der rechtlichen Verpflichtungen, denen TMG unterliegt. Hinsichtlich der sexuellen Ausrichtung stützt sich TMG zusätzlich auf die Rechtsgrundlage zur Geltendmachung, Ausübung oder Verteidigung von Rechtsansprüchen (Art. 9 (2) (f) DSGVO/UK GDPR).
    
* **Auditing, Berichterstattung und andere interne Vorgänge** . Zur Durchführung von Finanz-, Steuer- und Buchhaltungsprüfungen, Audits und Bewertungen unseres Betriebs, insbesondere unserer Datenschutz-, Sicherheits- und Finanzkontrollen, sowie für Risiko- und Compliance-Zwecke. Wir können personenbezogene Daten auch verwenden, um ordnungsgemäße Geschäftsunterlagen zu führen und unsere Richtlinien und Verfahren durchzusetzen. TMG stützt sich auf die Rechtsgrundlage „berechtigte Interessen“ (Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO/UK GDPR und Art. 31 (1) nDSG). Das berechtigte Interesse von TMG besteht darin, den Geschäftsbetrieb sicherzustellen und regelmäßig zu überprüfen, ob die Berichterstattungs- und Compliance-Verpflichtungen erfüllt werden.
    
* **Allgemeine geschäftliche und betriebliche Unterstützung** . Zur Bewertung und Durchführung von Fusionen, Übernahmen, Umstrukturierungen, Insolvenzverfahren und anderen Geschäftstransaktionen wie z. B. Finanzierungen sowie zur Verwaltung unserer Geschäfts-, Buchhaltungs-, Prüfungs-, Compliance-, Buchführungs- und Rechtsfunktionen. TMG stützt sich auf die Rechtsgrundlage „berechtigte Interessen“ (Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO und Art. 31 (1) nDSG). In diesem Zusammenhang hat TMG ein Interesse daran, potenziellen Käufern oder Interessenten für eine Übernahme und deren externen Beratern Informationen über ihre Vermögenswerte und Tätigkeiten offenzulegen und diese Informationen zu verarbeiten, um den Verkauf dieser Vermögenswerte und/oder Tätigkeiten zu erleichtern.

Die von uns im Zusammenhang mit der Verwendung von Cookies und ähnlichen Technologien verfolgten Zwecke, insbesondere in Bezug auf Targeting und Analysen, sind in Abschnitt 6. „Cookies, Targeting und Analysen“ beschrieben.

Sofern die Verarbeitung auf der Rechtsgrundlage Ihrer Einwilligung beruht, haben Sie das Recht, Ihre Einwilligung jederzeit zu widerrufen. Dieser Widerruf berührt jedoch nicht die Rechtmäßigkeit einer Verarbeitung, die auf der Grundlage Ihrer Einwilligung vor Ihrem Widerruf erfolgt ist. Sofern die Verarbeitung auf der Rechtsgrundlage eines berechtigten Interesses beruht, haben Sie außerdem das Recht, aus Gründen, die sich aus Ihrer besonderen Situation ergeben, jederzeit Widerspruch gegen die Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten einzulegen. Darüber hinaus haben Sie das Recht, der Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten für Zwecke des Direktmarketings jederzeit zu widersprechen. Hinsichtlich dieses Punktes gilt Artikel 21 der DSGVO/UK GDPR.

Sie können der Nutzung Ihrer E-Mail-Adresse zu Werbezwecken oder zur persönlichen Beratung bei der Registrierung oder später jederzeit widersprechen.

**4\. Offenlegung personenbezogener Daten**

Wir können die personenbezogenen Daten, die wir zu den oben beschriebenen Zwecken erfassen, zur Bereitstellung unserer Dienste, zur Beantwortung und Erfüllung Ihrer Anfragen, wie anderweitig von Ihnen angewiesen oder eingewilligt, sowie gegenüber folgenden Empfängern offenlegen:

* **Marken, verbundene Unternehmen und Tochtergesellschaften** . Wir können die von uns erfassten personenbezogenen Daten gegenüber unseren Marken, verbundenen Unternehmen und Tochtergesellschaften offenlegen.
    
* **Geschäftspartner** . Unter bestimmten Umständen kann TMG Partnerschaften mit anderen Unternehmen eingehen, um ihre Dienste anzubieten, insbesondere zur Ermöglichung bestimmter Programme oder spezieller Angebote, und wir können personenbezogene Daten gegenüber diesen Geschäftspartnern offenlegen.
    
* **Anbieter und Dienstleister** . Wir können die von uns erfassten personenbezogenen Daten gegenüber Anbietern und Dienstleistern offenlegen, die in unserem Auftrag Funktionen erbringen, z. B. IT- und Website-Hosting-Anbieter, Zahlungsdienstleister, Marketing- und Marktforschungsanbieter, Kundenbetreuungsunternehmen, Datenspeicherungsanbieter, Datenanalyseanbieter, Wirtschaftsprüfer, Berater und Bevollmächtigte sowie Rechtsbeistände.
    
* **Andere TMG-Benutzer** . Mit anderen Benutzern der Dienste im Zusammenhang mit bestimmten Funktionen, die sozialer Natur sind. Wenn Sie beispielsweise andere zur Nutzung unserer Dienste einladen oder wenn Sie Informationen über unsere öffentlichen, interaktiven Funktionen, Community-Foren oder Diskussionsblogs übermitteln oder zur Verfügung stellen, insbesondere wenn Sie Bewertungen oder Testimonials posten, können bestimmte personenbezogene Daten für andere Benutzer der Dienste verfügbar und über die Suchfunktion auffindbar sein. Wenn Sie beispielsweise an Pets teilnehmen, können andere Benutzer der Pets-Spielfunktion personenbezogene Daten wie Ihr Profilbild, Ihr Geschlecht, Ihren Wert, Ihr Bargeld, Ihre Besitztümer, Besitzverhältnisse und die Anzahl Ihrer Haustiere einsehen.
    
* **Externe Marketing- und Analyse-Anbieter** . Wir können Ihre personenbezogenen Daten, z. B. Geräte- und Browsingdaten sowie Aktivitäts- und Nutzungsdaten, auch an externe Anbieter von Marketing- und Datenanalysediensten sowie an andere Unternehmen weitergeben, die in unserem Auftrag Marketing-, Werbe-, Kampagnenmanagement- oder Analysedienste erbringen. Einen detaillierten Überblick über die einzelnen Empfänger finden Sie auf unserer Consent-Management-Plattform in der App.

Wir können Ihre personenbezogenen Daten auch in folgenden Fällen offenlegen:

* **Zur Unterstützung von Unternehmensübertragungen** . Wenn wir oder unsere verbundenen Unternehmen von einem anderen Unternehmen übernommen werden oder werden können, mit diesem fusionieren oder ein anderes Unternehmen in uns oder unsere verbundenen Unternehmen investiert, oder wenn einige unserer Vermögenswerte an ein anderes Unternehmen übertragen werden oder übertragen werden können, sei es im Rahmen eines Konkurs- oder Insolvenzverfahrens oder auf andere Weise, können wir die personenbezogenen Daten, die wir von Ihnen erfasst haben, in Übereinstimmung mit den geltenden Gesetzen gegenüber dem anderen Unternehmen offenlegen oder an dieses übertragen. Wir können auch bestimmte personenbezogene Daten gegenüber Kreditgebern, Wirtschaftsprüfern und externen Beratern, insbesondere Rechtsanwälten und Beratern, offenlegen, wenn dies vor dem Abschluss einer solchen Transaktion oder einer anderen Unternehmenstransaktion wie einer Finanzierung oder Umstrukturierung erforderlich ist.
    
* **Compliance und rechtliche Verpflichtungen** . Wir können personenbezogene Daten zudem gegenüber Dritten offenlegen, soweit dies nach geltendem Recht bzw. im Rahmen rechtlicher Verpflichtungen erforderlich ist. So können wir beispielsweise Informationen als Reaktion auf Vorladungen, gerichtliche Anordnungen und andere rechtmäßige Anfragen von Aufsichtsbehörden, Regierungsstellen und Strafverfolgungsbehörden offenlegen, insbesondere im Rahmen der nationalen Sicherheit oder der Strafverfolgung, oder wenn dies anderweitig gesetzlich vorgeschrieben oder im Rahmen eines Gerichtsverfahrens erforderlich ist. Darüber hinaus können wir ggf. die Namen der Gewinner von Preisausschreiben und Gewinnspielen in Übereinstimmung mit dem geltenden Recht offenlegen.
    
* **Sicherheit und Schutz der Rechte** . Sofern wir dies für notwendig halten, um die Dienste, unsere Rechte und unser Eigentum oder die Rechte, das Eigentum und die Sicherheit anderer zu schützen. So können wir beispielsweise personenbezogene Daten in folgenden Fällen offenlegen: (i) zur Verhinderung, Aufdeckung, Untersuchung und Reaktion auf Betrug, unbefugte Aktivitäten und unbefugten Zugriff, rechtswidrige Aktivitäten und Missbrauch der Dienste, (ii) in Situationen, in denen die Gesundheit, die Sicherheit oder die Rechte einer Person oder einer Drittpartei gefährdet sind, oder (iii) zur Durchsetzung, Aufdeckung, Untersuchung und Ergreifung von Maßnahmen bei Verstößen gegen unsere Geschäftsbedingungen.Wir können personenbezogene Daten zudem im Zusammenhang mit Rechtsstreitigkeiten und anderen rechtlichen Ansprüchen oder Verfahren, in die wir verwickelt sind, sowie für unsere internen Buchhaltungs-, Prüfungs-, Compliance-, Buchführungs- und Rechtsfunktionen offenlegen.
    
* **Sonstige Offenlegungen** . Wir können personenbezogene Daten auf andere, oben nicht beschriebene Weise offenlegen, sofern wir Sie darüber informieren oder Ihre Zustimmung dafür einholen, oder sofern dies anderweitig gesetzlich zulässig oder erforderlich ist.

Ungeachtet aller anderen Bestimmungen dieser Richtlinie können wir aggregierte, anonymisierte und andere Daten, die nicht zur Identifizierung einer natürlichen Person herangezogen werden können, im Zusammenhang mit unserem Geschäft und den Diensten für Qualitätskontrollen, Analysen, Forschung, Entwicklung und andere Zwecke verwenden und offenlegen. Sofern wir anonymisierte Daten (Daten, die nach vernünftigem Ermessen nicht mehr mit einer identifizierten oder identifizierbaren natürlichen Person, einem Haushalt oder einem persönlichen oder haushaltsgebundenen Gerät verknüpft sind oder verknüpft werden können) verwenden, offenlegen oder verarbeiten, werden wir die Informationen in anonymisierter Form aufbewahren und verwenden und nicht versuchen, die Anonymität der Daten wieder aufzuheben, außer um festzustellen, ob unsere Verfahren zur Anonymisierung gemäß den geltenden Datenschutzgesetzen ausreichend und angemessen sind.

**5\. Übermittlung personenbezogener Daten in Bezug auf Länder außerhalb des EWR/des Vereinigten Königreichs/der Schweiz**

Empfänger personenbezogener Daten können ihren Sitz außerhalb des EWR/des Vereinigten Königreichs/der Schweiz haben. Wenn personenbezogene Daten an Standorte außerhalb des EWR/des Vereinigten Königreichs/der Schweiz übermittelt werden (dies betrifft insbesondere Übermittlungen von uns in den USA als für die Verarbeitung Verantwortlicher im Geltungsbereich der DSGVO/der UK GDPR/des nDSG an Empfänger in den USA oder in anderen Ländern außerhalb des EWR/des Vereinigten Königreichs/der Schweiz, die nicht in den Geltungsbereich der DSGVO/der UK GDPR/des nDSG fallen), werden wir, soweit gesetzlich vorgeschrieben, sicherstellen, dass Ihre Datenschutzrechte angemessen geschützt sind, entweder weil die Europäische Kommission entschieden hat, dass das Land, in das personenbezogene Daten übermittelt werden, ein angemessenes Schutzniveau bietet (Art. 45 DSGVO/UK GDPR) oder die Übermittlung geeigneten Garantien unterliegt (z. B. Standarddatenschutzklauseln der Europäischen Union, die mit dem Empfänger vereinbart wurden) (Art. 46 DSGVO/UK GDPR), sofern nicht gemäß DSGVO/UK GDPR eine Ausnahme vorgesehen ist (Art. 49 DSGVO/UK GDPR). Darüber hinaus beabsichtigen wir, erforderlichenfalls mit den Empfängern zusätzliche Maßnahmen zu vereinbaren, um ein angemessenes Datenschutzniveau zu gewährleisten. Siehe auch Art. 16 f. nDSG bezüglich der Offenlegung von Personendaten außerhalb der Schweiz.

Gegebenenfalls schließen wir mit unseren Vertragspartnern auch ein entsprechendes „UK Addendum“ gemäß den Anforderungen des Information Commissioner's Office (ICO) und ein entsprechendes „CH-Addendum“ gemäß den Anforderungen des Eidgenössischen Datenschutz- und Öffentlichkeitsbeauftragten (EDÖB).

Kopien der angemessenen Sicherheitsvorkehrungen (soweit wir uns auf diese stützen) und eine Liste von Empfängern, die außerhalb des EWR/des Vereinigten Königreichs/der Schweiz ansässig sind, können unter [support@themeetgroup.com](mailto:support@themeetgroup.com) angefordert werden.Bitte beachten Sie, dass eine solche Kopie im erforderlichen Umfang geschwärzt werden kann, um den Schutz von Geschäftsgeheimnissen oder anderen vertraulichen Informationen zu gewährleisten.

**6\. Cookies, Targeting und Analysen**

Wir und unsere Drittanbieter verwenden Cookies, Pixel, lokale Speicherobjekte, Protokolldateien und andere Tracking-Mechanismen, um automatisch Browsing-, Aktivitäts-, Geräte- und andere ähnliche Informationen innerhalb unserer Dienste zu erfassen. Wir verwenden diese Daten, um zu analysieren und zu verstehen, wie Benutzer auf unsere Dienste zugreifen, sie nutzen und mit ihnen interagieren, um Bugs und Fehler in unseren Diensten zu identifizieren und zu beheben, um die Leistung unserer Dienste zu bewerten, zu sichern, zu schützen, zu optimieren und zu verbessern, sowie für Marketing- und Analysezwecke und zur Personalisierung von Inhalten in unseren Diensten. Abhängig von Ihrem Standort wird die Mehrzahl dieser Methoden nur eingesetzt, sofern Sie uns über unsere CMP in Ihren App-Einstellungen Ihre Einwilligung erteilt haben, wo Sie Ihre Einwilligung/Präferenzen in Bezug auf Cookies, zielgerichtete Werbung und andere ähnliche Tracking-Mechanismen innerhalb unserer Dienste verwalten können, siehe den nachstehenden Abschnitt 7. „Ihre Wahlmöglichkeiten zum Datenschutz“. Viele dieser Wahlmöglichkeiten sind browser- bzw. gerätespezifisch, was bedeutet, dass Sie die Einstellungen für alle Browser und Geräte, die Sie für den Zugriff auf unsere Dienste verwenden, einzeln vornehmen müssen. Außerdem müssen Sie, wenn Sie Cookies löschen oder blockieren, diese Einstellungen möglicherweise für jeden Browser und/oder jedes Gerät erneut vornehmen.

**Cookies** . „Cookies“ sind kleine Textdateien, die von einer besuchten Website auf dem Gerät eines Benutzers (z. B. einem Computer oder Smartphone) gespeichert werden. Cookies werden vom Server der Website erstellt und an den Browser des Benutzers gesendet, wo sie für spätere Zwecke gespeichert werden. Einige Cookies ermöglichen es uns, Ihnen die Navigation in unseren Diensten zu erleichtern, während andere beispielsweise verwendet werden, um einen schnelleren Anmeldevorgang zu ermöglichen, die Sicherheit und Leistung der Dienste zu unterstützen oder es uns zu ermöglichen, aggregierte und statistische Informationen über die Aktivitäten der Benutzer innerhalb der Dienste zu verfolgen.

**Pixel-Tags** . Pixel-Tags (manchmal auch als Zählpixel, Web Beacons oder Clear GIFs bezeichnet) sind winzige Grafiken mit einer eindeutigen Kennung, die ähnlich wie Cookies funktionieren. Während Cookies lokal auf Ihrem Gerät gespeichert werden, sind Pixel-Tags unsichtbar in Webseiten und Online-Inhalte eingebettet. Wir können diese in Verbindung mit unseren Diensten unter anderem dazu verwenden, die Aktivitäten der Benutzer zu verfolgen und uns die Verwaltung von Inhalten und die Erstellung von Nutzungsstatistiken zu erleichtern. Wir können diese auch in unseren E-Mails verwenden, um festzustellen, ob sie geöffnet oder weitergeleitet wurden, damit wir die Antwortquoten verfolgen und die Wirksamkeit unserer Mitteilungen messen können.

**Protokolldateien** . Wir können bestimmte Aktivitätsinformationen aus Protokolldateien erfassen. Protokolldateidaten werden automatisch erfasst, wenn Sie auf unsere Websites zugreifen. Wir zeichnen bestimmte Informationen aus diesen Protokolldateien auf, darunter Internetanfragen, IP-Adresse, Browsertyp und -version, Sprachinformationen, verweisende und verlassende URLs, angeklickte Links, aufgerufene Seiten und weitere ähnliche Informationen.

**Analysen von externen Anbietern** . Wir können automatisierte Geräte, Anwendungen und Tools wie Google Analytics verwenden, die von Drittunternehmen betrieben werden, um die Nutzung unserer Dienste auszuwerten. Diese Drittunternehmen können Cookies, Pixel und andere Tracking-Technologien verwenden, um Nutzungsdaten über unsere Dienste zu erfassen und uns Berichte und Metriken zur Verfügung zu stellen, anhand derer wir die Nutzung unserer Dienste bewerten und die Leistung und die Erfahrungen der Benutzer verbessern können. Weitere Informationen über die Datenschutzpraktiken von Google finden Sie in der Datenschutzerklärung von Google unter [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). Sie können auch das Browser-Add-on zur Deaktivierung von Google Analytics unter [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) herunterladen, um zu verhindern, dass Ihre Daten von Google Analytics verwendet werden. Eine Liste der von uns in dieser Hinsicht beauftragten Dritten finden Sie in unserer CMP unter Ihren App-Einstellungen.

**Werbung von externen Anbietern** . Wir arbeiten mit externen Werbenetzwerken, Marketingpartnern, Netzwerken für Werbung auf Mobilgeräten und weiteren („externe Werbeunternehmen“) zusammen, um Inhalte in unseren Diensten zu personalisieren und dort Werbung anzuzeigen sowie unsere Werbung auf Websites von Drittanbietern zu verwalten.Wir und diese externen Werbeunternehmen können Cookies, Pixel-Tags, SDKs (Software Development Kits) und andere Tools verwenden, um Informationen zum Surfen und anderen Aktivitäten innerhalb unserer Dienste (sowie auf Websites und Diensten von Drittanbietern) sowie IP-Adressen, eindeutige IDs, Cookie- und Werbe-IDs und andere Online-Kennungen zu erfassen. Wir und diese externen Werbeunternehmen verwenden diese Informationen, um Ihnen relevantere Werbung und Inhalte in unseren Diensten und auf Websites von Drittanbietern bereitzustellen und um den Erfolg dieser Werbung und dieser Inhalte zu bewerten. Eine Liste der externen Werbeunternehmen finden Sie in unserer CMP unter Ihren App-Einstellungen.

**Geräteübergreifende Nutzung** . Wir und unsere Drittanbieter können die Informationen, die wir über Sie erfassen (ob direkt von unseren Websites oder der Mobil-App, über Ihr(e) Gerät(e) oder aus Drittquellen), verwenden, um uns und unseren Drittanbietern zu helfen, andere von Ihnen verwendete Geräte zu identifizieren (z. B. ein Mobiltelefon, ein Tablet, einen anderen Computer usw.). Wir und unsere Drittanbieter können die geräteübergreifende Nutzung und andere Informationen, die wir über Sie in Erfahrung bringen, auch verwenden, um zielgerichtete Werbung zu schalten oder Inhalte innerhalb unserer Dienste zu personalisieren.

**Kundenlisten und Abgleich** . Wir können bestimmte Kundenlistendaten (wie z. B. Ihren Namen, Ihre E-Mail-Adresse und andere Kontaktangaben) an Dritte weitergeben oder diesen zur Verfügung stellen, damit wir Werbung und Inhalte auf Websites, Plattformen und Diensten Dritter gezielter an Sie richten können.In einigen Fällen können uns diese Dritten dabei helfen, unsere Kundenlisten mit zusätzlichen demografischen oder ähnlichen Informationen zu ergänzen, damit wir unsere Werbe- und Marketingkampagnen zielgerichteter gestalten können.

**7\. Ihre Wahlmöglichkeiten zum Datenschutz**

**Verwalten Ihrer Präferenzen** . Wir stellen Ihnen verschiedene Möglichkeiten zur Verfügung, Ihre Präferenzen und Datenschutzoptionen zu verwalten, wie unten beschrieben:

* **Konto und Profil** . Sie können einige der personenbezogenen Daten überprüfen und aktualisieren, die wir über Sie speichern, indem Sie sich bei Ihrem Konto anmelden und Ihre Konto- und Profilinformationen aktualisieren.
    
* **Marketing-Kommunikation** . Wir können Ihnen in regelmäßigen Abständen Werbe-E-Mails, Inhalte oder andere ähnliche Mitteilungen zusenden. Sie können sich von diesen Mitteilungen abmelden, indem Sie die Anweisungen in den betreffenden Mitteilungen befolgen. Wenn Sie sich gegen den Erhalt von Werbeinhalten entscheiden, können wir Ihnen dennoch weiterhin Mitteilungen über Ihr Konto oder die von Ihnen angeforderten oder erhaltenen Dienste zusenden. Zusätzlich können Sie Ihre Kommunikationspräferenzen in Ihren Konto- und Profileinstellungen verwalten.
    
* **Push-Benachrichtigungen** . Sie können die Art der Push-Benachrichtigungen, die Sie von uns erhalten, verwalten, indem Sie die Einstellungen Ihres Mobilgeräts oder die Einstellungen in unserer Mobil-App ändern. Dabei handelt es sich um Mitteilungen, die wir Ihnen im Rahmen der Vertragserfüllung zusenden, sowie um Werbeinformationen.

**Cookie- und Tracking-Präferenzen/zielgerichtete Werbung/Analysen** . Wir stellen Ihnen auch verschiedene Möglichkeiten zur Verfügung, Ihre Präferenzen in Bezug auf Cookies, zielgerichtete Werbung, Analysen und andere ähnliche Tracking-Mechanismen innerhalb unserer Dienste zu verwalten. Viele dieser Wahlmöglichkeiten sind browser- bzw. gerätespezifisch, was bedeutet, dass Sie die Einstellungen für alle Browser und Geräte, die Sie zum Zugriff auf unsere Dienste verwenden, einzeln vornehmen müssen.Außerdem müssen Sie, wenn Sie Cookies löschen oder blockieren, diese Einstellungen möglicherweise für jeden Browser und/oder jedes Gerät erneut vornehmen. Darüber hinaus bedeutet die Ablehnung von Cookies und Werbung nicht, dass Sie keine Werbeinhalte mehr von uns erhalten; entsprechend können Sie weiterhin allgemeine oder „kontextbezogene“ Werbung von uns erhalten.

* **Consent-Management-Plattform (CMP).** Um zu verhindern, dass Cookies oder andere nicht unbedingt erforderliche Tracking-Mechanismen Ihre Aktivitäten auf unseren Websites oder in unserer Mobil-App verfolgen, können Sie die Consent-Management-Plattform nutzen, die vor dem Einsatz der Cookies und Tracking-Mechanismen angezeigt wird. Eine einmal erteilte Einwilligung kann jederzeit mit Wirkung für die Zukunft widerrufen werden. Ausführlichere Informationen finden Sie in Abschnitt 15. „Zusätzliche Informationen zum Datenschutz für bestimmte Rechtsordnungen“, der zusätzliche Informationen über Datenschutzrechte für Einwohner bestimmter Rechtsgebiete enthält.
    
* **Cookie-Einstellungen** . Um zu verhindern, dass Cookies Ihre Aktivitäten auf unseren Websites oder Besuche über mehrere Websites hinweg verfolgen, können Sie über die Einstellungen Ihres Browsers bestimmte Cookies blockieren oder sich benachrichtigen lassen, wenn ein Cookie gesetzt wird.Sie können Cookies auch löschen. In der Hilfe-Funktion der Symbolleiste der meisten Browser erfahren Sie, wie Sie verhindern können, dass Ihr Gerät neue Cookies zulässt, wie Sie sich vom Browser benachrichtigen lassen können, wenn ein neues Cookie gesetzt wird, und wie Sie Cookies löschen können. Besucher unserer Websites, die Cookies deaktivieren, können zwar auf der Website surfen, einige Funktionen sind jedoch möglicherweise nicht verfügbar.
    
* **Browsersignale** . Wenn unsere Websites feststellen, dass Ihr Browser ein Opt-out-Signal sendet, wie z. B. ein „Global Privacy Control“-Signal (GPC-Signal), werden wir dieses Signal anwenden, um den betreffenden Browser auf Ihrem Gerät von Targeting-Cookies auf unseren Websites auszuschließen, soweit dies nach geltendem Recht erforderlich ist. Wenn Sie unsere Websites von einem anderen Gerät oder von einem anderen Browser auf demselben Gerät aufrufen, müssen Sie das GPC auch für diesen Browser und/oder dieses Gerät anwenden.
    
* **Branchenspezifische Wahlmöglichkeiten zur Anzeige von Werbung** . Sie können auch kontrollieren, wie teilnehmende externe Werbeunternehmen die Informationen verwenden, die sie über Ihre Besuche auf unseren Websites und denen von Dritten erfassen, um Ihnen relevantere zielgerichtete Werbung anzuzeigen. Weitere Informationen und Unterstützung in Bezug auf Web-Tracking-Mechanismen finden Sie unter [www.YourOnlineChoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/).

Einwohner bestimmter Rechtsgebiete haben unter Umständen zusätzliche Rechte in Bezug auf ihre personenbezogenen Daten, wie unten in Abschnitt 15. „Zusätzliche Informationen zum Datenschutz für bestimmte Rechtsordnungen“ dargelegt.

**8\. Aufbewahrungsdauer für personenbezogene Daten**

Wir speichern Ihre personenbezogenen Daten so lange, wie es zur Erfüllung der in Abschnitt 3. „Zwecke der Erfassung und Verarbeitung“ und Abschnitt 6. „Cookies, Targeting und Analysen“ genannten Zwecke erforderlich ist, oder solange wir ein berechtigtes Interesse an der weiteren Speicherung haben. In allen anderen Fällen löschen wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten, mit Ausnahme von Daten, die wir zur Einhaltung gesetzlicher Aufbewahrungsfristen (z. B. aus steuer- oder handelsrechtlichen Gründen, wie etwa im Zusammenhang mit der Rechnungslegung) aufbewahren müssen. Wir schränken die Verarbeitung personenbezogener Daten ein, die nur aufgrund einer Aufbewahrungspflicht aufbewahrt werden.

Informationen zur Speicherdauer von Cookies und anderen Tracking-Mechanismen finden Sie in unserer CMP unter Ihren App-Einstellungen.

**9\. Externe Links und Funktionen**

Unsere Dienste können Links zu Websites oder Funktionen Dritter enthalten oder bestimmte Verbindungen oder integrierte Dienste Dritter anbieten. Der Zugriff auf und die Nutzung von solchen verlinkten Websites oder Funktionen unterliegen nicht dieser Richtlinie, sondern den Datenschutzrichtlinien der betreffenden Drittparteien. Wir sind nicht verantwortlich für die Datenschutzmaßnahmen solcher Dritter, einschließlich der Erfassung, Verwendung und Weitergabe Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten durch diese Dritten. Sie sollten die Datenschutzrichtlinien und Nutzungsbedingungen dieser Dritten prüfen, bevor Sie derartige Websites besuchen oder derartige Funktionen nutzen.

**10\. Von Benutzern generierte Inhalte**

Wir können in Verbindung mit unseren Diensten öffentlich zugängliche interaktive Funktionen, Community-Foren oder Diskussionsblogs anbieten, über die Sie Informationen in Bezug auf die Dienste oder andere Themen von Interesse (z. B. Bewertungen, Testimonials und Fragen) austauschen können. Sie sollten sich darüber im Klaren sein, dass jegliche Mitteilungen, die Sie an solche interaktiven Funktionen der Dienste übermitteln oder dort einstellen, von anderen, einschließlich TMG-Benutzern und der Öffentlichkeit, eingesehen und über die Suchfunktion auffindbar sein können. Indem Sie Inhalte an solche öffentlich zugänglichen, interaktiven Funktionen übermitteln oder dort Beiträge veröffentlichen, nehmen Sie zur Kenntnis, dass Sie keinen Anspruch auf Privatsphäre oder Vertraulichkeit in Bezug auf die Inhalte haben, die Sie für solche Funktionen übermitteln, unabhängig davon, ob diese personenbezogene Daten über Sie enthalten oder nicht.

**11\. Sicherheit**

Wir haben angemessene Vorsichtsmaßnahmen getroffen, um die von uns erfassten Informationen vor Verlust, Missbrauch und unbefugtem Zugriff, Offenlegung, Änderung und Zerstörung zu schützen. Wir weisen Sie darauf hin, dass trotz unserer Bemühungen keine Datensicherheitsmaßnahmen die Sicherheit garantieren können.

**12\. Privatsphäre von Kindern**

Unsere Dienste sind nicht an Kinder gerichtet, und wir erfassen nicht wissentlich personenbezogene Daten von Kindern unter achtzehn (18) Jahren. Wenn wir erfahren, dass personenbezogene Daten von Personen unter 18 Jahren in den Diensten erfasst wurden, unternehmen wir die entsprechenden Schritte zur Löschung dieser Daten. Wenn Sie als Elternteil oder Erziehungsberechtigte(r) glauben, dass wir die Daten Ihres Kindes unter Verstoß gegen das geltende Recht erfasst haben, kontaktieren Sie uns bitte anhand der nachstehenden Kontaktangaben.

**13\. Änderungen an dieser Richtlinie**

Diese Richtlinie entspricht dem Stand des oben genannten Datums. Wir können diese Richtlinie von Zeit zu Zeit ändern, aktualisieren oder modifizieren, weshalb wir Sie bitten, sie regelmäßig zu überprüfen. Alle Aktualisierungen dieser Richtlinie werden hier veröffentlicht.Wenn wir Änderungen an dieser Richtlinie vornehmen, die sich wesentlich auf unsere Maßnahmen in Bezug auf unsere Verwendung der zuvor von Ihnen erfassten personenbezogenen Daten auswirken, werden wir uns bemühen, Sie darüber zu informieren, z. B. indem wir Ihnen eine E-Mail schicken oder einen auffälligen Hinweis auf unseren Websites, in unserer Mobil-App oder innerhalb der Dienste veröffentlichen.

**14\. Kontakt**

Wenn Sie Fragen oder Bedenken bezüglich dieser Richtlinie oder unserer Datenschutzmaßnahmen haben, können Sie uns eine E-Mail an [support@themeetgroup.com](mailto:support@themeetgroup.com) schicken oder uns unter folgender Adresse kontaktieren:

The Meet Group, Inc.

100 Union Square Drive

New Hope, PA 18938, USA

Unseren Datenschutzbeauftragten erreichen Sie unter:

ePrivacy GmbH vertreten durch Prof. Dr. Christoph Bauer, Große Bleichen 21, 20354 Hamburg, [privacy@themeetgroup.com](mailto:privacy@themeetgroup.com)

Für alle Anfragen bezüglich der Sicherheit Ihrer Daten wenden Sie sich bitte an unseren Datenschutzbeauftragten unter [privacy@themeetgroup.com](mailto:privacy@themeetgroup.com).

Unser EU-Vertreter gemäß Art. 27 DSGVO ist zu erreichen unter: ParshipMeet Holding GmbH, Speersort 10, 20095 Hamburg, E-Mail: [privacy@parshipmeet.com](mailto:privacy@parshipmeet.com)

Die Angaben unseres Vertreters für das Vereinigte Königreich gemäß Artikel 27 UK GDPR finden Sie in Abschnitt 15.B. „Zusätzliche Informationen für Einwohner des Vereinigten Königreichs“.

Die Angaben unseres Schweizer Vertreters gemäß Art. 14 nDSG (neues Schweizer Datenschutzgesetz) sind in Abschnitt 15.C. „Zusätzliche Informationen für Einwohner der Schweiz“ aufgeführt.

Treforma AG c/o MLL Legal; Grabenstrasse 25; 6340 Baar; Schweiz; [meetgroup@dsg-mll.com](mailto:meetgroup@dsg-mll.com)

**15\. Zusätzliche Informationen zum Datenschutz für bestimmte Rechtsordnungen**

Einwohner bestimmter Rechtsgebiete haben nach den geltenden Datenschutzgesetzen zusätzliche Rechte, wie in diesem Abschnitt beschrieben.

**A. DSGVO**

Wenn Sie in der Europäischen Union ansässig sind, haben Sie nach der DSGVO folgende Rechte, sofern die darin vorgesehenen rechtlichen Anforderungen erfüllt sind:

**Auskunftsrecht** – Sie können Auskunft über die Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten und eine Kopie der personenbezogenen Daten verlangen, die Gegenstand der Verarbeitung sind, sofern eine solche Kopie die Rechte und Freiheiten anderer nicht beeinträchtigt und keine andere Ausnahme vorliegt.

**Recht auf Berichtigung** – Sie können die Berichtigung von unrichtigen personenbezogenen Daten und/oder die Vervollständigung von unvollständigen Daten verlangen.

**Recht auf Löschung** – Sie können die Löschung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten verlangen, insbesondere wenn

* die personenbezogenen Daten in Bezug auf die Zwecke, für die sie erfasst oder anderweitig verarbeitet wurden, nicht mehr erforderlich sind,
    
* Sie Ihre Einwilligung, auf die sich die Verarbeitung stützte, widerrufen haben und es keine andere Rechtsgrundlage für die Verarbeitung gibt,
    
* Sie der Verarbeitung widersprochen haben, die auf der Rechtsgrundlage „berechtigte Interessen“ beruht, und es keine vorrangigen berechtigten Gründe für die Verarbeitung gibt, oder Sie der Verarbeitung zu Zwecken des Direktmarketings widersprochen haben,
    
* Ihre personenbezogenen Daten rechtswidrig verarbeitet wurden oder
    
* Ihre personenbezogenen Daten gelöscht werden müssen, um einer gesetzlichen Verpflichtung nachzukommen, der wir unterworfen sind.

Das Recht auf Löschung gilt jedoch insbesondere dann nicht, wenn die Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten zur Erfüllung einer rechtlichen Verpflichtung oder zur Geltendmachung, Ausübung oder Verteidigung von Rechtsansprüchen erforderlich ist.

**Recht auf Einschränkung der Verarbeitung** – Sie können die Einschränkung der Verarbeitung verlangen

* für den Zeitraum, in dem wir die Richtigkeit Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten überprüfen, wenn Sie die Richtigkeit der personenbezogenen Daten bestritten haben,
    
* wenn Sie im Falle einer rechtswidriger Verarbeitung anstelle der Löschung der Daten die Einschränkung der Verarbeitung verlangen,
    
* wenn wir die personenbezogenen Daten nicht mehr benötigen, Sie die Daten aber zur Geltendmachung, Ausübung oder Verteidigung von Rechtsansprüchen benötigen, oder
    
* wenn Sie der Verarbeitung auf der Rechtsgrundlage „berechtigte Interessen“ widersprochen haben, solange noch nicht geprüft wurde, ob unsere berechtigten Gründe Vorrang vor Ihren Interessen, Rechten und Freiheiten haben.

**Recht auf Datenübertragbarkeit** – Sie können verlangen, Ihre personenbezogenen Daten, die Sie uns zur Verfügung gestellt haben, in einem strukturierten, gängigen und maschinenlesbaren Format zu erhalten und diese Daten ohne Behinderung durch uns an einen anderen Verantwortlichen zu übermitteln, sofern die Verarbeitung auf einer Einwilligung oder der Erfüllung eines Vertrags beruht und die Verarbeitung mithilfe automatisierter Verfahren erfolgt; in diesen Fällen können Sie auch beantragen, dass die personenbezogenen Daten direkt an einen anderen Verantwortlichen übermittelt werden, sofern dies technisch umsetzbar ist.

Darüber hinaus haben Sie folgende Rechte:

**Recht auf Widerruf der Einwilligung –** Sie können Ihre Einwilligung jederzeit mit Wirkung für die Zukunft widerrufen, wenn die Verarbeitung auf Ihrer Einwilligung beruht, ohne dass die Rechtmäßigkeit der auf der Einwilligung beruhenden Verarbeitung vor deren Widerruf berührt wird.

**Widerspruchsrecht –**

**Sie haben das Recht, aus Gründen, die sich auf Ihre besondere Situation beziehen, jederzeit Widerspruch gegen die Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten einzulegen, die auf unserem berechtigten Interesse oder dem eines Dritten beruht (Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO). Wir verarbeiten Ihre personenbezogenen Daten dann nicht mehr zu dem Zweck, gegen den Sie Widerspruch eingelegt haben, es sei denn, wir können triftige Gründe für die Verarbeitung nachweisen, die Vorrang vor Ihren Interessen, Rechten und Freiheiten haben, oder die Verarbeitung erfolgt zum Zweck der Geltendmachung, Ausübung oder Verteidigung von Rechtsansprüchen.**

**Darüber hinaus haben Sie das Recht, der Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten zu Zwecken des Direktmarketings jederzeit zu widersprechen. Wenn Sie der Verarbeitung zu Zwecken des Direktmarketings widersprechen, verarbeiten wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten nicht mehr zu diesen Zwecken.**

* * *

**Beschwerderecht –** Sie können bei einer Aufsichtsbehörde, insbesondere in dem Mitgliedstaat Ihres gewöhnlichen Aufenthalts, Ihres Arbeitsplatzes oder des Ortes des mutmaßlichen Verstoßes, Beschwerde einlegen, wenn Sie der Ansicht sind, dass die Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten gegen die DSGVO verstößt.

Die für uns zuständige Datenschutzbehörde ist:

Freie und Hansestadt Hamburg, Der Hamburgische Beauftragte für Datenschutz und Informationsfreiheit, Ludwig-Erhard-Str. 22, 20459 Hamburg, E-Mail: [mailbox@datenschutz.hamburg.de](mailto:mailbox@datenschutz.hamburg.de)

**B. UK GDPR**

Wenn Sie im Vereinigten Königreich ansässig sind, haben Sie nach der UK GDPR und den Datenschutzgesetzen bestimmte Rechte. Gültigkeit und Umfang der Rechte können jeweils von den konkreten Umständen abhängen. Zur Ausübung dieser Rechte wenden Sie sich bitte an die nachstehenden Kontaktangaben. Die Rechte sind:

**Ihr Recht auf Information** – Sie haben das Recht, prägnante, transparente, verständliche und leicht zugängliche Informationen über Ihre personenbezogenen Daten und deren Verwendung durch uns zu erhalten. Mit dieser Richtlinie möchten wir Ihnen diese Informationen zur Verfügung stellen. Sollten Sie jedoch weitere Fragen oder Bedenken haben, wenden Sie sich bitte an die nachstehenden Kontaktangaben.

**Ihr Auskunftsrecht** – Sie haben das Recht, von uns Kopien Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten zu verlangen. Dieses Recht gilt immer, unterliegt jedoch bestimmten Ausnahmeregelungen, weshalb Sie möglicherweise nicht immer alle von Ihnen angeforderten Auskünfte erhalten. Ein derartiger Antrag auf Auskunft über Ihre personenbezogenen Daten wird als Data Subject Access Request (DSAR) bezeichnet. Wenn wir einen DSAR von Ihnen erhalten, müssen wir Sie möglicherweise nach Ausweispapieren fragen, um Ihre Identität zu überprüfen.

**Ihr Recht auf Berichtigung** – Sie haben das Recht, uns aufzufordern, personenbezogene Daten zu berichtigen, die Ihrer Meinung nach unrichtig sind. Sie haben auch das Recht, uns aufzufordern, Informationen zu vervollständigen, die Ihrer Meinung nach unvollständig sind.

**Ihr Recht auf Löschung** – Sie haben unter bestimmten Umständen das Recht, uns aufzufordern, Ihre personenbezogenen Daten zu löschen. Wir haben das Recht, einem Antrag auf Löschung nicht nachzukommen, wenn wir die personenbezogenen Daten aus einem der folgenden Gründe verarbeiten:

* Zur Ausübung des Rechts auf freie Meinungsäußerung und Information.
    
* Um einer rechtlichen Verpflichtung nachzukommen.
    
* Zur Wahrnehmung einer Aufgabe im öffentlichen Interesse oder zur Ausübung einer amtlichen Befugnis.
    
* Für Archivierungszwecke im öffentlichen Interesse, wissenschaftliche Forschung, geschichtliche Forschung oder statistische Zwecke.
    
* Zur Geltendmachung oder Verteidigung von Rechtsansprüchen.

**Ihr Recht auf Einschränkung der Verarbeitung** – Sie haben unter bestimmten Umständen das Recht, uns aufzufordern, die Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten einzuschränken. In diesem Fall bleiben die Daten bei uns gespeichert, werden aber nicht weiterverarbeitet. Dieses Recht stellt eine Alternative zum Recht auf Löschung dar. Sie können das Recht auf Einschränkung der Verarbeitung ausüben, sofern eine der folgenden Bedingungen zutrifft:

* Die Richtigkeit der personenbezogenen Daten wird bestritten.
    
* Die Verarbeitung der personenbezogenen Daten ist rechtswidrig.
    
* Wir benötigen die personenbezogenen Daten nicht mehr für die Verarbeitung, die personenbezogenen Daten werden jedoch im Rahmen eines Rechtsverfahrens benötigt.
    
* Das Widerspruchsrecht wurde ausgeübt und die Verarbeitung wird eingeschränkt, bis eine Entscheidung über den Status der Verarbeitung getroffen wurde.

**Ihr Recht auf Widerspruch gegen die Verarbeitung – Sie haben unter bestimmten Umständen das Recht, der Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten zu widersprechen, insbesondere der Verarbeitung zu Zwecken des Direktmarketings. Sie können auch Widerspruch einlegen, wenn die Verarbeitung auf der Grundlage unserer berechtigten Interessen (oder denen eines Dritten) erfolgt. Wir verarbeiten Ihre personenbezogenen Daten dann nicht mehr zu dem Zweck, gegen den Sie Widerspruch eingelegt haben, es sei denn, wir können triftige Gründe für die Verarbeitung nachweisen, die Vorrang vor Ihren Interessen, Rechten und Freiheiten haben, oder die Verarbeitung erfolgt zum Zweck der Geltendmachung, Ausübung oder Verteidigung von Rechtsansprüchen.**

**Ihr Recht auf Datenübertragbarkeit** – Dabei handelt es sich um Ihr Recht, Ihre personenbezogenen Daten in einem strukturierten, gängigen und maschinenlesbaren Format zu erhalten, das jedoch nur gilt, sofern wir Informationen auf der Rechtsgrundlage Ihrer Einwilligung oder zur Erfüllung eines Vertrags verarbeiten und die Verarbeitung automatisiert ist.

**Recht auf Widerruf der Einwilligung –** Sie können Ihre Einwilligung jederzeit mit Wirkung für die Zukunft widerrufen, wenn die Verarbeitung auf Ihrer Einwilligung beruht, ohne dass die Rechtmäßigkeit der auf der Einwilligung beruhenden Verarbeitung vor deren Widerruf berührt wird.

**Kontaktangaben**

Zur Ausübung Ihrer Rechte oder bei Fragen zur Verwendung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten durch uns nutzen Sie bitte die Angaben unter „Kontakt“. Bitte achten Sie auch darauf, dass Sie dabei ausreichende Angaben machen, damit wir Sie eindeutig identifizieren können.

Wir weisen darauf hin, dass wir einen für das Vereinigte Königreich zuständigen Vertreter ernannt haben, den Sie in unserem Namen gemäß Art. 27 UK GDPR kontaktieren können: eHarmony UK Ltd., 6-10 Great Portland Street, London W1W 8QL, Großbritannien

**Übermittlung personenbezogener Daten außerhalb des Vereinigten Königreichs**

Einzelheiten zum Schutz und zu den Sicherheitsvorkehrungen, die bei Übermittlungen Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten außerhalb des Vereinigten Königreichs gelten, entnehmen Sie bitte dem vorstehenden Abschnitt 5. „Übermittlung personenbezogener Daten in Bezug auf Länder außerhalb des EWR/des Vereinigten Königreichs/der Schweiz“.

**Recht, eine Beschwerde bei einer Aufsichtsbehörde einzureichen**

Sie haben das Recht, eine Beschwerde bei einer Datenschutzbehörde einzureichen.

Sie können sich an die britische Datenschutzbehörde, das Information Commissioner's Office, wenden: Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF, Telefonnummer: + 44 (0) 303 123 1113, E-Mail-Adresse: [casework@ico.org.uk](mailto:casework@ico.org.uk).

**C. Schweizerisches Datenschutzrecht**

**Ihr Auskunftsrecht** – Sie haben das Recht, von uns Kopien Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten zu verlangen. Dieses Recht gilt immer, unterliegt jedoch bestimmten Ausnahmeregelungen, weshalb Sie möglicherweise nicht immer alle von Ihnen angeforderten Auskünfte erhalten. Ein derartiger Antrag auf Auskunft über Ihre personenbezogenen Daten wird als Data Subject Access Request (DSAR) bezeichnet.

**Ihr Recht auf Berichtigung** – Sie haben das Recht, uns aufzufordern, personenbezogene Daten zu berichtigen, die Ihrer Meinung nach unrichtig sind. Sie haben auch das Recht, uns aufzufordern, Informationen zu vervollständigen, die Ihrer Meinung nach unvollständig sind.

**Ihr Recht auf Löschung** – Sie haben unter bestimmten Umständen das Recht, uns aufzufordern, Ihre personenbezogenen Daten zu löschen. Wir haben das Recht, einem Antrag auf Löschung nicht nachzukommen, wenn wir die personenbezogenen Daten aus einem der folgenden Gründe verarbeiten:

* Zur Ausübung des Rechts auf freie Meinungsäußerung und Information.
    
* Um einer rechtlichen Verpflichtung nachzukommen.
    
* Zur Wahrnehmung einer Aufgabe im öffentlichen Interesse oder zur Ausübung einer amtlichen Befugnis.
    
* Für Archivierungszwecke im öffentlichen Interesse, wissenschaftliche Forschung, geschichtliche Forschung oder statistische Zwecke.
    
* Zur Geltendmachung oder Verteidigung von Rechtsansprüchen.

**Ihr Recht auf Einschränkung der Verarbeitung** – Sie haben unter bestimmten Umständen das Recht, uns aufzufordern, die Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten einzuschränken. In diesem Fall bleiben die Daten bei uns gespeichert, werden aber nicht weiterverarbeitet. Dieses Recht stellt eine Alternative zum Recht auf Löschung dar. Sie können das Recht auf Einschränkung der Verarbeitung ausüben, sofern eine der folgenden Bedingungen zutrifft:

* Die Richtigkeit der personenbezogenen Daten wird bestritten.
    
* Die Verarbeitung der personenbezogenen Daten ist rechtswidrig.
    
* Wir benötigen die personenbezogenen Daten nicht mehr für die Verarbeitung, die personenbezogenen Daten werden jedoch im Rahmen eines Rechtsverfahrens benötigt.
    
* Das Widerspruchsrecht wurde ausgeübt und die Verarbeitung wird eingeschränkt, bis eine Entscheidung über den Status der Verarbeitung getroffen wurde.

**Ihr Recht auf Widerspruch gegen die Verarbeitung** – Sie haben unter bestimmten Umständen das Recht, der Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten zu widersprechen. Sie können auch Widerspruch einlegen, wenn die Verarbeitung für eine Aufgabe erfolgt, die im öffentlichen Interesse, in Ausübung einer Ihnen übertragenen offiziellen Befugnis oder in unserem berechtigten Interesse (oder dem eines Dritten) durchgeführt wird.

**Ihr Recht auf Widerspruch gegen Direktmarketing** – Sie können auch jederzeit der Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten zu Werbezwecken widersprechen („Widerspruch gegen Werbung“). Bitte beachten Sie, dass es aus organisatorischen Gründen zu Überschneidungen zwischen Ihrem Widerruf und der Verwendung Ihrer Daten im Rahmen einer bereits laufenden Kampagne kommen kann.

**Ihr Recht auf Datenübertragbarkeit** – Dieses Recht gilt nur, sofern wir Informationen auf der Rechtsgrundlage Ihrer Einwilligung oder zur Erfüllung eines Vertrags verarbeiten und die Verarbeitung automatisiert ist.

Zur Ausübung Ihrer Rechte nutzen Sie bitte die Angaben unter „Kontakt“. Bitte achten Sie auch darauf, dass Sie dabei ausreichende Angaben machen, damit wir Sie eindeutig identifizieren können.

**Kontaktangaben**

Zur Ausübung Ihrer Rechte oder bei Fragen zur Verwendung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten durch uns nutzen Sie bitte die Angaben unter „Kontakt“. Bitte achten Sie auch darauf, dass Sie dabei ausreichende Angaben machen, damit wir Sie eindeutig identifizieren können.

Wir weisen darauf hin, dass wir einen zuständigen Vertreter gemäß Art. 14 nDSG (neues Schweizer Datenschutzgesetz) ernannt haben: Treforma AG c/o MLL Legal; Grabenstrasse 25; 6340 Baar; Schweiz; [meetgroup@dsg-mll.com](mailto:meetgroup@dsg-mll.com)

**Übermittlung personenbezogener Daten außerhalb der Schweiz**

Einzelheiten zum Schutz und zu den Sicherheitsvorkehrungen, die bei Übermittlungen Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten außerhalb der Schweiz gelten, entnehmen Sie bitte dem vorstehenden Abschnitt 5. „Übermittlung personenbezogener Daten in Bezug auf Länder außerhalb des EWR/des Vereinigten Königreichs/der Schweiz“.

**Recht, eine Beschwerde bei einer Aufsichtsbehörde einzureichen**

Sie haben das Recht, eine Beschwerde bei einer Datenschutzbehörde einzureichen.

Sie können sich an die zuständige Datenschutzaufsichtsbehörde in der Schweiz wenden. Zuständig ist:

Der Eidgenössische Datenschutz- und Öffentlichkeitsbeauftragte (EDÖB).

Diesen können Sie kontaktieren unter:

[https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/de/home/deredoeb/kontakt/kontaktformular\_bgoe.html](https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/de/home/deredoeb/kontakt/kontaktformular_bgoe.html)

**The Meet Group Inc.**

Politique de respect de la vie privée pour les utilisateurs résidant dans l'Espace économique européen ou au Royaume-Uni
========================================================================================================================

_Dernière mise à jour : October 8, 2024_

The Meet Group, Inc. ses marques, ses sociétés affiliées et ses filiales se soucient de votre vie privée. La présente Politique de respect de la vie privée (« **Politique** ») décrit la façon dont The Meet Group, Inc. (« **TMG** », « **nous** », « **notre** » ou « **nos** ») collecte, utilise, divulgue et traite les données à caractère personnel (également appelées informations personnelles dans certaines juridictions) décrites dans la présente Politique, ainsi que vos droits et vos options en ce qui concerne ces données à caractère personnel.

Pour en savoir plus sur vos options en matière de protection de la vie privée concernant vos données à caractère personnel, veuillez consulter la clause 7. Vos options en matière de protection de la vie privée, ainsi que la clause 15. Informations supplémentaires sur la protection de la vie privée dans certaines juridictions, qui comprend des informations supplémentaires sur les droits en matière de protection de la vie privée pour les personnes résidant dans certaines juridictions.

Si vous résidez dans l'UE ou dans l'Espace économique européen (EEE), veuillez vous reporter au paragraphe 15.A. Informations complémentaires pour les résidents de l'UE/EEE concernant vos droits en vertu du Règlement général sur la protection des données (« RGPD »).

Si vous résidez au Royaume-Uni, veuillez vous reporter au paragraphe 15.B.Informations complémentaires pour les résidents du Royaume-Uni concernant vos droits en vertu du Règlement général sur la protection des données tel qu'incorporé dans le droit britannique en vertu de la clause 3 de la loi de 2018 sur l'Union européenne (retrait) du Royaume-Uni (« RGPD du Royaume-Uni »).

Si vous résidez en Suisse, veuillez vous reporter au paragraphe 15.C.Informations complémentaires pour les résidents suisses concernant vos droits en vertu de la nouvelle loi suisse sur la protection des données (« nLPD »).

Lorsque vous créez un profil sur l'un de nos Services, certaines de vos données à caractère personnel comme le nom d'utilisateur, le nom, l'âge, le genre et l'orientation sexuelle, conformément à vos paramètres de protection de la vie privée, peuvent être visibles également par les utilisateurs du Service concerné et de nos autres Services, ainsi que d'autres applications dont nous sommes propriétaires et d'autres applications et sites web qui ne nous appartiennent pas et avec lesquels nous partageons notre plateforme live. Ces autres utilisateurs résident dans le monde entier. Pour obtenir une liste de nos partenaires live actuels, cliquez [ici](https://talent.tagged.com/partner-policy-tagged.html).

Votre utilisation de nos Services est soumise à nos [Conditions générales](https://secure.tagged.com/terms_of_service.html), y compris les conditions applicables aux limitations des dommages et à la résolution des litiges.

**Table des matières**

1. Champ d'application
    
2. Données à caractère personnel collectées
    
3. Finalités de la collecte et du traitement
    
4. Divulgation des données à caractère personnel
    
5. Transferts de données à caractère personnel dans le cadre de pays situés en dehors de l'Espace économique européen (EEE), du Royaume-Uni et de la Suisse
    
6. Cookies, ciblage et analyses
    
7. Vos options en matière de protection de la vie privée
    
8. Durée de stockage des données à caractère personnel
    
9. Liens et fonctionnalités externes
    
10. Contenu généré par les Utilisateurs
    
11. Sécurité
    
12. Protection de la vie privée des enfants
    
13. Modifications de la présente Politique
    
14. Contacte-nous
    
15. Informations supplémentaires sur la protection de la vie privée dans certaines juridictions

**1\. Champ d'application**

Sauf indication contraire mentionnée ci-dessous, la présente Politique s'applique aux données à caractère personnel que TMG collecte et traite en rapport avec : les visiteurs de notre site web, sur lequel la présente Politique est disponible, y compris n'importe lequel de nos sites web qui renvoie à la présente Politique ou la publie (les « **Sites** ») ; les individus qui téléchargent et utilisent notre application mobile (« **Application mobile** », par ex. l'application Tagged ou l'application Pets) ; les individus qui s'inscrivent ou participent à nos événements, enquêtes, recherches, promotions et tirages au sort organisés par nous ; et les individus qui communiquent ou interagissent de toute autre manière avec nous ou avec les services disponibles via nos Sites, notre Application mobile ou d'autres services en ligne (collectivement dénommés les « **Services** »).

**2\. Données à caractère personnel collectées**

Comme décrit ci-dessous, nous pouvons collecter des données à caractère personnel directement auprès de vous, auprès de sources tierces et automatiquement par le biais de votre utilisation de nos Services.

**Données à caractère personnel collectées directement auprès de vous** . Bien que les données à caractère personnel que nous collectons varient en fonction de votre utilisation de nos Services et de nos interactions avec vous, nous pouvons, de manière générale, collecter directement auprès de vous les catégories de données à caractère personnel suivantes :

* **Coordonnées** . Lorsque vous nous contactez, y compris si vous nous envoyez un message ou si vous vous inscrivez pour en savoir plus sur nos Services, nous pouvons collecter votre nom, votre adresse e-mail, votre numéro de téléphone, ou toute autre information d'identification, ainsi que votre message, la nature de votre demande, et toute autre information que vous choisissez de nous fournir.
    
* **Informations sur le Compte et le Profil** . Lorsque vous créez un compte dans le cadre de nos Services (par exemple, un compte Tagged), nous pouvons collecter votre nom, votre adresse e-mail, votre numéro de téléphone, votre adresse (par exemple, votre code postal), votre nom d'utilisateur et votre mot de passe, votre date de naissance, votre genre, votre orientation sexuelle, votre image et votre photo de profil, votre adresse de facturation, ainsi que toute autre information fournie dans le cadre de la création ou de la gestion de votre compte, ou que vous nous transmettez via votre compte.

Si vous avez choisi de vous connecter via des fournisseurs tiers tels que Facebook ou Apple ou également par SMS, vous n'aurez pas à saisir d'adresse e-mail ou de mot de passe au cours de la procédure d'inscription. Les utilisateurs accèdent ensuite à notre Service en utilisant l'adresse e-mail fournie et le mot de passe choisi (identifiants de connexion), ou alternativement, en utilisant les identifiants de connexion du fournisseur tiers.

**Inscription via Facebook (« connexion via Facebook »)**

Nous proposons une authentification unique via Facebook. Vous pouvez ainsi vous inscrire via votre compte Facebook. Si vous utilisez cette fonction, nous recevons et traitons les données d'authentification suivantes de Facebook pour l'inscription : votre adresse e-mail, votre nom de profil, votre genre, votre date de naissance et la photo de profil que vous y avez stockée. Les données sont transférées à cet égard.

Lorsque vous vous connectez à notre site web ou à notre application via Facebook, Facebook collecte également des données à partir de scripts tiers, les traite à des fins d'analyse pour Facebook ou les transmet à des tiers. La Politique de respect de la vie privée de Facebook indique les données qui peuvent être collectées lorsque vous utilisez le système de connexion via Facebook.Il s'agit notamment des données relatives à votre appareil, à votre utilisation de notre Service, aux sites web que vous avez consultés et aux publicités que vous avez visionnées. Malheureusement, vous ne pouvez techniquement pas vous opposer à ce traitement dans le cadre de notre Service. Si vous ne souhaitez pas que Facebook collecte des données vous concernant en rapport avec votre utilisation de notre offre en ligne et les utilise à ses propres fins, vous ne devez pas utiliser la connexion via Facebook.

Vous pouvez à tout moment dissocier votre compte Tagged de votre compte Facebook. Dans ce cas, vous devrez nous fournir les données d'accès susmentionnées.

Pour en savoir plus sur l'objet et le champ d'application de la collecte, du traitement ultérieur et de l'utilisation de vos données par Facebook, ainsi que sur vos droits et options de paramétrage pour la protection de vos données, veuillez consulter la politique de confidentialité de Facebook : [http://www.facebook.com/policy.php](http://www.facebook.com/policy.php).

**Inscription/connexion via Google**

Si vous utilisez un appareil Android, vous avez la possibilité de vous inscrire ou de vous connecter à notre Service via votre compte Google. Dans ce cas, Google Ireland Limited, Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Irlande (« Google ») nous fournira les données nécessaires à l'inscription ou à la connexion (adresse e-mail, nom, identifiant du compte Google et photo de profil).

Nous n'avons aucun contrôle sur le champ d'application des données collectées par Google dans le cadre d'une connexion via Google. Si vous ne souhaitez pas que Google collecte des données vous concernant en rapport avec votre utilisation de notre offre en ligne et les utilise à ses propres fins, vous ne devez pas utiliser la connexion via Google.

Pour en savoir plus sur l'objet et le champ d'application de la collecte, du traitement et de l'utilisation de vos données par Google, ainsi que sur vos droits et options de paramétrage pour la protection de vos données, veuillez consulter les règles de confidentialité de Google : [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

**Inscription/connexion via Se connecter avec Apple**

Si vous utilisez un appareil iOS, nous vous offrons la possibilité de vous inscrire ou de vous connecter à notre Service via Apple. Si vous choisissez cette option, Apple Inc, One Apple Park Way, Cupertino, California, USA, 95014 (« Apple ») nous fournira les informations que vous avez sélectionnées et qui sont nécessaires à l'inscription ou à la connexion (par exemple, l'adresse e-mail générée par Apple, le nom).

Nous n'avons aucun contrôle sur le champ d'application des données collectées par Apple dans le cadre d'une connexion via Apple. Si vous ne souhaitez pas qu'Apple collecte des données vous concernant en rapport avec votre utilisation de notre offre en ligne et les utilise à ses propres fins, vous ne devez pas utiliser la connexion via Apple.

Pour en savoir plus sur l'objet et le champ d'application de la collecte, du traitement et de l'utilisation de vos données par Apple, ainsi que sur vos droits et options de paramétrage pour la protection de vos données, veuillez consulter la politique de confidentialité d'Apple : [https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/en/sign-in-with-apple/](https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/en/sign-in-with-apple/).

**Lors de l'inscription/la connexion via l'authentification par téléphone**

Lorsque vous vous inscrivez/connectez via l'authentification par téléphone, nous vous proposons de vous authentifier à l'aide de votre numéro de téléphone portable, que vous devez donc nous communiquer. Nous vous enverrons alors un SMS contenant un code de vérification que vous devrez saisir dans l'application pour finaliser le processus d'inscription. Lorsque vous souhaitez vous connecter, nous vous envoyons un SMS contenant un code que vous pouvez utiliser pour vous connecter à votre compte. Il y aura en outre un processus de vérification. Ce service est fourni par Sinch America Inc, une société du Delaware, Legal Department, 3500 Lenox Rd NE, Ste. 1875, Atlanta, GA 30326, Georgia, USA

et est disponible uniquement si vous nous avez donné votre accord préalable.

Pour en savoir plus sur l'objet et le champ d'application du traitement de vos données par Sinch, veuillez consulter la politique de confidentialité de Sinch : [https://www.sinch.com/privacy-notice/](https://www.sinch.com/privacy-notice/)

* **Achats, paiements et récompenses** . Lorsque vous effectuez un achat ou un paiement par le biais de nos Services (par exemple, dans le cadre de notre jeu Pets), nous pouvons collecter des informations telles que le type de paiement, les informations concernant la carte de paiement, la facturation, l'achat et toute autre information financière ou commerciale nécessaire pour faciliter l'utilisation de nos Services.
    
* **Communications et interactions** . Lorsque vous envoyez un e-mail, appelez, ou communiquez ou interagissez autrement avec nous ou avec d'autres utilisateurs de TMG, y compris si vous vous inscrivez à nos listes de diffusion, remplissez des formulaires disponibles sur nos Sites ou notre Application mobile, interagissez avec nos pages de réseaux sociaux, publiez un avis ou un témoignage, envoyez du contenu dans tout groupe de discussion en ligne, ou saisissez autrement des informations dans des champs de commentaires destinés au public, des blogs ou des forums communautaires parrainés par ou affiliés à TMG, nous pouvons collecter, recevoir et conserver des enregistrements de vos coordonnées, communications et interactions, de vos publications ou envois, ainsi que de nos réponses, le cas échéant.
    
* **Informations promotionnelles** . Si vous acceptez de recevoir des communications marketing de notre part, nous pouvons collecter votre nom, votre adresse e-mail, votre numéro de téléphone, vos préférences et, le cas échéant, des informations sur votre compte et votre profil, y compris les Services et fonctionnalités que vous utilisez. Si vous participez à des activités spéciales, à des offres, à des programmes ou à des promotions proposés par nous, nous pouvons également collecter certaines coordonnées, votre âge et toute autre information requise par la loi. Si vous gagnez une promotion, nous pouvons également être amenés à collecter certaines informations fiscales et/ou des renonciations et des décharges, en fonction du prix.
    
* **Réponses et feedback** . Si vous participez à des enquêtes, à des questionnaires ou à des activités ou initiatives de recherche menées par nous, par exemple à des fins de satisfaction des utilisateurs ou à d'autres fins similaires, nous pouvons être amenés à collecter vos réponses et votre feedback, ainsi que toute autre information que vous choisissez de fournir.
    
* **Événements et détails des inscriptions** . Nous pouvons également collecter des données à caractère personnel relatives à votre participation à nos événements ainsi qu'à d'autres demandes que vous nous soumettez en rapport avec nos Services. Par exemple, si vous vous inscrivez ou assistez à un événement que nous organisons ou sponsorisons, nous pouvons collecter des informations relatives à votre inscription et à votre participation à cet événement.
    
* **Préférences et autres demandes** . Nous pouvons également collecter des informations sur vos préférences, y compris vos préférences en matière de communication et d'utilisation de nos Services, ainsi que toute autre préférence ou demande que vous nous communiquez lorsque vous interagissez avec nous.

En règle générale, vous n'êtes pas tenu de nous communiquer vos données à caractère personnel. Toutefois, l'utilisation de certains Services ou de certains aspects de nos Services peut nécessiter la fourniture de données à caractère personnel, par exemple la création d'un compte Tagged. Si tel est le cas, nous vous en informerons. Si vous ne souhaitez pas nous fournir les informations requises, vous ne pourrez malheureusement pas utiliser le Service concerné.

**Données à caractère personnel collectées auprès de tiers** . Nous pouvons également collecter et recevoir certaines données à caractère personnel vous concernant à partir de sources tierces, telles que des partenaires commerciaux, notamment lors d'achats sur les boutiques d'applications, d'autres utilisateurs de TMG, des fournisseurs de services d'analyse de données et de marketing, des systèmes d'exploitation et des plateformes de réseaux sociaux, notamment lors de l'utilisation des fonctions de connexion décrites ci-dessus. En outre, nous pouvons collecter les informations suivantes à partir de sources tierces :

* **Informations provenant de réseaux sociaux et liées à l'inscription à des plateformes** . Lors de l'utilisation de nos Services, vous pouvez choisir de partager des informations ou du contenu, de vous connecter ou de vous inscrire aux Services via diverses plateformes de réseaux sociaux, des services de réseaux sociaux ou d'autres fonctionnalités ou services intégrés de tiers. Lorsque vous vous connectez à nos Services en utilisant vos comptes de réseaux sociaux ou d'autres services et fonctionnalités intégrés similaires, nous pouvons collecter ou recevoir des données à caractère personnel vous concernant que vous avez fournies à ce compte de réseau social, à ce service ou à cette fonctionnalité. Par exemple, nous pouvons collecter des informations à partir de votre compte et de votre profil, telles que votre nom, votre adresse e-mail, votre identifiant, votre photo de profil, votre liste d'amis et d'autres informations similaires disponibles sur votre profil. Vous devriez vérifier vos paramètres relatifs à la vie privée sur chaque plateforme, fonctionnalité ou service intégré de réseau social afin de mieux comprendre comment vos données à caractère personnel peuvent être utilisées, divulguées ou autrement traitées par ces parties.
    
* **Informations liées à des parrainages** . Nous pouvons vous donner la possibilité d'inviter des amis ou de parrainer d'autres utilisateurs pour leur permettre d'accéder à nos Services ou de les utiliser. Ce faisant, nous pouvons collecter et recevoir certaines données à caractère personnel vous concernant, y compris de la part d'autres utilisateurs et clients actuels ou potentiels de TMG qui s'engagent de la même manière dans ces activités.

**Données à caractère personnel collectées automatiquement** . Nous et nos fournisseurs de services tiers pouvons collecter automatiquement ou déduire des données à caractère personnel vous concernant lorsque vous utilisez nos Services, y compris par le biais de cookies, de pixels espions et d'autres technologies similaires.Les données à caractère personnel que nous pouvons collecter automatiquement sont les suivantes :

* **Données relatives à l'appareil et à la navigation** . Lorsque vous utilisez nos Services, nous pouvons collecter le type de navigateur, le nom de domaine, les pages consultées, les temps d'accès, les horodatages, le système d'exploitation, la langue, le type d'appareil, l'identifiant unique, le fournisseur d'accès Internet, les URL de référence et de sortie, les données de flux de clics, la langue et d'autres données similaires relatives à l'appareil et à la navigation.
    
* **Activités et utilisation** . Nous pouvons également collecter des données d'activité relatives à votre utilisation des Services, telles que des données sur les liens cliqués, les recherches, les fonctionnalités utilisées, les éléments consultés, le temps passé sur les Services, vos interactions avec nous et d'autres personnes sur les Services, ainsi que d'autres données similaires relatives à l'activité et à l'utilisation.
    
* **Données de localisation** . Nous pouvons également collecter ou déduire des informations générales de localisation vous concernant, par exemple via votre adresse IP.

Pour en savoir plus sur notre utilisation des cookies et autres technologies similaires, veuillez consulter la clause 6. Cookies, ciblage et analyse ci-dessous.

**3\. Finalités de la collecte et du traitement**

En règle générale, nous pouvons collecter, utiliser, divulguer et traiter autrement les catégories de données à caractère personnel que nous collectons ou à d'autres fins similaires :

* **Services et assistance** . Pour fournir et exploiter nos Services (par exemple, Tagged ou la fonctionnalité de jeu Pets), gérer votre compte, communiquer avec vous concernant votre utilisation des Services, assurer le dépannage, l'assistance technique, ou à des fins d'assistance similaires, et pour répondre à vos demandes, satisfaire vos requêtes, faciliter le traitement des paiements, et pour gérer nos opérations quotidiennes. Cela inclut de rendre certaines de vos données à caractère personnel comme votre identifiant, votre nom d'utilisateur, vos coordonnées comme sélectionnées dans vos paramètres de respect de la vie privée visibles aux utilisateurs du Service respectif ou de nos autres Services, et d'autres applications que nous possédons et d'autres applications et sites web qui ne nous appartiennent pas et avec lesquels nous partageons notre plateforme live. TMG s'appuie sur la base juridique « exécution d'un contrat »(art. 6 (1) (b) du RGPD et du RGPD du Royaume-Uni, et art. 31 (2) (b) de la nLPD). Dans la mesure où nous traitons vos données à caractère personnel pour les rendre visibles aux utilisateurs de nos autres Services, et d'autres applications que nous possédons et d'autres applications et sites web ne nous appartenant pas avec lesquels nous partageons notre plateforme live, TMG s'appuie sur la base « exécution d'un contrat » (art. 6 (1) (b) du RGPD et du RGPD du Royaume-Uni, et art. 31 (2) (b) de la nLPD).

En ce qui concerne les données de localisation, TMG s'appuie sur votre consentement (art. 6 (1) (a), art. 7 du GDPR).

En ce qui concerne l'orientation sexuelle, TMG s'appuie sur votre consentement explicite (art. 6 (1) (a), art. 7, art. 9 (2) (a) du RGPD/RGPD du Royaume-Uni) ou sur l'exception prévue à l'art. 9 (2) (e) du RGPD/RGPD du Royaume-Uni à condition que vous ayez révélé publiquement votre orientation sexuelle (par exemple, dans une diffusion en direct).

* **Analyses et améliorations** . Pour mieux comprendre la manière dont les utilisateurs accèdent et utilisent les Services, et à d'autres fins de recherche et d'analyse, telles que l'évaluation et l'amélioration du Site, de nos Services et de nos opérations commerciales, y compris pour développer nos Services et ses fonctionnalités, et à des fins de contrôle de qualité interne et de formation.TMG s'appuie sur la base juridique des « intérêts légitimes »(art. 6 (1) (f) RGPD/RGPD du Royaume-Uni et art. 31 (1) de la nLPD). À cet égard, TMG poursuit son intérêt à comprendre le fonctionnement du service d'un point de vue professionnel.

**Communication** . Pour répondre à vos questions, vous envoyer les documents demandés ainsi que des informations et des documents concernant nos offres et Services. Nous pouvons également utiliser ces informations pour vous envoyer des informations administratives, comme des informations concernant les Services et les modifications apportées à nos conditions et politiques par exemple. TMG s'appuie sur la base juridique « exécution d'un contrat » (art. 6 (1) (b) du RGPD/RGPD du Royaume-Uni et art. 31 (2) (a) de la nLPD) ou - en l'absence de contrat entre l'utilisateur concerné et TMG - « les intérêts légitimes » (art. 6 (1) (f) RGPD/RGPD du Royaume-Uni et art. 31 (1) de la nLPD). Lorsque TMG s'appuie sur des « intérêts légitimes », TMG poursuit ses intérêts en fournissant une assistance et en répondant aux demandes afin de garantir la satisfaction de l'utilisateur.

* **Personnalisation** . Pour adapter le contenu que nous pouvons envoyer ou afficher dans le cadre des Services, y compris pour offrir une personnalisation en fonction de la localisation et pour personnaliser d'une autre manière vos expériences et vos offres. TMG s'appuie sur la base juridique « exécution d'un contrat » (art. 6 (1) (b) du RGPD et du RGPD du Royaume-Uni, et art. 31 (2) (b) de la nLPD).
    
* Communication sur les réseaux sociaux et autres plateformes. Pour vous permettre de partager des informations ou du contenu, de vous connecter ou de vous inscrire aux Services par le biais de différentes plateformes de réseaux sociaux, de services de réseaux sociaux ou d'autres fonctionnalités ou services intégrés tiers. Pour vous permettre de vous connecter ou de vous inscrire aux Services, TMG s'appuie sur la base juridique « exécution d'un contrat » (art. 6 (1) (b) du RGPD et du RGPD du Royaume-Uni, et art. 31 (2) (b) de la nLPD). Autrement, TMG s'appuie sur la base juridique « intérêts légitimes » (art. 6 (1) (f) RGPD/RGPD du Royaume-Uni et art. 31 (1) de la nLPD). À cet égard, TMG poursuit son intérêt en permettant aux utilisateurs d'initier certaines communications avec des plateformes de réseaux sociaux, des services de réseaux sociaux ou d'autres fonctionnalités tierces ou services intégrés si tel est leur souhait.
    
* **Marketing et publicité** . À des fins de marketing, de publicité et de promotion. Par exemple, pour vous envoyer des informations promotionnelles concernant nos Services, y compris des newsletters, des informations concernant les événements de TMG, des webinaires, des présentations, des ventes, des bonnes affaires, des remises et de nouvelles offres, ainsi que toute autre information que vous acceptez de recevoir. TMG s'appuie sur la base juridique du « consentement » (art. 6 (1) (a), art. 7 du GDPR et du RGPD du Royaume-Uni et art. 31 (1) de la nLPD.

À des fins d'autopublicité / de marketing direct par le biais d'e-mails promotionnels et/ou de messages push, d'enquêtes (auprès des utilisateurs) et de guides individualisés (exclusivement des produits TMG). (La base juridique est l'intérêt légitime de TMG dans le marketing direct pour ses propres produits, ainsi que la clause 7 (3) de la « German Act against Unfair Competition » (UWG)).

* **Recherches et enquêtes** . Pour réaliser des enquêtes et des questionnaires, par exemple à des fins d'étude de marché, de satisfaction des utilisateurs ou à d'autres fins similaires. TMG s'appuie sur la base juridique du « consentement » (art. 6 (1) (a), art. 7 du GDPR et du RGPD du Royaume-Uni et art. 31 (1) de la nLPD.
    
* **Élaboration de renseignements et amélioration des données** . Nous pouvons combiner les données à caractère personnel collectées par le biais des Services avec d'autres informations que nous ou des tiers collectons sur vous dans d'autres contextes. Dans la plupart des cas, les informations que nous pouvons combiner avec les données à caractère personnel collectées par le biais des Services à des fins d'étude de marché, telles que les données démographiques, ne permettent pas d'identifier directement les consommateurs. TMG s'appuie sur la base juridique des « intérêts légitimes » (art. 6 (1) (f) RGPD/RGPD du Royaume-Uni et art. 31 (1) de la nLPD). À cet égard, TMG poursuit son intérêt à comprendre le fonctionnement du service d'un point de vue professionnel.
    
* **Accès et stockage d'informations sur l'appareil final de l'utilisateur** . Nous pouvons accéder à des informations ou les stocker sur votre appareil final. TMG s'appuie sur la base juridique du « consentement » (art. 5 (3) de la directive e-Privacy et art. 6 (4) du règlement PECR lorsque cela n'est pas strictement nécessaire au fonctionnement de notre site web ainsi qu'à la fourniture de services télémédias expressément demandés par l'utilisateur.
    
* **Planification et gestion d'événements** . Pour planifier des événements et à d'autres fins liées à la gestion, telles que l'inscription et la participation à des événements, la mise en relation avec d'autres participants à des événements et avec des utilisateurs de TMG, et la prise de contact avec vous à propos d'événements pertinents, de présentations et de nos Services. Nous pouvons également utiliser des données à caractère personnel pour faciliter l'organisation d'événements spéciaux, de tirages au sort, de concours et de promotions, qui peuvent être soumis à des règles de participation spécifiques. TMG s'appuie sur la base juridique du « consentement » (art. 6 (1) (a), art. 7 du GDPR et du RGPD du Royaume-Uni et art. 31 (1) de la nLPD.
    
* **Sécurité et protection des droits** . Pour protéger les Services et nos opérations métier, nos droits et ceux de nos parties prenantes et investisseurs, pour prévenir et détecter les fraudes, les activités et accès non autorisés et autres utilisations abusives de notre Site, y compris lorsque nous le jugeons nécessaire pour mener une enquête, prévenir ou prendre des mesures en cas d'activités illégales, de suspicion de fraude, de situations impliquant des menaces potentielles pour la sécurité ou les droits légaux d'une personne ou d'un tiers, ou de violations de nos Conditions d'utilisation. TMG s'appuie sur la base juridique des « intérêts légitimes » (art. 6 (1) (f) du RGPD/RGPD du Royaume-Uni et art. 31 (1) de la nLPD). L'intérêt légitime de TMG et des utilisateurs de TMG est que le service de TMG ne soit pas utilisé de manière abusive pour des actes contractuels et/ou illégaux de tiers. Notre intérêt légitime est également de protéger les systèmes de sécurisation informatique de TMG et donc en fin de compte de protéger les données à caractère personnel des utilisateurs de TMG. En ce qui concerne l'orientation sexuelle, TMG s'appuie en outre sur la base juridique de l'établissement, de l'exercice ou de la défense de droits en justice (art. 9 (2) (f) du RGPD/RGPD du Royaume-Uni).
    
* **Conformité et procédure judiciaire** . Pour se conformer aux obligations légales ou réglementaires en vigueur, y compris les obligations légales de conservation ou dans le cadre d'une procédure judiciaire, pour répondre à une citation à comparaître, à un mandat, à une ordonnance d'un tribunal ou à toute autre procédure judiciaire, ou dans le cadre d'une enquête ou d'une demande, qu'elle soit formelle ou informelle, formulée par les forces de l'ordre ou par une autorité gouvernementale. TMG s'appuie sur la base juridique du (i) « respect des obligations légales » (art. 6 (1) (c) du RGPD/RGPD du Royaume-Uni et art. 31 (2) (a) de la nLPD) si cette obligation découle de la législation européenne ou de celle d'un État membre de l'UE, ou (ii) l'« intérêt légitime » (art. 6 (1) (f) du RGPD/RGPD du Royaume-Uni et l'art. 31 (1) de la nLPD) si cette obligation provient d'autres juridictions. Lorsque les intérêts légitimes sont pertinents, TMG poursuit ses intérêts en se conformant aux obligations légales auxquelles TMG est soumise. En ce qui concerne l'orientation sexuelle, TMG s'appuie en outre sur la base juridique de l'établissement, de l'exercice ou de la défense de droits en justice (art. 9 (2) (f) du RGPD/RGPD du Royaume-Uni).
    
* **Audits, rapports et autres opérations internes** . Pour effectuer des audits financiers, fiscaux et comptables, des vérifications et des évaluations de nos opérations, y compris de notre niveau de protection de la vie privée, de notre sécurité et de nos contrôles financiers, ainsi qu'à des fins de risque et de conformité. Nous pouvons également utiliser des données à caractère personnel pour tenir les registres commerciaux appropriés et appliquer nos politiques et procédures. TMG s'appuie sur la base juridique des « intérêts légitimes » (art. 6 (1) (f) du RGPD/RGPD du Royaume-Uni et art. 31 (1) de la nLPD). L'intérêt légitime de TMG est de préserver les opérations commerciales et de s'assurer régulièrement que les obligations en matière de rapports et de conformité sont remplies.
    
* **Gestion de l'activité et assistance opérationnelle** . Pour évaluer et réaliser des fusions, des acquisitions, des réorganisations, des faillites et d'autres opérations commerciales telles que des financements, et pour gérer nos activités, notre comptabilité, nos audits, notre conformité, la tenue de nos dossiers et nos fonctions juridiques. TMG s'appuie sur la base juridique des « intérêts légitimes » (art. 6 (1) (f) du RGPD et art. 31 (1) de la nLPD. Dans ce contexte, TMG a un intérêt à divulguer et à traiter des informations sur ses actifs et ses activités à des acheteurs ou acquéreurs potentiels et à leurs conseillers externes afin de faciliter la vente de ces actifs et/ou activités.

Les objectifs que nous poursuivons en utilisant des cookies et des technologies similaires, en particulier en ce qui concerne le ciblage et l'analyse, sont décrits à la clause 6. Cookies, ciblage et analyse.

Lorsque la base juridique du traitement est votre consentement, vous avez le droit de le retirer à tout moment. Toutefois, ce retrait n'affectera pas la légalité de tout traitement effectué sur la base de votre consentement avant votre retrait. Si la base juridique est un intérêt légitime, vous avez également le droit, de manière générale, de vous opposer au traitement de vos données à caractère personnel, à tout moment, pour des raisons liées à votre situation. En outre, vous avez le droit de vous opposer à tout moment au traitement de vos données à caractère personnel à des fins de marketing direct. L'article 21 du GDPR / RGPD du Royaume-Uni s'applique à cet égard.

Lors de votre inscription ou ultérieurement, vous pouvez à tout moment vous opposer à l'utilisation de votre adresse e-mail à des fins promotionnelles ou de conseils personnels.

**4\. Divulgation des données à caractère personnel**

Nous pouvons divulguer les données à caractère personnel que nous collectons aux fins décrites ci-dessus, pour vous fournir nos Services, pour répondre à vos demandes, selon vos instructions ou votre consentement, et avec les destinataires suivants :

* **Marques, sociétés affiliées et filiales** . Nous pouvons divulguer les données à caractère personnel que nous collectons à nos marques, sociétés affiliées et filiales.
    
* **Partenaires commerciaux** . Dans certaines circonstance, TMG peut s'associer à d'autres entreprises pour offrir ses Services, y compris pour favoriser certains programmes ou offres spéciales, et nous pouvons divulguer des données à caractère personnel à ces partenaires commerciaux.
    
* **Fournisseurs et prestataires de services** . Nous pouvons divulguer les données à caractère personnel que nous collectons à des fournisseurs et prestataires de services qui exécutent des fonctions en notre nom, tels que des services informatiques et d'hébergement de sites web, des prestataires de services de paiement, des prestataires de services de marketing et d'études de marché, des services d'assistance client, des services de stockage de données, des prestataires de services d'analyse de données, des auditeurs, des consultants, des conseillers et des agents, ainsi que des conseillers juridiques.
    
* **Autres utilisateurs de TMG** . Avec d'autres utilisateurs des Services dans le cadre de fonctionnalités ayant une dimension sociale de façon intrinsèque. Par exemple, si vous invitez d'autres personnes à utiliser nos Services, ou si vous soumettez ou mettez à disposition des informations par le biais de nos fonctionnalités interactives orientées public, de nos forums communautaires ou de nos blogs de discussion, y compris lorsque vous publiez des avis ou des témoignages, certaines données à caractère personnel peuvent être accessibles et consultables par d'autres utilisateurs des Services. Par exemple, si vous participez à Pets, d'autres utilisateurs de la fonctionnalité de jeu Pets pourront voir des données à caractère personnel telles que votre photo de profil, votre genre, votre valeur, vos liquidités, vos actifs, les Pets possédés et combien vous en possédez.
    
* **Fournisseurs d'analyse et de services de marketing tiers** . Nous pouvons également transmettre vos informations personnelles, telles que les données relatives aux appareils et à la navigation, ainsi que les données d'activité et d'utilisation, à des fournisseurs tiers de services de marketing et d'analyse de données, ainsi qu'à d'autres entreprises qui fournissent des services de marketing, de publicité, de gestion de campagne ou d'analyse en notre nom. Pour obtenir une vue détaillée des destinataires spécifiques, consultez notre plateforme de gestion du consentement dans l'application.

Nous pouvons également divulguer vos données à caractère personnel dans les circonstances suivantes :

* **Pour soutenir des transferts d'activité** . Si nous ou nos sociétés affiliées sommes ou pouvons être rachetés, faire l'objet d'une fusion ou d'un investissement par une autre société, ou si l'un de nos actifs est ou peut être transféré à une autre société, que ce soit dans le cadre d'une procédure de faillite ou d'insolvabilité ou autrement, nous pouvons divulguer ou transférer les données à caractère personnel que nous avons collectées auprès de vous avec ou à l'autre société, conformément aux lois en vigueur. Nous pouvons également divulguer certaines données à caractère personnel si cela s'avère nécessaire avant la réalisation d'une telle transaction ou de toute autre opération telle qu'un financement ou une restructuration, à des prêteurs, des auditeurs et des conseillers tiers, y compris des avocats et des consultants.
    
* **Pour respecter nos obligations juridiques et de conformité** . Nous pouvons également divulguer des données à caractère personnel à des tiers dans la mesure où le droit applicable et les obligations légales l'exigent. Nous pouvons, par exemple, divulguer des données pour répondre à des citations à comparaître, à des ordonnances judiciaires et à d'autres demandes légales émanant de régulateurs, d'entités gouvernementales et d'autorités chargées de l'application de la loi, y compris pour répondre à des exigences de divulgation en matière de sécurité nationale ou d'application de la loi, ou si la loi ou une procédure judiciaire l'exige. En outre, et le cas échéant, nous pouvons divulguer les noms des gagnants de concours et de loteries conformément à la loi en vigueur.
    
* **Pour garantir la sécurité et protéger les droits** . Lorsque nous estimons que cela est nécessaire pour protéger les Services, nos droits et nos biens, ou les droits, les biens et la sécurité d'autrui. Par exemple, nous pouvons divulguer des données à caractère personnel pour (i) prévenir, détecter, enquêter et réagir à la fraude, aux activités et accès non autorisés, aux activités illégales et à l'utilisation abusive des Services, (ii) aux situations présentant des menaces potentielles pour la santé, la sécurité ou les droits légaux d'une personne ou d'un tiers, ou (iii) appliquer, détecter, enquêter et prendre des mesures en cas de violation de nos Conditions d'utilisation.Nous pouvons également divulguer des données à caractère personnel dans le cadre de litiges et d'autres réclamations ou procédures juridiques dans lesquelles nous sommes impliqués, ainsi que pour nos fonctions internes de comptabilité, d'audit, de conformité, d'archivage et juridiques.
    
* **Autres divulgations** . Nous pouvons divulguer des données à caractère personnel d'une autre manière que celle décrite ci-dessus, si nous vous en informons ou si nous obtenons votre consentement, ou si la loi l'autorise ou l'exige.

Nonobstant toute autre disposition de la présente Politique, nous pouvons utiliser et divulguer des données agrégées, dépersonnalisées et autres données non identifiables relatives à nos activités et aux Services à des fins de contrôle de la qualité, d'analyse, de recherche, de développement et autres. Lorsque nous utilisons, divulguons ou traitons des données dépersonnalisées (données qui ne sont plus raisonnablement liées ou rattachables à une personne physique identifiée ou identifiable, à un foyer ou à un appareil personnel ou domestique), nous conserverons et utiliserons les informations sous une forme dépersonnalisée et ne tenterons pas de réidentifier les informations, sauf lorsqu'il s'agit de déterminer si nos processus de dépersonnalisation sont raisonnables et adéquats en vertu des lois en vigueur en matière de protection de la vie privée.

**5\. Transferts de données à caractère personnel dans le cadre de pays situés en dehors de l'Espace économique européen (EEE), du Royaume-Uni et de la Suisse**

Les destinataires des données à caractère personnel peuvent être situés en dehors de l'EEE/du Royaume-Uni/de la Suisse.Lorsque des données à caractère personnel sont transférées en dehors de l'EEE/du Royaume-Uni/de la Suisse (ce qui inclut les transferts de notre part aux États-Unis en tant que responsable du traitement dans le cadre du RGPD/du RGPD du Royaume-Uni/de la nLPD vers des destinataires aux États-Unis ou dans d'autres pays en dehors de l'EEE/du Royaume-Uni/de la Suisse, qui n'entrent pas dans le champ d'application du RGPD/du RGPD du Royaume-Uni/de la nLPD), nous veillerons, comme la loi l'exige, à ce que vos droits en matière de respect de la vie privée soient protégés de manière adéquate, soit parce que la Commission européenne a décidé que le pays vers lequel les données à caractère personnel sont transférées garantit un niveau de protection adéquat (art. 45 du RGPD / RGPD du Royaume-Uni), soit parce que le transfert est soumis à des garanties appropriées (par exemple, des clauses types de protection des données de l'Union européenne convenues avec le destinataire) (art. 46 du RGPD / RGPD du Royaume-Uni), à moins que le RGPD / RGPD du Royaume-Uni ne prévoie une exception (art. 49 du RGPD / RGPD du Royaume-Uni). En outre, nous avons l'intention, le cas échéant, de mettre en place des mesures supplémentaires avec les destinataires afin de garantir un niveau adéquat de protection des données. Voir également l'art. 16 f. de la nLPD relatif à la divulgation de données à caractère personnel en dehors de la Suisse.

Si besoin, nous concluons également avec nos partenaires contractuels un « Addendum britannique » correspondant, conformément aux exigences de l'Information Commissioner's Office (ICO), et un « Addendum suisse » correspondant, conformément aux exigences du Préposé fédéral à la protection des données et à la transparence (PFPDT) suisse.

Des copies des mesures de protection appropriées (dans la mesure où nous nous appuyons sur ces mesures) et une liste des destinataires situés en dehors de l'EEE/du Royaume-Uni/de la Suisse peuvent être demandées à [support@themeetgroup.com](mailto:support@themeetgroup.com).Veuillez noter que cette copie peut être expurgée dans la mesure nécessaire pour protéger les secrets professionnels ou toute autre information confidentielle.

**6\. Cookies, ciblage et analyses**

Nous et nos prestataires de services tiers utilisons des cookies, des pixels espions, des objets de stockage local, des fichiers journaux et d'autres mécanismes de suivi pour collecter automatiquement des informations sur la navigation, l'activité, l'appareil et d'autres informations similaires au sein de nos Services. Nous exploitons ces informations pour analyser et comprendre comment les utilisateurs accèdent à nos Services, les utilisent et interagissent avec eux, pour identifier et résoudre les bogues et les erreurs dans nos Services, pour évaluer, sécuriser, protéger, optimiser et améliorer les performances de nos Services, ainsi qu'à des fins de marketing et d'analyse, et pour personnaliser le contenu de nos Services. Selon votre localisation, la plupart de ces actions ne seront effectuées que si vous avez donné votre consentement via notre CMP, qui est à votre disposition dans les paramètres de votre application afin de vous permettre de gérer votre consentement / vos préférences concernant les cookies, la publicité ciblée et d'autres mécanismes de suivi similaires au sein de nos Services ; veuillez vous reporter à la clause 7. Vos options en matière de protection de la vie privée ci-dessous. Beaucoup de ces options sont spécifiques au navigateur et à l'appareil, ce qui signifie que vous devrez peut-être définir la préférence pour chaque navigateur et appareil que vous utilisez pour accéder à nos Services. En outre, si vous supprimez ou bloquez les cookies, vous devrez peut-être appliquer à nouveau ces préférences à chaque navigateur et/ou appareil.

**Cookies** . Les « cookies » sont de petits fichiers texte stockés sur l'appareil d'un utilisateur (comme un ordinateur ou un smartphone) par un site web qu'il visite. Il sont créés par le serveur du site web et envoyés au navigateur de l'utilisateur, où ils sont stockés pour être utilisés ultérieurement. Certains cookies nous permettent d'améliorer la navigation dans nos Services, tandis que d'autres sont utilisés, par exemple, pour accélérer le processus de connexion, renforcer le niveau de sécurité et les performances des Services, ou nous permettre de collecter des informations globales et statistiques sur l'activité des utilisateurs dans le cadre des Services.

**Pixels espions** . Les pixels espions (parfois appelés balises web ou pixels invisibles) sont de minuscules éléments graphiques dotés d'un identifiant unique, dont la fonction est similaire à celle des cookies. Alors que les cookies sont stockés localement sur votre appareil, les pixels espions sont intégrés de manière invisible dans les pages web et le contenu en ligne. Nous pouvons les utiliser dans le cadre de nos Services pour, entre autres, suivre les activités des utilisateurs et nous permettre de gérer le contenu et de compiler des statistiques d'utilisation. Nous pouvons également les utiliser dans nos e-mails pour savoir s'ils ont été ouverts ou transférés, afin de suivre le taux de réponse et d'évaluer l'efficacité de nos communications.

**Fichiers journaux** . Nous pouvons collecter certaines informations concernant les activités à partir de fichiers journaux. Les informations des fichiers journaux sont collectées automatiquement lorsque vous accédez à nos Sites. Nous enregistrons certaines informations à partir de ces fichiers journaux, notamment les requêtes web, l'adresse IP, le type et la version du navigateur, les informations sur la langue, les URL de référence et de sortie, les liens cliqués, les pages consultées et d'autres informations similaires.

**Outils d'analyse tiers** . Nous pouvons utiliser des dispositifs, des applications et des outils automatisés, tels que Google Analytics, qui sont exploités par des entreprises tierces, pour évaluer l'utilisation de nos Services. Ces entreprises tierces peuvent utiliser des cookies, des pixels et d'autres technologies de suivi pour collecter des données sur l'utilisation de nos Services et nous fournir des rapports et des indicateurs qui nous aident à évaluer l'utilisation de nos Services et à améliorer les performances et l'expérience des utilisateurs. Pour en savoir plus sur les pratiques de Google en matière de respect de la vie privée, veuillez consulter les règles de confidentialité de Google à [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). Vous pouvez également télécharger le module complémentaire de navigateur pour la désactivation de Google Analytics afin d'empêcher l'utilisation de vos données par Google Analytics sur [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). Une liste des tiers auxquels nous faisons appel à cet égard figure dans notre CMP, que vous trouverez dans les paramètres de votre application.

**Publicités tierces** . Nous travaillons avec des réseaux publicitaires tiers, des partenaires marketing, des réseaux publicitaires mobiles et d'autres (« agences de publicité tierces ») pour personnaliser le contenu et afficher de la publicité au sein de nos Services, ainsi que pour gérer notre publicité sur des sites web tiers.Nous et ces agences de publicité tierces pouvons utiliser des cookies, des pixels espions, des kits de développement logiciel (SDK) et d'autres outils pour collecter des informations sur la navigation et l'activité au sein de nos Services (ainsi que sur des sites et services tiers), ainsi que l'adresse IP, l'identifiant unique, les identifiants de cookies et de publicité et d'autres identificateurs en ligne. Nous et ces agences de publicité tierces utilisons ces informations pour vous proposer des publicités et du contenu plus pertinents au sein de nos Services et sur des sites tiers, et pour évaluer les performances de ces publicités et de ce contenu. Une liste des agences de publicité tierces est disponible dans notre CMP, dans les paramètres de votre application.

**Utilisation sur tous les appareils** . Nous et nos prestataires de services tiers pouvons utiliser les informations que nous collectons à votre sujet (que ce soit directement à partir de nos Sites ou de l'App mobile, par le biais de votre (vos) appareil(s), ou à partir de sources tierces) pour nous permettre et permettre à nos prestataires de services tiers d'identifier les autres appareils que vous utilisez (par exemple, un téléphone mobile, une tablette, un autre ordinateur, etc.). Nous et nos prestataires de services tiers pouvons également avoir recours à l'utilisation sur tous les appareils et à d'autres informations que nous obtenons à votre sujet pour diffuser des publicités ciblées ou personnaliser le contenu de nos Services.

**Listes personnalisées et ciblage** . Nous pouvons partager ou mettre à disposition certaines informations relatives aux listes de clients (telles que votre nom, votre adresse e-mail et d'autres informations de contact) avec des tiers afin de mieux cibler les publicités et le contenu qui vous sont proposés sur des sites web, des plateformes et des services tiers.Dans certains cas, ces tiers peuvent nous aider à enrichir nos listes de clients avec des informations démographiques supplémentaires ou d'autres informations similaires afin que nous puissions mieux cibler nos campagnes publicitaires et marketing.

**7\. Vos options en matière de protection de la vie privée**

**Gestion de vos préférences** . Nous vous proposons plusieurs solutions pour gérer vos préférences et vos options en matière de protection de la vie privée, comme décrit ci-dessous :

* **Compte et profil** . Vous pouvez consulter et mettre à jour certaines des données à caractère personnel que nous conservons à votre sujet en vous connectant à votre compte et en mettant à jour les informations relatives à votre compte et à votre profil.
    
* **Communications marketing** . Nous pouvons vous envoyer des e-mails promotionnels, du contenu ou d'autres communications similaires de manière périodique. Vous pouvez refuser ces communications en suivant les instructions qui vous sont fournies dans la communication. Si vous refusez de recevoir du contenu promotionnel de notre part, nous pouvons toujours vous envoyer des communications concernant votre compte ou tout service que vous avez demandé ou reçu de notre part. En outre, vous pouvez gérer vos préférences en matière de communication depuis les paramètres de votre compte et de votre profil.
    
* **Notifications Push** . Vous pouvez gérer le type de notifications push que vous recevez de notre part en ajustant les paramètres de votre appareil mobile ou en modifiant ceux de notre application mobile. Il s'agit de messages que nous vous envoyons dans le cadre de l'exécution du contrat, ainsi que d'informations promotionnelles.

**Préférences en matière de cookies et de suivi, de publicité ciblée et d'analyse** . Nous mettons également à votre disposition plusieurs méthodes pour gérer vos préférences en matière de cookies, de publicité ciblée, d'analyse et d'autres mécanismes de suivi similaires au sein de nos Services. Beaucoup de ces options sont spécifiques au navigateur et à l'appareil, ce qui signifie que vous devrez peut-être définir la préférence pour chaque navigateur et appareil que vous utilisez pour accéder à nos Services.En outre, si vous supprimez ou bloquez les cookies, vous devrez peut-être appliquer à nouveau ces préférences à chaque navigateur et/ou appareil. En outre, le fait de refuser les cookies et la publicité ne signifie pas que vous ne recevrez plus de contenu publicitaire de notre part, et vous pouvez continuer à recevoir des publicités génériques ou « contextuelles » de notre part.

* **Plateforme de gestion du consentement (CMP)** . Pour empêcher les cookies ou autres mécanismes de suivi qui ne sont pas strictement nécessaires de suivre votre activité sur nos Sites ou dans notre Application mobile, vous pouvez utiliser la plateforme de gestion du consentement qui est fournie avant que les cookies et les mécanismes de suivi ne soient utilisés. Une fois qu'un consentement est donné, il peut être retiré à tout moment avec effet dans le futur. Pour en savoir plus, veuillez consulter la clause 15. Informations supplémentaires sur la protection de la vie privée dans certaines juridictions, qui comprend des informations supplémentaires sur les droits en matière de protection de la vie privée pour les personnes résidant dans certaines juridictions.
    
* **Paramètres en matière de cookies** . Pour empêcher les cookies de suivre votre activité sur nos Sites ou vos visites sur plusieurs sites web, vous pouvez configurer votre navigateur pour qu'il bloque certains cookies ou qu'il vous avertisse lorsqu'un cookie est défini.Vous pouvez également supprimer les cookies. La partie « Aide » de la barre d'outils de la plupart des navigateurs vous indiquera comment empêcher votre appareil d'accepter de nouveaux cookies, comment faire en sorte que le navigateur vous prévienne lorsque vous recevez un nouveau cookie ou comment les supprimer. Les visiteurs de nos Sites qui désactivent les cookies pourront naviguer sur le Site, mais certaines fonctionnalités risquent de ne pas fonctionner.
    
* **Signaux du navigateur** . Dans la mesure où le droit applicable l'exige, si nos Sites détectent que votre navigateur transmet un signal de préférence de refus, tel qu'un signal « global privacy control » (ou GPC), nous appliquerons ce signal pour refuser les cookies de ciblage sur nos Sites au navigateur concerné. Si vous accédez à nos Sites à partir d'un autre appareil ou d'un autre navigateur sur le même appareil, vous devrez également appliquer le CPG pour ce navigateur et/ou cet appareil.
    
* **Programmes de préférences publicitaires** . Vous pouvez également contrôler la manière dont les agences de publicité tierces utilisent les informations qu'elles collectent sur vos visites sur nos Sites et sur ceux de tiers, afin de vous proposer des publicités ciblées plus pertinentes. Pour en savoir plus et obtenir de l'aide concernant les mécanismes de suivi sur le web, rendez-vous sur [www.YourOnlineChoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/).

Les personnes résidant dans certaines juridictions peuvent avoir des droits supplémentaires concernant leurs données à caractère personnel, comme indiqué ci-dessous dans la clause 15. Informations supplémentaires sur la protection de la vie privée dans certaines juridictions.

**8\. Durée de stockage des données à caractère personnel**

Nous conservons vos données à caractère personnel aussi longtemps que nécessaire pour atteindre les objectifs mentionnés à la clause 3 « Finalités de la collecte et du traitement » et à la clause 6 « Cookies, ciblage et analyses », ou aussi longtemps que nous avons un intérêt légitime à poursuivre la conservation de ces données. Dans tous les autres cas, nous supprimons vos données à caractère personnel, à l'exception des données que nous devons continuer à conserver afin de respecter les délais de conservation légaux (par exemple, en vertu du droit fiscal ou commercial, notamment en ce qui concerne les factures). Nous limitons le traitement des données personnelles qui ne sont conservées qu'en raison d'une obligation de conservation.

Vous trouverez des informations sur la durée de stockage des cookies et autres mécanismes de suivi dans notre CMP, qui est disponible dans les paramètres de votre application.

**9\. Liens et fonctionnalités externes**

Nos Services peuvent contenir des liens vers des sites web ou des fonctionnalités tiers ou fournir certaines connexions ou des services intégrés tiers. Tout accès et utilisation de ces sites web ou fonctionnalités liés n'est pas régi par la présente Politique, mais par les politiques de respect de la vie privée de ces tiers. Nous ne sommes pas responsables des pratiques en matière d'information de ces tiers, y compris de la collecte, de l'utilisation et de la divulgation de vos données à caractère personnel. Vous devez consulter les politiques de respect de la vie privée et les conditions d'utilisation de ces tiers avant de vous rendre sur ces sites web ou d'utiliser ces fonctionnalités.

**10\. Contenu généré par les Utilisateurs**

Nous pouvons proposer des fonctionnalités interactives publiques, des forums communautaires ou des blogs de discussion en rapport avec nos Services, vous permettant de partager des informations sur les Services ou sur d'autres sujets (par exemple, des avis, des témoignages et des questions). Vous devez savoir que toute communication que vous soumettez ou publiez dans le cadre de ces fonctionnalités interactives des Services peut être consultée et recherchée par d'autres personnes, y compris les utilisateurs de TMG et le public. En soumettant ou en publiant dans le cadre de ces fonctionnalités interactives publiques, vous reconnaissez que vous ne vous attendez pas à ce que le contenu que vous soumettez dans le cadre de ces fonctionnalités soit privé ou confidentiel, qu'il contienne ou non des données à caractère personnel vous concernant.

**11\. Sécurité**

Nous avons mis en œuvre des mesures de précaution raisonnables afin de protéger les données que nous collectons contre la perte, l'utilisation abusive, l'accès non autorisé, la divulgation, l'altération et la destruction. Veuillez noter que malgré tous nos efforts, aucune mesure de sécurité des données ne peut garantir la sécurité.

**12\. Protection de la vie privée des enfants**

Nos Services ne s'adressent pas aux enfants et nous ne collectons pas sciemment des données à caractère personnel auprès d'enfants âgés de moins de dix-huit (18) ans. Si nous apprenons que des données à caractère personnel ont été collectées via les Services auprès de personnes âgées de moins de 18 ans, nous prendrons les mesures nécessaires pour supprimer ces données. Si vous êtes un parent ou un tuteur légal et que vous pensez que nous avons collecté les données de votre enfant au mépris de la législation en vigueur, veuillez nous contacter en utilisant les coordonnées ci-dessous.

**13\. Modifications de la présente Politique**

La présente Politique est en vigueur à la date indiquée ci-dessus. Nous pouvons modifier ou mettre à jour la présente Politique de temps à autre, veuillez donc la consulter régulièrement. Nous publierons ici toute mise à jour de la présente Politique.Si nous apportons des modifications à la présente Politique qui affectent matériellement nos pratiques concernant notre utilisation des données à caractère personnel que nous avons précédemment collectées auprès de vous, nous nous efforcerons de vous en informer, en vous envoyant par exemple un e-mail ou en publiant un avis bien visible sur nos Sites, dans notre Application mobile ou au sein des Services.

**14\. Nous contacter**

Si vous avez des questions ou des préoccupations concernant la présente Politique ou nos pratiques en matière de protection de la vie privée, vous pouvez nous envoyer un e-mail à l'adresse [support@themeetgroup.com](mailto:support@themeetgroup.com) ou nous contacter à l'adresse suivante :

The Meet Group, Inc.

100 Union Square Drive

New Hope, PA 18938

Vous pouvez contacter notre délégué à la protection des données à :

ePrivacy GmbH représentée par Prof Dr. Christoph Bauer, Große Bleichen 21, 20354 Hamburg, [privacy@themeetgroup.com](mailto:privacy@themeetgroup.com)

Pour toute demande concernant la sécurité de vos données, veuillez contacter notre délégué à la protection des données à [privacy@themeetgroup.com](mailto:privacy@themeetgroup.com).

Notre représentant pour l'UE conformément à l'art. 27 du RGPD peut être contacté à l'adresse suivante : ParshipMeet Holding GmbH, Speersort 10, 20095 Hamburg, e-mail : [privacy@parshipmeet.com](mailto:privacy@parshipmeet.com).

Les coordonnées de notre représentant pour le Royaume-Uni, conformément à l'article 27 du RGPD, sont indiquées au paragraphe 15.B. Informations supplémentaires pour les résidents du Royaume-Uni

Les coordonnées de notre représentant suisse conformément à l'art. 14 de la nLPD (nouvelle Loi suisse sur la protection des données) sont indiquées au paragraphe 15.C.Informations complémentaires pour les résidents suisses.

Treforma AG c/o MLL Legal ; Grabenstrasse 25 ; 6340 Baar ; Switzerland ; [meetgroup@dsg-mll.com](mailto:meetgroup@dsg-mll.com)

**15\. Informations supplémentaires sur la protection de la vie privée dans certaines juridictions**

Les personnes résidant dans certaines juridictions disposent de droits supplémentaires en vertu des lois applicables en matière de protection de la vie privée, comme décrit dans la présente clause.

**A. RGPD**

Si vous résidez dans l'Union européenne, vous disposez des droits suivants en vertu du RGPD, à condition que les exigences légales soient respectées :

**Droit d'accès** - Vous pouvez demander des informations sur le traitement de vos données à caractère personnel et une copie des données à caractère personnel en cours de traitement dans la mesure où cette copie ne porte pas atteinte aux droits et libertés d'autrui et qu'aucune autre exception ne s'applique.

**Droit de rectification** - Vous pouvez demander que vos données à caractère personnel soient rectifiées si elles sont inexactes et/ou qu'elles soient complétées.

**Droit à l'effacement** - Vous pouvez demander l'effacement de vos données à caractère personnel, notamment dans les situations suivantes :

* Les données à caractère personnel ne sont plus nécessaires au regard des finalités pour lesquelles elles ont été collectées ou traitées d'une autre manière.
    
* Vous avez retiré votre consentement sur lequel le traitement était fondé et aucune autre base juridique ne justifie le traitement.
    
* Vous vous êtes opposé au traitement fondé sur la base juridique des « intérêts légitimes » et il n'existe aucun motif légitime prépondérant pour le traitement, ou vous vous êtes opposé au traitement à des fins de marketing direct.
    
* Vos données à caractère personnel ont été traitées de manière illégale.
    
* Vos données à caractère personnel doivent être effacées afin de satisfaire à une obligation légale à laquelle nous sommes soumis.

Toutefois, le droit à l'effacement ne s'applique pas dans le cas particulier où le traitement de vos données à caractère personnel est nécessaire pour satisfaire à une obligation légale ou pour la constatation, l'exercice ou la défense de droits en justice.

**Droit à la limitation du traitement** - Vous pouvez demander la limitation du traitement de vos données :

* au cours de la période pendant laquelle nous vérifions l'exactitude de vos données à caractère personnel si vous avez contesté leur exactitude ;
    
* lorsque le traitement est illégal et que vous demandez la limitation du traitement au lieu de l'effacement des données ;
    
* lorsque nous n'avons plus besoin des données à caractère personnel, mais que vous en avez besoin pour la constatation, l'exercice ou la défense de droits en justice ; ou
    
* si vous vous êtes opposé à un traitement fondé sur la base juridique des « intérêts légitimes », et ce, jusqu'à ce qu'il ait été établi que nos motifs légitimes l'emportent sur vos intérêts, vos droits et vos libertés.

**Droit à la portabilité** - Vous pouvez demander à recevoir les données à caractère personnel vous concernant, que vous nous avez fournies, dans un format structuré, couramment utilisé et lisible par machine, et à transmettre ces données à un autre responsable du traitement sans que nous nous y opposions, lorsque le traitement est fondé sur le consentement ou l'exécution d'un contrat et que le traitement est effectué par des moyens automatisés. Dans ces cas, vous pouvez également demander à ce que les données à caractère personnel soient transmises directement à un autre responsable du traitement, lorsque cela est techniquement possible.

En outre, vous disposez des droits suivants :

**Droit au retrait** - Vous pouvez retirer votre consentement à tout moment et pour le futur lorsque le traitement est basé sur votre consentement, sans affecter la légalité du traitement basé sur le consentement avant son retrait.

**Droit d'opposition -**

**Vous avez le droit de vous opposer, pour des raisons liées à la particularité de votre situation, à tout moment au traitement de vos données à caractère personnel qui est fondé sur notre intérêt légitime ou celui d'un tiers (art. 6 (1) (f) du RGPD). Nous ne traiterons alors plus vos données à caractère personnel pour la finalité à laquelle vous vous êtes opposé, à moins que nous soyons en mesure de prouver l'existence de motifs légitimes impérieux pour le traitement qui prévalent sur vos intérêts, droits et libertés ou pour la constatation, l'exercice ou la défense de droits en justice.**

**En outre, vous avez le droit de vous opposer à tout moment au traitement de vos données à caractère personnel à des fins de marketing direct. Lorsque vous vous opposez au traitement à des fins de marketing direct, nous ne traiterons plus vos données à caractère personnel à ces fins.**

* * *

**Droit de déposer une plainte** - Vous pouvez déposer une plainte auprès d'une autorité de contrôle, en particulier dans l'État membre de votre résidence habituelle, de votre lieu de travail ou du lieu où une violation présumée a été commise, si vous considérez que le traitement de vos données à caractère personnel enfreint le RGPD.

Notre autorité compétente en matière de protection des données est :

Free and Hanseatic City of Hamburg, The Hamburg Commissioner for Data Protection and Freedom of Information, Ludwig-Erhard-Str. 22, 20459 Hamburg, adresse e-mail : [mailbox@datenschutz.hamburg.de](mailto:mailbox@datenschutz.hamburg.de)

**B. RGPD du Royaume-Uni**

Si vous résidez au Royaume-Uni, vous avez des droits en vertu du RGPD du Royaume-Uni et des lois relatives à la protection des données. L'application de ces droits et la mesure dans laquelle ils s'appliquent dépendent des circonstances. Pour exercer l'un de ces droits, veuillez utiliser les coordonnées fournies ci-dessous. Ces droits sont les suivants :

**Votre droit d'être informé** -- Vous avez le droit de recevoir des informations concises, transparentes, intelligibles et facilement accessibles concernant vos données à caractère personnel et l'utilisation que nous en avons faite. La présente Politique constitue notre moyen de vous faire part de ces informations, mais si vous avez d'autres questions ou préoccupations, veuillez utiliser les informations de contact fournies ci-dessous.

**Votre droit d'accès** -- Vous avez le droit de nous demander des copies de vos données à caractère personnel. Ce droit existe en permanence, mais il existe des exceptions à son application, ce qui signifie que vous ne recevrez pas toujours l'ensemble des informations que vous avez demandées. Lorsque vous demandez vos données à caractère personnel, il s'agit d'une demande d'accès aux données de la personne concernée. Nous pouvons être amenés à vous demander des documents afin de vérifier votre identité lorsque nous recevons une demande d'accès aux données de votre part.

**Votre droit de rectification** -- Vous avez le droit de nous demander de rectifier des données à caractère personnel qui, selon vous, sont inexactes. Vous avez également le droit de nous demander de compléter des informations que vous jugez incomplètes.

**Votre droit à l'effacement** -- Vous avez le droit de nous demander d'effacer vos données à caractère personnel dans certaines circonstances. Nous avons le droit de refuser de donner suite à une demande d'effacement si nous traitons les données à caractère personnel pour l'une des raisons suivantes :

* Pour exercer le droit à la liberté d'expression et d'information.
    
* Pour satisfaire à une obligation légale.
    
* Pour accomplir une tâche dans l'intérêt public ou exercer une autorité officielle.
    
* À des fins d'archivage dans l'intérêt public, de recherche scientifique, de recherche historique ou à des fins statistiques.
    
* Pour l'exercice ou la défense de droits légaux.

**Votre droit à la limitation du traitement** -- Vous avez le droit de nous demander de limiter le traitement de vos données à caractère personnel dans certaines circonstances. Dans ce cas, nous conserverons les données mais ne les traiterons plus. Ce droit est une alternative au droit à l'effacement. Si l'une des conditions suivantes s'applique, vous pouvez exercer le droit à la limitation du traitement :

* L'exactitude des données à caractère personnel est contestée.
    
* Le traitement des données à caractère personnel est illégal.
    
* Nous n'avons plus besoin des données à caractère personnel pour le traitement, mais celles-ci sont requises dans le cadre d'une procédure judiciaire.
    
* Le droit d'opposition a été exercé et le traitement est limité dans l'attente d'une décision concernant le statut du traitement.

**Votre droit d'opposition au traitement -- Vous avez le droit de vous opposer au traitement dans certaines circonstances, y compris le marketing direct. Vous pouvez également vous opposer au traitement si celui-ci est fondé sur nos intérêts légitimes (ou ceux d'un tiers). Nous ne traiterons alors plus vos données à caractère personnel pour la finalité à laquelle vous vous êtes opposé, à moins que nous soyons en mesure de prouver l'existence de motifs légitimes impérieux pour le traitement qui prévalent sur vos intérêts, droits et libertés ou pour la constatation, l'exercice ou la défense de droits en justice.**

**Votre droit à la portabilité des données** -- Ce droit vous permet de recevoir vos données à caractère personnel dans un format structuré, couramment utilisé et lisible par machine, mais il s'applique uniquement si nous traitons des informations sur la base de votre consentement ou pour l'exécution d'un contrat et que le traitement est automatisé.

**Droit au retrait** - Vous pouvez retirer votre consentement à tout moment et pour le futur lorsque le traitement est basé sur votre consentement, sans affecter la légalité du traitement basé sur le consentement avant son retrait.

**Coordonnées**

Si vous souhaitez exercer l'un de vos droits ou si vous avez des questions concernant notre utilisation de vos données à caractère personnel, veuillez utiliser les informations figurant dans la rubrique Nous contacter. Veillez également à fournir les informations nécessaires pour nous permettre de vous identifier clairement.

Veuillez noter que nous avons désigné un représentant britannique que vous pouvez contacter en notre nom conformément à l'article 27 du RGPD : eHarmony UK Ltd, 6-10 Great Portland Street, London W1W 8QL, Grande-Bretagne.

**Transferts de données à caractère personnel en dehors du Royaume-Uni**

Pour de plus amples informations sur les mécanismes de protection appliqués à vos données à caractère personnel lorsqu'elles sont transférées en dehors du Royaume-Uni, veuillez consulter la clause 5 Transferts de données à caractère personnel dans le cadre de pays situés en dehors de l'Espace économique européen (EEE), du Royaume-Uni et de la Suisse, ci-dessus.

**Droit de déposer une plainte auprès d'une autorité de contrôle**

Vous avez le droit de déposer une plainte auprès d'une autorité chargée de la protection des données.

Vous pouvez contacter l'autorité britannique chargée de la protection des données, l'Information Commissioner's Office par courrier à l'adresse suivante : Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF, Numéro de téléphone : + 44 (0) 303 123 1113, adresse e-mail : [casework@ico.org.uk](mailto:casework@ico.org.uk).

**C. Loi suisse sur la protection des données**

**Votre droit d'accès** -- Vous avez le droit de nous demander des copies de vos données à caractère personnel. Ce droit existe en permanence, mais il existe des exceptions à son application, ce qui signifie que vous ne recevrez pas toujours l'ensemble des informations que vous avez demandées. Lorsque vous faites une demande de données à caractère personnel, il s'agit d'une demande d'accès aux données de la personne concernée (DSAR).

**Votre droit de rectification** -- Vous avez le droit de nous demander de rectifier des données à caractère personnel qui, selon vous, sont inexactes. Vous avez également le droit de nous demander de compléter des informations que vous jugez incomplètes.

**Votre droit à l'effacement** -- Vous avez le droit de nous demander d'effacer vos données à caractère personnel dans certaines circonstances. Nous avons le droit de refuser de donner suite à une demande d'effacement si nous traitons les données à caractère personnel pour l'une des raisons suivantes :

* Pour exercer le droit à la liberté d'expression et d'information.
    
* Pour satisfaire à une obligation légale.
    
* Pour accomplir une tâche dans l'intérêt public ou exercer une autorité officielle.
    
* À des fins d'archivage dans l'intérêt public, de recherche scientifique, de recherche historique ou à des fins statistiques.
    
* Pour l'exercice ou la défense de droits légaux.

**Votre droit à la limitation du traitement** -- Vous avez le droit de nous demander de limiter le traitement de vos données à caractère personnel dans certaines circonstances. Dans ce cas, nous conserverons les données mais ne les traiterons plus. Ce droit est une alternative au droit à l'effacement. Si l'une des conditions suivantes s'applique, vous pouvez exercer le droit à la limitation du traitement :

* L'exactitude des données à caractère personnel est contestée.
    
* Le traitement des données à caractère personnel est illégal.
    
* Nous n'avons plus besoin des données à caractère personnel pour le traitement, mais celles-ci sont requises dans le cadre d'une procédure judiciaire.
    
* Le droit d'opposition a été exercé et le traitement est limité dans l'attente d'une décision concernant le statut du traitement.

**Votre droit d'opposition au traitement** -- Vous avez le droit de vous opposer au traitement dans certaines circonstances. Vous pouvez également vous opposer au traitement si celui-ci concerne une tâche effectuée dans l'intérêt public, l'exercice de l'autorité publique dont vous êtes investi ou nos intérêts légitimes (ou ceux d'un tiers).

**Votre droit de vous opposer au marketing direct** - Vous pouvez également vous opposer à tout moment au traitement de vos données à caractère personnel à des fins publicitaires (« objection publicitaire »). Veuillez tenir compte du fait que, pour des raisons organisationnelles, il peut exister un chevauchement entre votre révocation et l'utilisation de vos données dans le cadre d'une campagne déjà en cours.

**Votre droit à la portabilité des données** -- Ce droit s'applique uniquement si nous traitons des informations sur la base de votre consentement ou pour l'exécution d'un contrat et que le traitement est automatisé.

Si vous souhaitez exercer l'un de vos droits, veuillez utiliser les informations figurant dans la rubrique Nous contacter. Veillez également à fournir les informations nécessaires pour nous permettre de vous identifier clairement.

**Coordonnées**

Si vous souhaitez exercer l'un de vos droits ou si vous avez des questions concernant notre utilisation de vos données à caractère personnel, veuillez utiliser les informations figurant dans la rubrique Nous contacter. Veillez également à fournir les informations nécessaires pour nous permettre de vous identifier clairement.

Veuillez noter que nous avons désigné un représentant suisse conformément à l'article 14 de la nLPD (nouvelle Loi suisse sur la protection des données) : Treforma AG c/o MLL Legal ; Grabenstrasse 25 ; 6340 Baar ; Switzerland ; [meetgroup@dsg-mll.com](mailto:meetgroup@dsg-mll.com)

**Transferts de données à caractère personnel en dehors de la Suisse**

Pour de plus amples informations sur les mécanismes de protection appliqués à vos données à caractère personnel lorsqu'elles sont transférées en dehors de la Suisse, veuillez consulter la clause 5 Transferts de données à caractère personnel dans le cadre de pays situés en dehors de l'Espace économique européen (EEE), du Royaume-Uni et de la Suisse, ci-dessus.

**Droit de déposer une plainte auprès d'une autorité de contrôle**

Vous avez le droit de déposer une plainte auprès d'une autorité chargée de la protection des données.

Vous pouvez contacter l'autorité suisse chargée de la protection des données. Il s'agit du :

Préposé fédéral à la protection des données et à la transparence (PFPDT).

Vous pouvez la contacter en vous rendant sur cette page :

[https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/de/home/deredoeb/kontakt/kontaktformular\_bgoe.html](https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/de/home/deredoeb/kontakt/kontaktformular_bgoe.html)

**The Meet Group Inc.**

Polityka prywatności dla użytkowników z miejscem zamieszkania w Europejskim Obszarze Gospodarczym lub w Wielkiej Brytanii
=========================================================================================================================

_Data ostatniej aktualizacji: October 8, 2024_

Firma The Meet Group, Inc., jej marki, podmioty stowarzyszone i zależne cenią prywatność użytkowników. Niniejsza Polityka prywatności („ **Polityka** ”) opisuje, w jaki sposób firma The Meet Group, Inc. („ **TMG** ”, „ **my** ”, „ **nasz** ” lub „ **nas** ” we wszystkich formach gramatycznych) gromadzi, wykorzystuje, ujawnia i w inny sposób przetwarza dane użytkowników (zwane również danymi osobowymi w niektórych jurysdykcjach) opisane w niniejszej Polityce, a także prawa i wybory, jakie użytkownik ma w odniesieniu do takich danych osobowych.

Dodatkowe informacje na temat wyborów dotyczących prywatności, które przysługują użytkownikowi w odniesieniu do swoich danych osobowych, przedstawiamy w punkcie 7 zatytułowanej „Wybory użytkownika dotyczące prywatności” oraz w punkcie 15 zatytułowanej „Dodatkowe informacje o prywatności dla niektórych jurysdykcji”, który zawiera dodatkowe informacje o prawach do prywatności dla mieszkańców niektórych jurysdykcji.

Jeśli użytkownik jest rezydentem UE / Europejskiego Obszaru Gospodarczego (EOG), prosimy o zapoznanie się z punktem 15.A zatytułowanym „Dodatkowe informacje dla rezydentów UE/EOG” w celu uzyskania informacji o prawach użytkownika wynikających z ogólnego rozporządzenia o ochronie danych („RODO”).

Jeśli użytkownik jest rezydentem Wielkiej Brytanii, prosimy o zapoznanie z punktem 15.B zatytułowanym „Dodatkowe informacje dla rezydentów Wielkiej Brytanii” w celu uzyskania informacji o prawach użytkownika wynikających z ogólnego rozporządzenia o ochronie danych włączonego do prawa Wielkiej Brytanii na mocy punktu 3 brytyjskiej ustawy o (wystąpieniu z) Unii Europejskiej z 2018 r. („brytyjskie RODO”).

Jeśli użytkownik jest rezydentem Szwajcarii, prosimy o zapoznanie się z punktem 15.Czatytułowanym „Dodatkowe informacje dla rezydentów Szwajcarii” w celu uzyskania informacji o prawach użytkownika wynikających z nowej szwajcarskiej ustawy o ochronie danych („nDSG”).

Gdy użytkownik tworzy profil w jednej z naszych Usług, niektóre z jego danych osobowych, takie jak nazwa użytkownika, imię i nazwisko, wiek, płeć i orientacja seksualna, zgodnie z ustawieniami prywatności użytkownika mogą być widoczne również dla użytkowników odpowiedniej Usługi i innych naszych Usług, a także innych aplikacji, których jesteśmy właścicielem, oraz innych aplikacji i witryn internetowych niebędących naszą własnością, którym udostępniamy naszą platformę na żywo. Ci inni użytkownicy znajdują się na całym świecie. Aby zapoznać się z listą naszych obecnych partnerów na żywo, należy kliknąć [tutaj](https://talent.tagged.com/partner-policy-tagged.html).

Korzystanie z naszych Usług podlega naszym [Warunkom świadczenia usługi](https://secure.tagged.com/terms_of_service.html), w tym ich obowiązującym warunkom regulującym ograniczenia szkód i rozstrzygania sporów.

**Spis treści**

1. Zakres
    
2. Gromadzone dane osobowe
    
3. Cele gromadzenia i przetwarzania danych
    
4. Ujawnianie danych osobowych
    
5. Przekazywanie danych osobowych w kontekście krajów znajdujących się poza obszarem EOG / Wielkiej Brytanii / Szwajcarii
    
6. Pliki cookie, targetowanie i analityka
    
7. Wybory użytkownika dotyczące prywatności
    
8. Okres przechowywania danych osobowych
    
9. Zewnętrzne linki i funkcje
    
10. Treści generowane przez użytkowników
    
11. Bezpieczeństwo
    
12. Ochrona prywatności dzieci
    
13. Zmiany w niniejszej Polityce
    
14. Contact Us
    
15. Dodatkowe informacje dotyczące prywatności w niektórych jurysdykcjach

**1\. Zakres**

O ile poniżej nie opisano inaczej, niniejsza Polityka ma zastosowanie do danych osobowych gromadzonych i przetwarzanych przez firmę TMG w odniesieniu do: osób odwiedzających naszą witrynę internetową, w której zamieszczono niniejszą Politykę, w tym wszelkie nasze witryny internetowe, które zawierają linki do niniejszej Polityki lub ją publikują („ **Witryna** ”); osób, które pobierają naszą aplikację mobilną („ **Aplikacja mobilna** ”, np. Tagged lub Pets) i z niej korzystają; osoby, które rejestrują się lub uczestniczą w naszych wydarzeniach, ankietach, badaniach, promocjach i loteriach prowadzonych przez nas; osoby, które komunikują się lub w inny sposób wchodzą w interakcję lub angażują się w relacje z nami lub usługami dostępnymi za pośrednictwem naszych Witryn, Aplikacji mobilnej lub innych usług online (zwanych łącznie „ **Usługami** ”).

**2\. Gromadzone dane osobowe**

Jak opisano poniżej, możemy gromadzić dane osobowe bezpośrednio od użytkownika, ze źródeł zewnętrznych i automatycznie poprzez korzystanie przez użytkownika z naszych Usług.

**Dane osobowe zbierane bezpośrednio od użytkownika** . Chociaż gromadzone przez nas dane osobowe różnią się w zależności od korzystania przez użytkownika z naszych Usług i naszych interakcji z użytkownikiem, ogólnie możemy gromadzić następujące kategorie danych osobowych zebranych bezpośrednio od użytkownika:

* **Informacje kontaktowe** . Gdy użytkownik kontaktuje się z nami, w tym gdy wysyła nam wiadomość lub rejestruje się, aby dowiedzieć się więcej o naszych Usługach, możemy gromadzić imię i nazwisko użytkownika, adres e-mail, numer telefonu lub inne podobne identyfikatory, a także wiadomość użytkownika, charakter jego zapytania i wszelkie inne informacje, które zdecyduje się podać.
    
* **Informacje pochodzące z konta i profilu** . Gdy użytkownik rejestruje konto w związku z naszymi Usługami (np. konto aplikacji Tagged), możemy gromadzić imię i nazwisko użytkownika, adres e-mail, numer telefonu, adres (np. kod pocztowy), nazwę użytkownika i hasło, datę urodzenia i płeć, orientację seksualną, obraz i zdjęcie profilowe oraz informacje o adresie rozliczeniowym, a także wszelkie inne informacje dostarczone w związku z tworzeniem lub utrzymywaniem konta lub które w inny sposób użytkownik przekazuje nam za pośrednictwem swojego konta.

Jeśli użytkownik wybrał logowanie za pośrednictwem dostawców zewnętrznych, takich jak Facebook lub Apple lub za pośrednictwem wiadomości SMS, w procesie rejestracji nie wprowadza adresu e-mail ani hasła. Następnie użytkownicy uzyskują dostęp do naszej Usługi za pomocą podanego adresu e-mail i wybranego hasła (dane logowania) lub alternatywnie za pomocą danych logowania zewnętrznego dostawcy.

**Rejestracja przez serwis Facebook („Logowanie przez Facebook”)**

Umożliwiamy pojedyncze logowanie za pośrednictwem serwisu Facebook. Dzięki temu użytkownik może zarejestrować się za pośrednictwem swojego konta na Facebooku. Jeśli użytkownik korzysta z tej funkcji, my otrzymujemy i przetwarzamy następujące dane uwierzytelniające z serwisu Facebook w celu rejestracji: adres e-mail użytkownika, nazwę profilu, płeć, datę urodzenia i przechowywane tam zdjęcie profilowe. Dane są przesyłane w tym zakresie.

Gdy użytkownik loguje się do naszej witryny lub aplikacji za pośrednictwem serwisu Facebook, Facebook będzie również zbierać dane ze skryptów stron trzecich, przetwarzać je do celów analitycznych serwisu Facebook lub przekazywać je stronom trzecim. Polityka prywatności serwisu Facebook określa dane, które mogą być gromadzone, gdy użytkownik korzysta z logowania za pośrednictwem serwisu Facebook. Obejmuje to dane dotyczące urządzenia użytkownika, korzystania przez użytkownika z naszej Usługi, odwiedzonych przez użytkownika witryn internetowych oraz wyświetlanych reklam. Niestety ze względów technicznych użytkownik nie może odmówić tego przetwarzania w związku z korzystaniem z naszej Usługi. Jeśli użytkownik nie chce, aby Facebook gromadził dane na jego temat związane z korzystaniem przez użytkownika z naszej oferty online i wykorzystywał je do własnych celów, nie powinien korzystać z logowania za pośrednictwem serwisu Facebook.

Użytkownik może oddzielić swoje konto Tagged od konta w serwisie Facebook w dowolnym momencie. W takim przypadku konieczne będzie podanie przez użytkownika wyżej wymienionych danych dostępowych.

Więcej informacji na temat celu i zakresu gromadzenia oraz dalszego przetwarzania i wykorzystywania danych użytkownika przez serwis Facebook, a także praw użytkownika i opcji ustawień w celu ochrony jego danych można znaleźć w Polityce prywatności serwisu Facebook: [http://www.facebook.com/policy.php](http://www.facebook.com/policy.php).

**Rejestracja/logowanie przez serwis Google**

Jeśli użytkownik korzysta z urządzenia z systemem Android, oferujemy możliwość zarejestrowania się lub zalogowania się do naszej Usługi za pośrednictwem konta Google. Jeśli użytkownik wybierze to rozwiązanie, firma Google Ireland Limited, Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Irlandia („Google”) przekaże nam dane wymagane do rejestracji lub logowania (adres e-mail, imię i nazwisko, identyfikator konta Google i zdjęcie profilowe konta Google).

Nie mamy kontroli nad zakresem danych gromadzonych przez Google w przypadku logowania się za pośrednictwem serwisu Google. Jeśli użytkownik nie chce, aby serwis Google gromadził dane na jego temat związane z korzystaniem przez użytkownika z naszej oferty online i wykorzystywał je do własnych celów, nie powinien korzystać z logowania za pośrednictwem serwisu Google.

Więcej informacji na temat celu i zakresu gromadzenia oraz dalszego przetwarzania i wykorzystywania danych użytkownika przez serwis Google, a także praw użytkownika i opcji ustawień w celu ochrony jego danych można znaleźć w Polityce prywatności serwisu Google: [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

**Rejestracja/logowanie przez serwis Apple**

Jeśli użytkownik korzysta z urządzenia z systemem iOS, oferujemy możliwość zarejestrowania się lub zalogowania się do naszej Usługi za pośrednictwem Apple. Jeśli użytkownik wybierze opcję, firma Apple Inc, One Apple Park Way, Cupertino, California, USA, 95014 („Apple”) przekaże nam informacje, które użytkownik wybierze i które są wymagane do rejestracji lub logowania (np. wygenerowany przez Apple adres e-mail, imię i nazwisko).

Nie mamy kontroli nad zakresem danych gromadzonych przez Apple w przypadku logowania się za pośrednictwem serwisu Apple. Jeśli użytkownik nie chce, aby serwis Apple gromadził dane na jego temat związane z korzystaniem przez użytkownika z naszej oferty online i wykorzystywał je do własnych celów, nie powinien korzystać z logowania za pośrednictwem serwisu Apple.

Więcej informacji na temat celu i zakresu gromadzenia oraz dalszego przetwarzania i wykorzystywania danych użytkownika przez serwis Apple, a także praw użytkownika i opcji ustawień w celu ochrony jego danych można znaleźć w Polityce prywatności serwisu Apple: [https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/en/sign-in-with-apple/](https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/en/sign-in-with-apple/).

**Rejestracja/logowanie za pośrednictwem uwierzytelniania telefonicznego**

Jeśli użytkownik wybierze opcję rejestracji/logowania za pośrednictwem uwierzytelniania telefonicznego, oferujemy uwierzytelnianie za pomocą numeru telefonu komórkowego, dlatego użytkownik musi podać nam swój numer telefonu komórkowego. Następnie wyślemy wiadomość SMS z kodem weryfikacyjnym, który użytkownik musi wprowadzić w aplikacji, aby zakończyć proces rejestracji. Gdy użytkownik zechce się zalogować, wyślemy mu wiadomość SMS wraz z kodem, którego może użyć do zalogowania się na swoje konto. Dodatkowo zostanie przeprowadzony proces weryfikacji. Ta usługa jest świadczona przez firmę Sinch America Inc., firmę w stanie Delaware, Dział Prawny, 3500 Lenox Rd NE, Ste. 1875, Atlanta, GA 30326, Georgia, USA

i jest to możliwe tylko wtedy, gdy użytkownik wyrazi na to wcześniej zgodę.

Więcej informacji na temat celu i zakresu przetwarzania danych użytkownika przez Google można znaleźć w polityce prywatności firmy Sinch: [https://www.sinch.com/privacy-notice/](https://www.sinch.com/privacy-notice/).

* **Zakupy, płatności i nagrody** . Gdy użytkownik dokonuje zakupu lub płatności za pośrednictwem naszych Usług (np. w związku z funkcją naszej gry Pets), możemy gromadzić informacje, takie jak rodzaj płatności, dane karty płatniczej, rozliczenia, informacje o zakupach i wszelkie inne informacje finansowe lub handlowe niezbędne do realizacji naszych Usług.
    
* **Komunikacja i interakcje** . Gdy użytkownik wysyła wiadomość e-mail, dzwoni lub w inny sposób komunikuje się lub wchodzi w interakcję z nami lub z innymi użytkownikami TMG, w tym gdy zapisuje się na nasze listy mailingowe, wypełnia formularze w naszych Witrynach lub w Aplikacji mobilnej, wchodzi w interakcję z naszymi stronami mediów społecznościowych, publikuje recenzję lub referencje, przesyła treści w dowolnych internetowych grupach dyskusyjnych bądź w inny sposób wprowadza informacje do publicznych pól komentarzy, blogów lub forów społecznościowych sponsorowanych lub powiązanych z TMG, możemy gromadzić, otrzymywać i przechowywać zapisy danych kontaktowych, komunikacji i interakcji, wpisów lub zgłoszeń oraz naszych odpowiedzi, jeśli ma to zastosowanie.
    
* **Informacje promocyjne** . Jeśli użytkownik wyrazi zgodę na otrzymywanie od nas wiadomości marketingowych, możemy gromadzić jego imię i nazwisko, adres e-mail, numer telefonu, preferencje oraz, w stosownych przypadkach, informacje o jego koncie i profilu, w tym o Usługach i funkcjach, z których korzysta. Jeśli użytkownik uczestniczy w specjalnych działaniach, ofertach, programach lub promocjach, które oferujemy, możemy również gromadzić pewne dane kontaktowe, wiek użytkownika i wszelkie inne informacje, które mogą być wymagane przez prawo. Jeśli użytkownik wygra nagrodę w promocji, może być również konieczne zebranie pewnych informacji podatkowych i/lub zrzeczenia się i zgody, w zależności od nagrody.
    
* **Odpowiedzi i informacje zwrotne** . Jeśli użytkownik bierze udział w ankietach, kwestionariuszach lub działaniach badawczych lub inicjatywach prowadzonych przez nas, takich jak ocena satysfakcji użytkownika lub inne podobne cele, możemy zbierać odpowiedzi i opinie oraz wszelkie inne informacje, które użytkownik zdecyduje się podać.
    
* **Wydarzenia i szczegóły rejestracji** . Możemy również gromadzić dane osobowe związane z udziałem użytkownika w naszych wydarzeniach, a także inne wnioski, które użytkownik przesyła do nas w związku z naszymi Usługami. Na przykład, jeśli użytkownik zarejestruje się lub weźmie udział w wydarzeniu, które organizujemy lub sponsorujemy, możemy gromadzić informacje związane z jego rejestracją i uczestnictwem w takim wydarzeniu.
    
* **Preferencje i inne wnioski** . Możemy również gromadzić informacje o preferencjach użytkownika, w tym preferencjach dotyczących komunikacji, preferencjach związanych z korzystaniem z naszych Usług oraz wszelkich innych preferencjach lub wnioskach, które użytkownik przekazuje podczas interakcji z nami.

Ogólnie rzecz biorąc, użytkownik nie ma obowiązku przekazywania nam swoich danych osobowych. Korzystanie z niektórych Usług lub z niektórych cech naszych Usług może jednak wymagać podania danych osobowych, np. rejestracji konta w aplikacji Tagged. Jeśli wystąpi taka sytuacja, powiadomimy użytkownika o tym. Jeśli użytkownik nie chce przekazać nam wymaganych informacji, nie będzie mógł korzystać z danej usługi.

**Dane osobowe zebrane od stron trzecich** . Możemy również gromadzić i otrzymywać określone dane osobowe użytkownika od stron trzecich, takich jak partnerzy biznesowi, w szczególności w przypadku korzystania z dostawców sklepów z aplikacjami do zakupów, innych użytkowników TMG, dostawców usług analizy danych i marketingu, systemów operacyjnych i platform mediów społecznościowych, w szczególności w przypadku korzystania z opisanych powyżej funkcji logowania. Ponadto możemy gromadzić następujące informacje zebrane od stron trzecich:

* **Informacje z rejestracji w mediach społecznościowych i na platformie** . Podczas korzystania z naszych Usług użytkownik może udostępniać informacje lub treści, logować się do Usług lub rejestrować się w nich za pośrednictwem różnych platform mediów społecznościowych, serwisów społecznościowych bądź innych funkcji stron trzecich lub zintegrowanych usług. Gdy użytkownik łączy się z naszymi Usługami za pomocą swoich kont w mediach społecznościowych lub innych podobnych zintegrowanych usług i funkcji, możemy gromadzić lub otrzymywać dane osobowe o użytkowniku, które zapisał na swoim koncie w mediach społecznościowych, usłudze lub funkcji. Możemy na przykład gromadzić informacje z konta i profilu użytkownika, takie jak imię i nazwisko, adres e-mail, identyfikator użytkownika, zdjęcie profilowe, lista znajomych i inne podobne informacje dostępne na jego profilu. Użytkownik powinien sprawdzić swoje ustawienia prywatności na każdej platformie mediów społecznościowych, w funkcji lub zintegrowanej usłudze, aby lepiej zrozumieć, w jaki sposób jego dane osobowe mogą być wykorzystywane, ujawniane lub w inny sposób przetwarzane przez te strony.
    
* **Informacje związane z polecaniem** . Możemy zaoferować użytkownikowi możliwość zapraszania znajomych lub polecania innych użytkowników w celu uzyskania dostępu do naszych Usług lub korzystania z nich. W ten sposób możemy gromadzić i otrzymywać pewne dane osobowe dotyczące użytkownika, w tym od innych obecnych lub potencjalnych użytkowników serwisu TMG i klientów, którzy w podobny sposób angażują się w te działania.

**Dane osobowe zbierane automatycznie** . My i dostarczające nam usługi strony trzecie możemy automatycznie gromadzić lub uzyskiwać dane osobowe na temat użytkownika w związku z korzystaniem przez niego z naszych Usług, w tym za pomocą plików cookie, znaczników pikselowych i innych podobnych technologii. Dane osobowe, które możemy gromadzić automatycznie, obejmują:

* **Informacje o urządzeniu i przeglądaniu** . Gdy użytkownik korzysta z naszych Usług, możemy zbierać informacje o typie przeglądarki, nazwie domeny, odsłonach stron, czasie dostępu, znacznikach daty/godziny, systemie operacyjnym, języku, typie urządzenia, unikatowym identyfikatorze, dostawcy usług internetowych, odsyłających i wychodzących adresach URL, danych strumienia kliknięć oraz podobne informacje o urządzeniu i przeglądaniu.
    
* **Aktywność i sposób korzystania z usług** . Możemy również gromadzić informacje o aktywności związane z korzystaniem przez użytkownika z Usług, takie jak informacje o klikniętych linkach, wyszukiwaniach, używanych funkcjach, przeglądanych elementach, czasie spędzonym w naszych Usługach, interakcjach użytkownika z nami i innymi osobami w Usługach oraz inne podobne informacje o aktywności i sposobie korzystania z usług.
    
* **Informacje o lokalizacji** . Możemy również gromadzić lub uzyskiwać ogólne informacje o lokalizacji, takie jak adres IP użytkownika.

Aby uzyskać więcej informacji na temat korzystania przez nas z plików cookie i innych podobnych technologii, należy zapoznać się z poniższym punktem 6 „Pliki cookie, targetowanie i analizy”.

**3\. Cele gromadzenia i przetwarzania danych**

Możemy gromadzić, wykorzystywać, ujawniać i w inny sposób przetwarzać gromadzone przez nas kategorie danych osobowych w następujących celach:

* **Usługi i wsparcie** . Aby świadczyć i obsługiwać nasze Usługi (np. aplikację Tagged lub funkcję gry Pets), zarządzać kontem użytkownika, komunikować się z nim w sprawie korzystania przez niego z Usług, zapewniać rozwiązywanie problemów, wsparcie techniczne lub w podobnych celach związanych ze wsparciem, a także odpowiadać na zapytania użytkownika, realizować jego wnioski, ułatwiać przetwarzanie płatności oraz w inny sposób prowadzić naszą codzienną działalność. Obejmuje to udostępnianie niektórych danych osobowych użytkownika, takich jak identyfikator użytkownika, imię i nazwisko użytkownika, dane kontaktowe wybrane w ustawieniach prywatności, które są widoczne dla innych użytkowników odpowiedniej Usługi lub innych naszych Usług oraz innych aplikacji, które posiadamy, a także innych aplikacji i witryn niebędących naszą własnością, z którymi dzielimy naszą platformę na żywo. Firma TMG opiera się na podstawie prawnej „wykonania umowy” (art. 6 ust. 1 lit. b) RODO i brytyjskiego RODO oraz art. 31 ust. 2 lit. b) nDSG). W zakresie, w jakim przetwarzamy dane osobowe użytkownika, aby były one widoczne dla użytkowników naszych innych Usług i innych aplikacji, których jesteśmy właścicielem, oraz innych aplikacji i witryn internetowych niebędących naszą własnością, z którymi dzielimy naszą platformę na żywo, TMG opiera się na podstawie prawnej „wykonania umowy” (art. 6 ust. 1 lit. b) RODO i brytyjskiego RODO oraz art. 31 ust. 2 lit. b) nDSG).

W odniesieniu do danych dotyczących lokalizacji, TMG opiera się na zgodzie wyrażonej przez użytkownika (art. 6 ust. 1 lit. a), art. 7 RODO).

W odniesieniu do orientacji seksualnej TMG opiera się na wyrażonej przez użytkownika wyraźnej zgodzie (art. 6 ust. 1 lit. a), art. 7, art. 9 ust. 2 lit. a) RODO / brytyjskiego RODO) lub na podstawie wyjątku w art. 9 ust. 2 lit. e) RODO / brytyjskiego RODO, pod warunkiem, że użytkownik publicznie ujawnił swoją orientację seksualną (np. w transmisji na żywo).

* **Analizy i ulepszenia** . Aby lepiej zrozumieć, w jaki sposób użytkownicy uzyskują dostęp do Usług i korzystają z nich, a także do innych celów badawczych i analitycznych, takich jak ocena i ulepszanie Witryny, naszych Usług, i operacji biznesowych, w tym w celu rozwoju naszych Usług i ich funkcji oraz do wewnętrznej kontroli jakości i celów szkoleniowych, firma TMG opiera się na podstawie prawnej „prawnie uzasadnionych interesów” (art. 6 ust. 1 lit. f) RODO / brytyjskiego RODO i art. 31 ust. 1 nDSG). W tym aspekcie firma TMG dąży do zrozumienia, w jaki sposób usługa działa z perspektywy biznesowej.

**Komunikacja** . Możemy komunikować się, aby odpowiadać na pytania, przesyłać żądane materiały, a także informacje i materiały dotyczące naszych Usług i ofert. Możemy również wykorzystywać te informacje do wysyłania użytkownikowi informacji administracyjnych, na przykład informacji dotyczących Usług i zmian w naszych warunkach świadczenia usługi i politykach. Firma TMG opiera się na podstawie prawnej „wykonania umowy” (art. 6 ust. 1 lit. b) RODO / brytyjskiego RODO i art. 31 ust. 2 lit. a) nDSG) lub – w przypadku braku umowy między danym użytkownikiem a TMG – podstawie prawnej „prawnie uzasadnionych interesów” (art. 6 ust. 1 lit. f) RODO / brytyjskiego RODO i art. 31 ust. 1 nDSG). W przypadku gdy firma TMG opiera się na podstawie prawnej „prawnie uzasadnionych interesów”, TMG realizuje swoje interesy w zakresie zapewniania wsparcia, a także w celu odpowiadania na żądania użytkownika, aby zapewnić jego satysfakcję.

* **Dostosowanie i personalizacja** . W celu ich dostosowania możemy wysyłać treści lub wyświetlać je w Usługach, w tym w celu oferowania personalizacji lokalizacji oraz w celu spersonalizowania w inny sposób doświadczeń i ofert użytkownika. Firma TMG opiera się na podstawie prawnej „wykonania umowy” (art. 6 ust. 1 lit. b) RODO i brytyjskiego RODO oraz art. 31 ust. 2 lit. b) nDSG.
    
* Media społecznościowe i inne platformy komunikacji. Zapewniamy użytkownikowi możliwość udostępniania informacji lub treści, logowania się lub rejestrowania się do Usług za pośrednictwem różnych platform mediów społecznościowych, serwisów społecznościowych bądź innych funkcji lub zintegrowanych usług stron trzecich. Aby umożliwić użytkownikowi logowanie lub rejestrowanie się do Usług, firma TMG opiera się na podstawie prawnej „wykonania umowy” (art. 6 ust. 1 lit. b) RODO i brytyjskiego RODO oraz art. 31 ust. 2 lit. b) nDSG). W innych przypadkach firma TMG opiera się na podstawie prawnej „prawnie uzasadnionych interesów” (art. 6 ust. 1 lit. f) RODO / brytyjskiego RODO i art. 31 ust. 1 nDSG). W związku z tym firma TMG realizuje swój interes polegający na umożliwieniu użytkownikom inicjowania określonej komunikacji z platformami społecznościowymi, serwisami społecznościowymi lub innymi funkcjami lub zintegrowanymi usługami stron trzecich, jeśli użytkownicy sobie tego życzą.
    
* **Marketing i reklama** . Możemy wysyłać materiały do celów marketingowych, reklamowych i promocyjnych. Na przykład w celu przesyłania użytkownikowi informacji promocyjnych dotyczących naszych Usług, w tym biuletynów, informacji o wydarzeniach TMG, webinariach, prezentacjach, wyprzedażach, ofertach, rabatach i nowych ofertach, a także wszelkich innych informacji, które użytkownik subskrybuje. Firma TMG opiera się na podstawie prawnej „udzielonej zgody” (art. 6 ust. 1 lit. a), art. 7 RODO i brytyjskiego RODO oraz art. 31 ust. 1 nDSG.

Możemy wysyłać materiały do celów autoreklamy / marketingu bezpośredniego za pośrednictwem promocyjnych wiadomości e-mail i/lub wiadomości push, ankiet (użytkownika) i zindywidualizowanych przewodników (wyłącznie produkty TMG). Podstawą prawną jest prawnie uzasadniony interes firmy TMG w marketingu bezpośrednim własnych produktów, jak również zapis w sekcji 7 ust. 3 niemieckiej ustawy o zwalczaniu nieuczciwej konkurencji (UWG).

* **Badania i ankiety** . Zastrzegamy sobie prawo do administrowania ankietami i kwestionariuszami, takimi jak badania rynku, badania satysfakcji użytkowników lub w innych podobnych celach. Firma TMG opiera się na podstawie prawnej „udzielonej zgody” (art. 6 ust. 1 lit. a), art. 7 RODO i brytyjskiego RODO oraz art. 31 ust. 1 nDSG.
    
* **Rozwój wiedzy i poprawa jakości danych** . Możemy łączyć dane osobowe gromadzone za pośrednictwem Usług z innymi informacjami, które my lub strony trzecie gromadzimy na temat użytkownika w innych kontekstach. W większości przypadków informacje, które możemy łączyć z danymi osobowymi zebranymi za pośrednictwem Usług na potrzeby badań rynkowych, takie jak informacje demograficzne, nie identyfikują bezpośrednio użytkowników. Firma TMG opiera się na podstawie prawnej „prawnie uzasadnionych interesów” (art. 6 ust. 1 lit. f) RODO / brytyjskiego RODO i art. 31 ust. 1 nDSG). W tym aspekcie firma TMG dąży do zrozumienia, w jaki sposób usługa działa z perspektywy biznesowej.
    
* **Przechowywanie informacji na urządzeniu końcowym użytkownika i dostęp do nich** . Możemy przechowywać informacje na urządzeniu końcowym użytkownika lub uzyskiwać do nich dostęp. Firma TMG opiera się na podstawie prawnej „udzielonej zgody” art. 5 ust. 3 dyrektywy o prywatności i łączności elektronicznej oraz przepisów dotyczących prywatności i łączności elektronicznej (PECR) Reg. 6(4), gdy nie jest to bezwzględnie konieczne do działania naszej witryny internetowej, jak również do świadczenia usług telemedialnych wyraźnie zażądanych przez użytkownika.
    
* **Planowanie wydarzeń i zarządzanie nimi** . Możemy korzystać z danych osobowych na potrzeby planowania wydarzeń i innych celów związanych z zarządzaniem, takich jak rejestracja na wydarzenia i uczestnictwo, łączenie użytkownika z innymi uczestnikami wydarzeń i użytkownikami TMG oraz kontaktowanie się z użytkownikiem w sprawie odpowiednich wydarzeń, prezentacji i naszych Usług. Możemy również wykorzystywać dane osobowe do celów ułatwiania wydarzeń specjalnych, loterii, konkursów i promocji, które mogą mieć własne określone zasady uczestnictwa. Firma TMG opiera się na podstawie prawnej „udzielonej zgody” (art. 6 ust. 1 lit. a), art. 7 RODO i brytyjskiego RODO oraz art. 31 ust. 1 nDSG.
    
* **Bezpieczeństwo i ochrona praw** . Sekcja to opisuje podejmowane działania, aby chronić Usługi i nasze operacje biznesowe, nasze prawa oraz prawa naszych interesariuszy i inwestorów, aby wykrywać oszustwa, nieautoryzowane działania i dostęp oraz inne niewłaściwe korzystanie z naszej Witryny oraz zapobiegać im, w tym w przypadku, gdy uważamy, że konieczne jest zbadanie, zapobieganie lub podjęcie działań w związku z nielegalnymi działaniami, podejrzewanymi oszustwami, sytuacjami związanymi z potencjalnymi zagrożeniami dla bezpieczeństwa lub praw jakiejkolwiek osoby lub strony trzeciej albo naruszeniami naszych Warunków. Firma TMG opiera się na podstawie prawnej „prawnie uzasadnionych interesów” (art. 6 ust. 1 lit. f) RODO / brytyjskiego RODO i art. 31 ust. 1 nDSG). Prawnie uzasadniony interes firmy TMG i użytkowników TMG, którzy korzystają z serwisu TMG, nie jest nadużywany do działań umownych i/lub niezgodnych z prawem osób trzecich. Naszym prawnie uzasadnionym interesem jest również ochrona naszych własnych systemów zabezpieczających IT używanych w TMG, a tym samym ostatecznie ochrona danych osobowych użytkowników TMG. W odniesieniu do orientacji seksualnej firma TMG dodatkowo opiera się na podstawie prawnej, jaką jest ustalenie, dochodzenie lub obrona roszczeń (art. 9 ust. 2 lit. f) RODO / brytyjskiego RODO).
    
* **Zgodność z przepisami i proces prawny** . Podejmujemy działania w celu spełnienia obowiązków prawnych lub regulacyjnych, w tym ustawowych obowiązków przechowywania lub, w przypadku postępowania sądowego, w celu udzielenia odpowiedzi na wezwanie sądowe, nakaz (w tym sądowy) lub inny proces prawny bądź w ramach dochodzenia lub wniosku, formalnego lub nieformalnego, złożonego przez organy ścigania lub organ rządowy. Firma TMG opiera się na podstawie prawnej (i) „wypełnienia obowiązku prawnego” (art. 6 ust. 1 lit. c) RODO / brytyjskiego RODO oraz art. 31 ust. 2 lit. a) nDSG), jeżeli obowiązek ten wynika z prawa UE lub państwa członkowskiego UE, lub (ii) „prawnie uzasadnionego interesu” (art. 6 ust. 1 lit. f) RODO/brytyjskiego RODO oraz art. 31 ust. 1 nDSG), jeżeli obowiązek ten wynika z innych jurysdykcji. W przypadkach, w których prawnie uzasadnione interesy są istotne, firma TMG realizuje swoje interesy w zakresie wypełniania obowiązków prawnych, którym podlega TMG. W odniesieniu do orientacji seksualnej firma TMG dodatkowo opiera się na podstawie prawnej, jaką jest ustalenie, dochodzenie lub obrona roszczeń (art. 9 ust. 2 lit. f) RODO / brytyjskiego RODO).
    
* **Audyt, sprawozdawczość i inne operacje wewnętrzne** . Korzystamy z danych osobowych do przeprowadzania audytów finansowych, podatkowych i księgowych, audytów i ocen naszej działalności, w tym naszej prywatności, bezpieczeństwa i kontroli finansowych, a także w celach związanych z ryzykiem i zgodnością. Możemy również wykorzystywać dane osobowe do prowadzenia odpowiedniej dokumentacji biznesowej oraz w celu egzekwowania naszych zasad i procedur. Firma TMG opiera się na podstawie prawnej „prawnie uzasadnionych interesów” (art. 6 ust. 1 lit. f) RODO / brytyjskiego RODO i art. 31 ust. 1 nDSG). Prawnie uzasadnionym interesem TMG jest zabezpieczenie operacji biznesowych oraz regularne sprawdzanie, czy obowiązki w zakresie sprawozdawczości i zgodności są wypełniane.
    
* **Ogólne wsparcie biznesowe i operacyjne** . Korzystamy z danych osobowych w celu oceny i wdrażania fuzji, przejęć, reorganizacji, upadłości i innych transakcji biznesowych, takich jak finansowanie, oraz w celu administrowania naszą działalnością, księgowością, audytem, zgodnością, prowadzeniem dokumentacji i funkcjami prawnymi. Firma TMG opiera się na podstawie prawnej „prawnie uzasadnionych interesów” (art. 6 ust. 1 lit. f) RODO i art. 31 ust. 1 nDSG). W tym kontekście firma TMG ma interes w ujawnianiu i przetwarzaniu w inny sposób informacji o swoich aktywach i działalności potencjalnym nabywcom lub nabywcom i ich zewnętrznym doradcom w celu ułatwienia sprzedaży tych aktywów i/lub działalności.

Cele realizowane przez nas w związku z wykorzystywaniem plików cookie i podobnych technologii, w szczególności dotyczące targetowania i analityki, zostały opisane w sekcji 6 „Pliki cookie, targetowanie i analityka”.

Gdy podstawą prawną przetwarzania danych jest wyrażona na to zgoda użytkownika, użytkownik ma prawo wycofać swoją zgodę w dowolnym momencie. Wycofanie zgody nie będzie jednak miało wpływu na zgodność z prawem przetwarzania, którego dokonano na podstawie zgody użytkownika przed jej wycofaniem. Gdy podstawą prawną jest prawnie uzasadniony interes, użytkownik ma również prawo, co do zasady, do wniesienia sprzeciwu wobec przetwarzania jego danych osobowych, w dowolnym momencie, z przyczyn wynikających z jego szczególnej sytuacji. Ponadto użytkownik ma prawo w dowolnym momencie sprzeciwić się przetwarzaniu jego danych osobowych do celów marketingu bezpośredniego. W tym zakresie zastosowanie ma artykuł 21 RODO / brytyjskiego RODO.

Użytkownik może sprzeciwić się wykorzystywaniu przez nas jego adresu e-mail do celów promocyjnych lub osobistych wskazówek, podczas rejestracji lub później w dowolnym momencie.

**4\. Ujawnianie danych osobowych**

Możemy ujawniać gromadzone przez nas dane osobowe w celach opisanych powyżej, aby świadczyć użytkownikowi nasze Usługi, odpowiadać na wnioski użytkownika i je realizować, zgodnie z innymi zaleceniami lub zgodą użytkownika, a także następującym odbiorcom:

* **Marki oraz jednostki zależne i stowarzyszone** . Możemy ujawniać gromadzone przez nas dane osobowe naszym markom oraz jednostkom stowarzyszonym i zależnym.
    
* **Partnerzy biznesowi** . W niektórych okolicznościach firma TMG może współpracować z innymi firmami w celu oferowania swoich Usług, w tym w celu ułatwienia niektórych programów lub ofert specjalnych, a my możemy ujawniać dane osobowe tym partnerom biznesowym.
    
* **Sprzedawcy i dostawcy usług** . Możemy ujawniać gromadzone przez nas dane osobowe sprzedawcom i usługodawcom, którzy wykonują funkcje w naszym imieniu, takie jak IT i hosting stron internetowych, podmioty przetwarzające płatności, dostawcy usług marketingowych i badań marketingowych, obsługa klienta, przechowywanie danych, dostawcy usług analizy danych, audytorzy, konsultanci, doradcy i agenci oraz radcy prawni.
    
* **Inni użytkownicy TMG** . Możemy ujawniać gromadzone przez nas dane osobowe innym użytkownikom Usług w kontekście określonych funkcji o charakterze społecznościowym. Na przykład, jeśli użytkownik zaprasza innych do korzystania z naszych Usług bądź jeśli przesyła lub udostępnia informacje za pośrednictwem naszych publicznych, interaktywnych funkcji, forów społecznościowych lub blogów dyskusyjnych, w tym gdy publikuje recenzje lub referencje, niektóre dane osobowe mogą być dostępne i możliwe do przeszukiwania przez innych użytkowników Usług. Na przykład, jeśli użytkownik bierze udział w grze Pets, inni użytkownicy gry Pets będą mogli zobaczyć jego dane osobowe, takie jak zdjęcie profilowe, płeć, wartość, gotówka, aktywa, posiadane przez użytkownika zwierzęta i ich liczba.
    
* **Zewnętrzni dostawcy usług marketingowych i analitycznych** . Możemy również ujawniać dane osobowe użytkownika, takie jak informacje o urządzeniu i przeglądaniu oraz aktywności i użytkowaniu, zewnętrznym dostawcom usług marketingowych i analitycznych oraz innym firmom, które świadczą usługi marketingowe, reklamowe, w zakresie zarządzania kampaniami lub analityczne w naszym imieniu. Aby uzyskać szczegółowy przegląd konkretnych odbiorców, należy się zapoznać się z naszą platformą zarządzania zgodami w aplikacji.

Możemy również ujawnić dane osobowe użytkownika w następujących okolicznościach:

* **Wsparcie transferów biznesowych** . Jeśli my lub nasze podmioty stowarzyszone zostaną lub mogą zostać przejęte, połączone lub inna firma w nie zainwestuje bądź jeśli jakiekolwiek z naszych aktywów zostaną lub mogą zostać przeniesione do innej firmy, czy to w związku z postępowaniem w sprawie upadłości bądź niewypłacalności czy z innego powodu, możemy ujawnić lub przekazać dane osobowe, które zebraliśmy od użytkownika, od lub do innej firmy zgodnie z obowiązującymi przepisami prawa. Możemy również ujawnić pewne dane osobowe w razie potrzeby przed zakończeniem takiej transakcji lub innej transakcji korporacyjnej, takiej jak finansowanie lub restrukturyzacja, kredytodawcom, audytorom i doradcom zewnętrznym, w tym prawnikom i konsultantom.
    
* **Zgodność z przepisami i proces prawny** . Możemy również ujawniać dane osobowe stronom trzecim w zakresie wymaganym przez obowiązujące prawo i zobowiązania prawne. Na przykład możemy ujawniać informacje w odpowiedzi na wezwania sądowe, nakazy sądowe i inne zgodne z prawem żądania organów regulacyjnych, podmiotów rządowych i organów ścigania, w tym w odpowiedzi na wymogi bezpieczeństwa narodowego lub egzekwowania prawa, lub w inny sposób wymagany przez prawo lub proces prawny. Ponadto, jeśli zajdzie taka konieczność, możemy ujawnić imiona i nazwiska zwycięzców loterii i konkursów zgodnie z obowiązującym prawem.
    
* **Bezpieczeństwo i ochrona praw** . Możemy ujawniać dane osobowe w przypadku, gdy uważamy, że jest to konieczne w celu ochrony Usług, naszych praw i własności lub praw, własności i bezpieczeństwa innych osób. Na przykład możemy ujawniać dane osobowe w celu: (i) reagowania na oszustwa, nieautoryzowane działania i dostęp, nielegalne działania i niewłaściwe korzystanie z Usług, zapobiegania takiej aktywności oraz wykrywania i badania jej; (ii) zapobiegania sytuacjom związanym z potencjalnymi zagrożeniami dla zdrowia, bezpieczeństwa bądź praw osoby lub strony trzeciej; (iii) egzekwowania, wykrywania, badania i podejmowania działań w odpowiedzi na naruszenia naszych Warunków świadczenia usługi. Możemy również ujawniać dane osobowe związane ze sporami sądowymi i innymi roszczeniami lub postępowaniami prawnymi, w które jesteśmy zaangażowani, a także do celów naszej wewnętrznej księgowości, audytu, zgodności, prowadzenia dokumentacji i realizacji funkcji prawnych.
    
* **Inne okoliczności ujawniania danych osobowych** . Możemy ujawniać dane osobowe w inny sposób nieopisany powyżej, o którym powiadomimy użytkownika lub na który uzyskamy zgodę użytkownika bądź który jest w inny sposób dozwolony lub wymagany przez prawo.

Niezależnie od innych postanowień opisanych w niniejszej Polityce możemy wykorzystywać i ujawniać dane zagregowane, pozbawione elementów umożliwiających identyfikację i inne dane niepozwalające na identyfikację związane z naszą działalnością i Usługami w celu kontroli jakości, analizy, badań, rozwoju i innych celów. W przypadku wykorzystywania, ujawniania lub przetwarzania danych pozbawionych elementów umożliwiających identyfikację (dane, które nie są już w uzasadniony sposób powiązane lub możliwe do powiązania ze zidentyfikowaną bądź możliwą do zidentyfikowania osobą fizyczną, gospodarstwem domowym lub urządzeniem osobistym lub domowym), będziemy utrzymywać i wykorzystywać informacje w formie pozbawionej elementów umożliwiających identyfikację i nie będziemy podejmować prób ponownej identyfikacji informacji, z wyjątkiem sytuacji, gdy będzie to konieczne do ustalenia, czy nasze procesy usuwania elementów umożliwiających identyfikację są uzasadnione i zgodne z obowiązującymi przepisami o ochronie prywatności.

**5\. Przekazywanie danych osobowych w kontekście krajów znajdujących się poza obszarem EOG / Wielkiej Brytanii / Szwajcarii**

Odbiorcy danych osobowych mogą znajdować się poza obszarem EOG / Wielkiej Brytanii / Szwajcarii. W przypadku przekazywania danych osobowych do lokalizacji poza obszarem EOG / Wielkiej Brytanii / Szwajcarii (co obejmuje przekazywanie danych przez nas w USA jako administratora danych w zakresie objętym przepisami RODO / brytyjskiego RODO / nDSG do odbiorców w USA lub innych krajach poza obszarem EOG / Wielkiej Brytanii / Szwajcarii, które nie są objęte przepisami RODO / brytyjskiego RODO / nDSG), zgodnie z wymogami prawa zagwarantujemy, że prawa użytkownika do prywatności będą odpowiednio chronione, ponieważ Komisja Europejska zdecydowała, że kraj, do którego przekazywane są dane osobowe, zapewnia odpowiedni poziom ochrony (art. 45 RODO / brytyjskiego RODO) lub przekazanie odbywa się z zastosowaniem odpowiednich zabezpieczeń (np. uzgodnionych z odbiorcą standardowych klauzul umownych Unii Europejskiej dotyczących ochrony danych) (art. 46 RODO / brytyjskiego RODO), chyba że RODO / brytyjskie RODO przewiduje wyjątek (art. 49 RODO / brytyjskiego RODO). Ponadto zamierzamy w razie potrzeby uzgodnić z odbiorcami dodatkowe środki w celu zapewnienia odpowiedniego poziomu ochrony danych. Zobacz również art. 16 lit. f) ustawy nDSG w odniesieniu do ujawniania danych osobowych poza Szwajcarią.

W razie potrzeby zawieramy również odpowiednie „Uzupełnienie brytyjskie” z naszymi partnerami umownymi zgodnie z wymogami Biura Komisarza ds. Informacji (ICO) oraz odpowiednie „Uzupełnienie szwajcarskie” zgodnie z wymogami szwajcarskiego federalnego komisarza ds. ochrony danych i informacji (FDPIC).

Kopie odpowiednich zabezpieczeń (w zakresie, w jakim na nich polegamy) oraz listę odbiorców znajdujących się poza EOG / Wielką Brytanią / Szwajcarią można uzyskać pod adresem [support@themeetgroup.com](mailto:support@themeetgroup.com). Należy pamiętać, że taka kopia może zostać zredagowana w zakresie niezbędnym do ochrony tajemnic handlowych lub innych informacji poufnych.

**6\. Pliki cookie, targetowanie i analityka**

My i nasi zewnętrzni dostawcy usług używamy plików cookie, pikseli, lokalnych obiektów pamięci, plików dziennika i innych mechanizmów śledzących w celu automatycznego gromadzenia informacji o przeglądaniu, aktywności, urządzeniu i innych podobnych informacji w naszych Usługach. Używamy tych informacji, aby analizować i zrozumieć, w jaki sposób użytkownicy uzyskują dostęp do naszych Usług, korzystają z nich i wchodzą z nimi w interakcje, aby identyfikować i usuwać błędy i usterki w naszych Usługach, oceniać bezpieczeństwo, chronić, optymalizować i poprawiać wydajność naszych Usług, a także do celów marketingowych i analitycznych oraz do personalizowania treści w naszych Usługach. W zależności od lokalizacji użytkownika większość z nich zostanie użyta tylko wówczas, gdy użytkownik wyrazi na to zgodę za pomocą naszej platformy CMP, co jest możliwe z poziomu ustawień aplikacji i pozwala na zarządzanie zgodą / preferencjami dotyczącymi plików cookie, ukierunkowanych reklam i innych podobnych mechanizmów śledzenia w naszych Usługach, patrz punkt 7 „Wybory użytkownika dotyczące prywatności” poniżej. Wiele z tych opcji jest specyficznych dla przeglądarki i urządzenia, co oznacza, że może być konieczne ustawienie preferencji dla każdej przeglądarki i urządzenia, z którego użytkownik korzysta w celu uzyskania dostępu do naszych Usług. Ponadto, jeśli użytkownik usunie lub zablokuje pliki cookie, może być konieczne ponowne zastosowanie tych preferencji w każdej przeglądarce i/lub na każdym urządzeniu.

**Pliki cookie** . „Pliki cookie” to małe pliki tekstowe zapisywane na urządzeniu użytkownika (takim jak komputer lub smartfon) przez odwiedzaną witrynę internetową. Pliki cookie są tworzone przez serwer witryny i wysyłane do przeglądarki użytkownika, gdzie są przechowywane do wykorzystania w przyszłości. Niektóre pliki cookie pozwalają nam ułatwić użytkownikowi poruszanie się po naszych Usługach, podczas gdy inne są używane, na przykład aby umożliwić szybszy proces logowania, wspierać bezpieczeństwo i wydajność Usług lub umożliwić nam śledzenie zbiorczych i statystycznych informacji o aktywności użytkowników w Usługach.

**Znaczniki pikselowe** . Znaczniki pikselowe (czasami nazywane sygnalizatorami WWW lub czystymi plikami GIF) to małe grafiki z unikatowym identyfikatorem, podobne w działaniu do plików cookie. Podczas gdy pliki cookie są przechowywane lokalnie na urządzeniu użytkownika, znaczniki pikselowe są osadzane w niewidoczny sposób na stronach internetowych i treściach online. Możemy korzystać z nich w związku z naszymi Usługami, aby między innymi śledzić działania użytkowników oraz pomagać nam w zarządzaniu treścią i kompilowaniu statystyk użytkowania. Możemy ich również używać w naszych wiadomościach e-mail, aby uzyskać informację o tym, kiedy zostały otwarte lub przesłane dalej, dzięki czemu możemy śledzić wskaźniki odpowiedzi i oceniać skuteczność naszej komunikacji.

**Pliki dziennika** . Możemy zbierać pewne informacje o aktywności z plików dziennika. Informacje o plikach dziennika są zbierane automatycznie, gdy użytkownik uzyskuje dostęp do naszych Witryn. Rejestrujemy pewne informacje z tych plików dziennika, w tym żądania internetowe, adres IP, typ i wersję przeglądarki, informacje o języku, odsyłające i wychodzące adresy URL, kliknięte linki, przeglądane strony i inne podobne informacje.

**Analityka firm zewnętrznych** . Możemy korzystać ze zautomatyzowanych urządzeń, aplikacji i narzędzi, takich jak Google Analytics, które są obsługiwane przez firmy zewnętrzne, w celu oceny korzystania z naszych Usług. Te firmy zewnętrzne mogą wykorzystywać pliki cookie, znaczniki pikselowe i inne technologie śledzenia w celu gromadzenia danych dotyczących korzystania z naszych Usług oraz dostarczania nam raportów i wskaźników, które pomagają nam oceniać sposób korzystania z naszych Usług oraz poprawiać wydajność i wrażenia użytkowników. Aby dowiedzieć się więcej o praktykach Google w zakresie prywatności, należy się zapoznać z Polityką prywatności Google pod adresem [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). Użytkownik może również pobrać dodatek do przeglądarki blokujący Google Analytics, aby zapobiec wykorzystywaniu danych przez Google Analytics. Jest on dostępny pod adresem [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). Lista firm zewnętrznych zaangażowanych przez nas w tym zakresie znajduje się na naszej platformie CMP, która jest dostępna w ustawieniach aplikacji.

**Reklamy firm zewnętrznych** . Współpracujemy z zewnętrznymi sieciami reklamowymi, partnerami marketingowymi, sieciami reklam mobilnych i innymi („zewnętrznymi firmami reklamowymi”) w celu personalizacji treści i wyświetlania reklam w naszych Usługach, a także w celu zarządzania naszymi reklamami w witrynach internetowych firm zewnętrznych. My i te zewnętrzne firmy reklamowe możemy wykorzystywać pliki cookie, znaczniki pikselowe, zestawy SDK (zestawy do tworzenia oprogramowania) i inne narzędzia do gromadzenia informacji o przeglądaniu i aktywności w naszych Usługach (a także w witrynach i usługach firm zewnętrznych), jak również adres IP, unikatowy identyfikator, identyfikatory reklamowe plików cookie oraz inne identyfikatory online. My i te zewnętrzne firmy reklamowe wykorzystujemy te informacje, aby dostarczać użytkownikowi bardziej trafne reklamy i treści w naszych Usługach i w witrynach internetowych firm zewnętrznych, a także w celu oceny skuteczności takich reklam i treści. Listę zewnętrznych firm reklamowych można znaleźć na naszej platformie CMP, która jest dostępna w ustawieniach aplikacji.

**Korzystanie z różnych urządzeń** . My i nasi zewnętrzni dostawcy usług możemy wykorzystywać informacje, które zbieramy o użytkowniku (czy to bezpośrednio z naszych Witryn lub aplikacji mobilnej, za pośrednictwem urządzenia (urządzeń) użytkownika, czy ze źródeł zewnętrznych), aby pomóc nam i naszym zewnętrznym dostawcom usług zidentyfikować inne urządzenia, z których korzysta użytkownik (np. telefon komórkowy, tablet, inny komputer itp.). My i nasi zewnętrzni dostawcy usług możemy również wykorzystywać informacje o korzystaniu z różnych urządzeń i inne informacje, których się dowiadujemy o użytkowniku, aby wyświetlać ukierunkowane reklamy lub personalizować treści w naszych Usługach.

**Listy klientów i dopasowywanie** . Możemy udostępniać określone informacje z listy klientów (takie jak imię i nazwisko, adres e-mail i inne dane kontaktowe) firmom zewnętrznym, abyśmy mogli wyświetlać użytkownikowi bardziej ukierunkowane reklamy i treści w witrynach, na platformach i w usługach firm zewnętrznych. W niektórych przypadkach te firmy zewnętrzne mogą pomóc nam w rozszerzeniu naszych list klientów o dodatkowe informacje demograficzne lub inne podobne informacje, aby umożliwić nam lepsze ukierunkowanie naszych kampanii reklamowych i marketingowych.

**7\. Wybory użytkownika dotyczące prywatności**

**Zarządzanie preferencjami użytkownika** . Zapewniamy kilka możliwości zarządzania swoimi preferencjami i wyborami dotyczącymi prywatności, jak opisano poniżej:

* **Informacje pochodzące z konta i profilu** . Użytkownik może przeglądać i aktualizować niektóre z danych osobowych, które przechowujemy na jego temat. W tym celu należy zalogować się na swoje konto i zaktualizować informacje na koncie i w profilu.
    
* **Komunikacja marketingowa** . Możemy wysyłać do użytkownika okresowe promocyjne wiadomości e-mail, treści lub inne podobne komunikaty. Użytkownik może zrezygnować z tych wiadomości, postępując zgodnie z instrukcjami dostarczonymi w wiadomości. Jeśli użytkownik zrezygnuje z otrzymywania od nas treści promocyjnych, możemy nadal wysyłać mu wiadomości dotyczące jego konta lub wszelkich usług, które u nas zamówił lub otrzymał od nas. Ponadto użytkownik może zarządzać swoimi preferencjami komunikacyjnymi w ustawieniach konta i profilu.
    
* **Powiadomienia push** . Użytkownik może zarządzać rodzajem powiadomień push, które od nas otrzymuje. W tym celu należy dostosować ustawienia urządzenia mobilnego lub zmienić ustawienia w naszej aplikacji mobilnej. Są to wiadomości, które wysyłamy do użytkownika w związku z realizacją umowy, a także informacje promocyjne.

**Preferencje dotyczące plików cookie i śledzenia / ukierunkowanej reklamy / analiz** . Udostępniamy użytkownikowi również kilka sposobów zarządzania preferencjami dotyczącymi plików cookie, ukierunkowanych reklam, analiz i innych podobnych mechanizmów śledzenia w naszych Usługach. Wiele z tych opcji jest specyficznych dla przeglądarki i urządzenia, co oznacza, że może być konieczne ustawienie preferencji dla każdej przeglądarki i urządzenia, z którego użytkownik korzysta w celu uzyskania dostępu do naszych Usług. Ponadto, jeśli użytkownik usunie lub zablokuje pliki cookie, może być konieczne ponowne zastosowanie tych preferencji w każdej przeglądarce i/lub na każdym urządzeniu. Ponadto rezygnacja z plików cookie i reklam nie oznacza, że użytkownik nie będzie już otrzymywać od nas treści reklamowych. Użytkownik może nadal otrzymywać od nas ogólne lub „kontekstowe” reklamy.

* **Platforma zarządzania zgodami (CMP)** . Aby uniemożliwić plikom cookie lub innym mechanizmom śledzenia, które nie są bezwzględnie konieczne, śledzenie aktywności użytkownika w naszych Witrynach lub w naszej Aplikacji mobilnej, użytkownik może skorzystać z udostępnianej przez nas platformy zarządzania zgodami, przed użyciem plików cookie i mechanizmów śledzenia. Udzielona zgoda może zostać w dowolnym momencie wycofana i taki stan będzie uwzględniany w przyszłości. Aby uzyskać bardziej szczegółowe informacje, prosimy o zapoznanie się z punktem 15 „Dodatkowe informacje o prywatności w niektórych jurysdykcjach”, który zawiera dodatkowe informacje o prawach do prywatności dla mieszkańców niektórych jurysdykcji.
    
* **Ustawienia plików cookie** . Aby uniemożliwić plikom cookie śledzenie aktywności użytkownika w naszych Witrynach lub wizyt na wielu witrynach internetowych, użytkownik może skonfigurować przeglądarkę tak, aby blokowała określone pliki cookie lub powiadamiała go o pojawieniu się pliku cookie. Użytkownik może również usunąć pliki cookie. Opcja „Pomoc” na pasku narzędzi w większości przeglądarek zawiera informacje na temat tego, jak uniemożliwić swojemu urządzeniu akceptowanie nowych plików cookie, jak sprawić, by przeglądarka powiadamiała użytkownika, gdy otrzyma nowy plik cookie, lub jak usunąć pliki cookie. Odwiedzający nasze Witryny, którzy wyłączą pliki cookie, będą mogli przeglądać Witrynę, ale niektóre funkcje mogą nie działać.
    
* **Sygnały przeglądarki** . W zakresie wymaganym przez obowiązujące prawo, jeśli nasze Witryny wykryją, że przeglądarka użytkownika przesyła sygnał preferencji rezygnacji, taki jak sygnał „globalnej kontroli prywatności” (lub GPC), zastosujemy ten sygnał i zrezygnujemy z kierowania plików cookie z naszej Witryny do konkretnej przeglądarki na urządzeniu użytkownika. Jeśli jednak użytkownik odwiedzi nasze Witryny na innym urządzeniu lub w innej przeglądarce na tym samym urządzeniu, będzie musiał wysłać sygnał GPC również dla tej przeglądarki i/lub urządzenia.
    
* **Programy wyboru reklam branżowych** . Użytkownik może również kontrolować sposób, w jaki uczestniczące zewnętrzne firmy reklamowe wykorzystują informacje, które zbierają o jego wizytach w naszych Witrynach i witrynach firm zewnętrznych, w celu wyświetlania mu bardziej trafnych, ukierunkowanych reklam. Aby uzyskać więcej informacji i pomoc związaną z mechanizmami śledzenia stron internetowych, należy odwiedzić witrynę [www.YourOnlineChoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/).

Rezydenci niektórych jurysdykcji mogą mieć dodatkowe prawa do swoich danych osobowych, jak określono poniżej w punkcie 15 zatytułowanym „Dodatkowe informacje dotyczące prywatności w niektórych jurysdykcjach”.

**8\. Okres przechowywania danych osobowych**

Przechowujemy dane osobowe użytkowników tak długo, jak jest to konieczne do realizacji celów wymienionych w punkcie 3 „Cele gromadzenia i przetwarzania danych” oraz punkcie 6 „Pliki cookie, targetowanie i analityka” lub tak długo, jak mamy prawnie uzasadniony interes w dalszym ich przechowywaniu. We wszystkich innych przypadkach usuwamy dane osobowe użytkownika, z wyjątkiem informacji, które musimy nadal przechowywać w celu zachowania zgodności z ustawowymi okresami przechowywania danych osobowych (na przykład wynikającymi z prawa podatkowego lub handlowego, np. informacje dotyczące faktur). Ograniczamy przetwarzanie danych osobowych, które są przechowywane wyłącznie ze względu na obowiązek ich przechowywania.

Informacje na temat czasu przechowywania plików cookie i innych mechanizmów śledzenia zamieszczono na naszej platformie CMP, którą można znaleźć w ustawieniach aplikacji.

**9\. Zewnętrzne linki i funkcje**

Nasze Usługi mogą zawierać łącza do witryn lub funkcji stron trzecich bądź zapewniać określone połączenia lub zintegrowane usługi stron trzecich. Jakikolwiek dostęp do takich powiązanych witryn internetowych lub funkcji i korzystanie z nich nie podlega niniejszej Polityce, lecz polityce prywatności tych stron trzecich. Nie ponosimy odpowiedzialności za praktyki informacyjne takich stron trzecich, w tym za gromadzenie, wykorzystywanie i ujawnianie przez nie danych osobowych użytkowników. Przed przejściem do tych witryn lub skorzystaniem z tych funkcji użytkownik powinien zapoznać się z polityką prywatności i warunkami świadczenia usług stron trzecich.

**10\. Treści generowane przez użytkowników**

Możemy oferować publicznie dostępne funkcje interaktywne, fora społecznościowe lub blogi dyskusyjne w związku z naszymi Usługami, które umożliwiają udostępnianie informacji o Usługach lub innych interesujących użytkownika kwestiach (np. recenzje, referencje i pytania). Użytkownik powinien mieć świadomość, że wszelkie wiadomości przesyłane lub publikowane w takich interaktywnych funkcjach Usług mogą być widoczne i możliwe do przeszukiwania przez inne osoby, w tym użytkowników TMG i innych użytkowników. Przesyłając wiadomości lub publikując treści w takich publicznych, interaktywnych funkcjach, użytkownik potwierdza, że nie oczekuje prywatności ani poufności treści, które przesyła do takich funkcji, niezależnie od tego, czy zawierają one jego dane osobowe.

**11\. Bezpieczeństwo**

Wdrożyliśmy uzasadnione środki ostrożności mające na celu ochronę gromadzonych przez nas informacji przed utratą, niewłaściwym wykorzystaniem i nieuprawnionym dostępem, ujawnieniem, zmianą i zniszczeniem. Należy jednak pamiętać, że pomimo naszych najlepszych starań żadne środki bezpieczeństwa danych nie mogą zagwarantować bezpieczeństwa.

**12\. Ochrona prywatności dzieci**

Nasze Usługi nie są przeznaczone dla dzieci i nie zbieramy świadomie danych osobowych od dzieci w wieku poniżej osiemnastu (18) lat. Jeśli dowiemy się, że za pomocą Usług zostały zebrane dane osobowe od osób poniżej 18. roku życia, podejmiemy odpowiednie kroki w celu usunięcia tych informacji. Jeśli użytkownik jest rodzicem lub opiekunem prawnym i uważa, że zebraliśmy informacje od jego dziecka w sposób naruszający obowiązujące prawo, prosimy o skontaktowanie się z nami za pomocą poniższych danych kontaktowych.

**13\. Zmiany w niniejszej Polityce**

Niniejsza Polityka jest aktualna na dzień określony powyżej. Od czasu do czasu możemy zmieniać, aktualizować lub modyfikować niniejszą Politykę, więc należy pamiętać, aby ją okresowo sprawdzać. Wszelkie aktualizacje niniejszej Polityki będą publikowane tutaj. Jeśli wprowadzimy jakiekolwiek zmiany w niniejszej Polityce, które w istotny sposób wpłyną na nasze praktyki dotyczące wykorzystywania przez nas danych osobowych zebranych wcześniej zebraliśmy od użytkownika, dołożymy wszelkich starań, aby przekazać użytkownikowi powiadomienie, na przykład wysyłając mu wiadomość e-mail lub publikując wyraźne powiadomienie w naszych Witrynach, w naszej Aplikacji mobilnej lub w naszych Usługach.

**14\. Kontakt**

W przypadku pytań lub wątpliwości dotyczących niniejszej Polityki lub naszych praktyk w zakresie ochrony prywatności należy do nas wiadomość na adres [support@themeetgroup.com](mailto:support@themeetgroup.com) lub napisać do nas na adres:

The Meet Group, Inc.

100 Union Square Drive

New Hope, PA 18938

Można skontaktować się z naszym inspektorem ochrony danych pod adresem:

ePrivacy GmbH, reprezentowana przez prof. dr. Christopha Bauera, Große Bleichen 21, 20354 Hamburg, [privacy@themeetgroup.com](mailto:privacy@themeetgroup.com)

W przypadku wszelkich kwestii dotyczących bezpieczeństwa danych prosimy o kontakt z naszym inspektorem ochrony danych pod adresem [privacy@themeetgroup.com](mailto:privacy@themeetgroup.com).

Z naszym przedstawicielem w UE zgodnie z art. 27 RODO można skontaktować się pod adresem: ParshipMeet Holding GmbH, Speersort 10, 20095 Hamburg, e-mail: [privacy@parshipmeet.com](mailto:privacy@parshipmeet.com)

Dane naszego przedstawiciela w Wielkiej Brytanii zgodnie z art. 27 brytyjskiego RODO są podane w punkcie 15.B. „Dodatkowe informacje dla mieszkańców Wielkiej Brytanii”.

Dane naszego przedstawiciela w Szwajcarii zgodnie z art. 14 nDSG (new Swiss Data Protection Act) są podane w punkcie 15.C „Dodatkowe informacje dla mieszkańców Szwajcarii”.

Treforma AG c/o MLL Legal; Grabenstrasse 25; 6340 Baar; Switzerland; [meetgroup@dsg-mll.com](mailto:meetgroup@dsg-mll.com)

**15\. Dodatkowe informacje dotyczące prywatności w niektórych jurysdykcjach**

Rezydentom niektórych jurysdykcji przysługują dodatkowe prawa na mocy obowiązujących przepisów o ochronie prywatności, jak opisano w tym punkcie.

**A. RODO**

Jeśli użytkownik jest rezydentem Unii Europejskiej, przysługują mu na mocy RODO następujące prawa pod warunkiem spełnienia określonych w nim wymogów prawnych:

**Prawo dostępu** – użytkownik może zażądać informacji na temat przetwarzania jego danych osobowych oraz kopii przetwarzanych danych osobowych, o ile taka kopia nie wpływa niekorzystnie na prawa i wolności innych osób i nie ma zastosowania żadne inne odstępstwo.

**Prawo do sprostowania danych** – użytkownik może zażądać sprostowania swoich danych osobowych, które są niedokładne, i/lub uzupełnienia danych, które są niekompletne.

**Prawo do usunięcia danych** – użytkownik może zażądać usunięcia swoich danych osobowych, w szczególności gdy

* dane osobowe nie są już potrzebne w związku z celami, do których zostały zebrane lub w inny sposób przetwarzane;
    
* użytkownik wycofał swoją zgodę, na której opierało się przetwarzanie, i nie ma innej podstawy prawnej przetwarzania;
    
* użytkownik wniósł sprzeciw wobec przetwarzania danych opartego na podstawie prawnej „prawnie uzasadnionych interesów” i nie występują nadrzędne, prawnie uzasadnione podstawy przetwarzania lub użytkownik wniósł sprzeciw wobec przetwarzania na potrzeby marketingu bezpośredniego;
    
* dane osobowe użytkownika były przetwarzane niezgodnie z prawem lub
    
* dane osobowe użytkownika muszą zostać usunięte w celu spełnienia obowiązku prawnego, któremu podlegamy.

Prawo do usunięcia danych nie ma jednak zastosowania w szczególności w sytuacji, gdy przetwarzanie danych osobowych użytkownika jest niezbędne do wypełnienia obowiązku prawnego lub do ustalenia, dochodzenia lub obrony roszczeń.

**Prawo do ograniczenia przetwarzania danych** – użytkownik może zażądać ograniczenia przetwarzania danych

* przez okres, w którym weryfikujemy prawidłowość jego danych osobowych, jeśli użytkownik zakwestionował prawidłowość swoich danych osobowych;
    
* gdy przetwarzanie jest niezgodne z prawem, a zamiast usunięcia danych użytkownik zażąda ograniczenia ich przetwarzania;
    
* gdy nie potrzebujemy już danych osobowych użytkownika, ale użytkownik potrzebuje ich w celu ustalenia, dochodzenia lub obrony roszczeń; lub
    
* jeśli użytkownik sprzeciwił się przetwarzaniu, które opiera się na podstawie prawnej „prawnie uzasadnionych interesów” do czasu zweryfikowania, czy nasze uzasadnione podstawy są nadrzędne wobec interesów, praw i wolności użytkownika.

**Prawo do przenoszenia danych** – użytkownik może zażądać otrzymania swoich danych osobowych, które nam dostarczył, w ustrukturyzowanym, powszechnie używanym formacie nadającym się do odczytu maszynowego i przekazania tych danych innemu administratorowi bez przeszkód z naszej strony, w przypadku gdy przetwarzanie odbywa się na podstawie zgody lub w celu wykonania umowy oraz jest realizowane w zautomatyzowany sposób. W takich przypadkach użytkownik może również zażądać, aby dane osobowe zostały przesłane bezpośrednio innemu administratorowi, o ile jest to technicznie wykonalne.

Ponadto użytkownikowi przysługują następujące prawa:

**Prawo do wycofania zgody** – użytkownik może wycofać swoją zgodę w dowolnym momencie, gdy przetwarzanie odbywa się na podstawie jego zgody, bez wpływu na zgodność z prawem przetwarzania na podstawie zgody, które odbywało się przed jej wycofaniem.

**Prawo do sprzeciwu –**

**użytkownik ma prawo do wniesienia sprzeciwu w dowolnym momencie, w związku ze swoją szczególną sytuacją, wobec przetwarzania danych osobowych użytkownika, które opiera się na podstawie prawnie uzasadnionych interesów naszych lub strony trzeciej (art. 6 ust. 1 lit. f) RODO). W takim przypadku nie będziemy już przetwarzać danych osobowych użytkownika w celu, przeciwko któremu użytkownik wyraził sprzeciw, chyba że będziemy w stanie wykazać ważne, prawnie uzasadnione podstawy przetwarzania, które są nadrzędne wobec interesów, praw i wolności użytkownika, lub w celu ustalenia, dochodzenia lub obrony roszczeń.**

**Ponadto użytkownik ma prawo w dowolnym momencie sprzeciwić się przetwarzaniu swoich danych osobowych do celów marketingu bezpośredniego. W przypadku gdy użytkownik sprzeciwi się przetwarzaniu danych osobowych do celów marketingu bezpośredniego, nie będziemy już przetwarzać jego danych osobowych do takich celów.**

* * *

**Prawo do wniesienia skargi** – użytkownik może wnieść skargę do organu nadzorczego, w szczególności w państwie członkowskim swojego zwykłego pobytu, miejsca pracy lub miejsca popełnienia domniemanego naruszenia, jeżeli uważa, że przetwarzanie jego danych osobowych narusza postanowienia RODO.

Właściwym dla nas organem ochrony danych jest:

Wolne i Hanzeatyckie Miasto Hamburg, Hamburski Komisarz ds. Ochrony Danych i Wolności Informacji, Ludwig-Erhard-Str. 22, 20459 Hamburg, e-mail: [mailbox@datenschutz.hamburg.de](mailto:mailbox@datenschutz.hamburg.de)

**B. Brytyjskie RODO**

Jeśli użytkownik jest rezydentem Wielkiej Brytanii, przysługują mu określone prawa zgodnie z brytyjskim RODO i przepisami o ochronie danych. To, czy i w jakim zakresie prawa te mają zastosowanie, może zależeć od pewnych okoliczności. Aby skorzystać z któregokolwiek z tych praw, użytkownik może skorzystać z danych kontaktowych podanych poniżej. Są to następujące prawa:

**Prawo do informacji** – użytkownik ma prawo do otrzymywania zwięzłych, przejrzystych, zrozumiałych i łatwo dostępnych informacji na temat swoich danych osobowych i sposobie ich wykorzystywania przez nas. Wszelkie informacje na ten temat są zawarte w niniejszej Polityce, ale jeśli użytkownik ma dodatkowe pytania lub wątpliwości, zachęcamy do skorzystania z danych kontaktowych podanych poniżej.

**Prawo dostępu** – użytkownik ma prawo zażądać wydania kopii swoich danych osobowych. Prawo to ma zastosowanie zawsze, ale istnieją pewne wyjątki od jego stosowania, co oznacza, że nie zawsze użytkownik może otrzymać wszystkie informacje, których zażąda. Kiedy użytkownik zażąda dostępu do swoich danych osobowych, określa się to jako złożenie wniosku o dostęp do danych osoby, której dane dotyczą (DSAR). Po otrzymaniu od użytkownika wniosku DSAR mamy prawo zażądać okazania dokumentu tożsamości, aby zweryfikować tożsamość użytkownika składającego wniosek.

**Prawo do sprostowania danych** – użytkownik ma prawo zażądać sprostowania danych osobowych, które uważa za niedokładne. Użytkownik ma również prawo zażądać uzupełnienia informacji, które uważa za niekompletne.

**Prawo do usunięcia danych** – w pewnych okolicznościach użytkownik ma prawo zażądać usunięcia swoich danych osobowych. Zastrzegamy sobie prawo odmowy spełnienia żądania usunięcia danych, jeśli przetwarzamy dane osobowe z jednego z następujących powodów:

* W związku z korzystaniem z prawa do wolności wypowiedzi i informacji.
    
* W celu spełnienia obowiązku prawnego.
    
* W związku z wykonywaniem zadań w interesie publicznym lub w imieniu władz publicznych.
    
* W celu archiwizacji w interesie publicznym, badań naukowych, badań historycznych lub celów statystycznych.
    
* W celu dochodzenia lub obrony roszczeń prawnych.

**Prawo do ograniczenia przetwarzania danych** – w pewnych okolicznościach użytkownik może zażądać ograniczenia przetwarzania danych osobowych. W takim przypadku nadal będziemy przechowywać dane, ale nie będziemy ich dalej przetwarzać. Prawo to jest alternatywą dla prawa do usunięcia danych. Jeśli ma zastosowanie jeden z poniższych warunków, użytkownik może skorzystać z prawa do ograniczenia przetwarzania danych:

* Kwestionowana jest dokładność danych osobowych.
    
* Przetwarzanie danych osobowych jest niezgodne z prawem.
    
* Nie potrzebujemy już przetwarzać danych osobowych, ale dane osobowe są wymagane jako część procesu prawnego.
    
* Użytkownik skorzystał z prawa do sprzeciwu, a przetwarzanie jest ograniczone do czasu podjęcia decyzji o statusie przetwarzania.

**Prawo do sprzeciwu wobec przetwarzania danych – użytkownik ma prawo w dowolnym momencie sprzeciwić się przetwarzaniu swoich danych osobowych, w tym do celów marketingu bezpośredniego. Użytkownik może również wyrazić sprzeciw, jeśli przetwarzanie odbywa się na podstawie naszych prawnie uzasadnionych interesów (lub interesów strony trzeciej). W takim przypadku nie będziemy już przetwarzać danych osobowych użytkownika w celu, przeciwko któremu użytkownik wyraził sprzeciw, chyba że będziemy w stanie wykazać ważne, prawnie uzasadnione podstawy przetwarzania, które są nadrzędne wobec interesów, praw i wolności użytkownika, lub w celu ustalenia, dochodzenia lub obrony roszczeń.**

**Prawo do przenoszenia danych** – użytkownik może zażądać otrzymania swoich danych osobowych, które nam dostarczył, w ustrukturyzowanym, powszechnie używanym formacie nadającym się do odczytu maszynowego w przypadku, gdy przetwarzanie odbywa się na podstawie zgody lub w celu wykonania umowy i jest realizowane w zautomatyzowany sposób.

**Prawo do wycofania zgody** – użytkownik może wycofać swoją zgodę w dowolnym momencie, gdy przetwarzanie odbywa się na podstawie jego zgody, bez wpływu na zgodność z prawem przetwarzania na podstawie zgody, które odbywało się przed jej wycofaniem.

**Informacje kontaktowe**

Jeśli użytkownik chce skorzystać z któregokolwiek ze swoich praw lub ma pytania dotyczące wykorzystywania przez nas swoich danych osobowych, prosimy o skontaktowanie się z nami z użyciem informacji podanych w sekcji „Kontakt”. W takiej sytuacji należy podać wystarczające informacje, które umożliwią nam jednoznaczną identyfikację użytkownika.

Należy pamiętać, że wyznaczyliśmy przedstawiciela w Wielkiej Brytanii, z którym można kontaktować się zgodnie z art. 27 brytyjskiego RODO: eHarmony UK Ltd., 6-10 Great Portland Street, Londyn W1W 8QL, Wielka Brytania.

**Przekazywanie danych osobowych poza Wielką Brytanię**

Aby uzyskać szczegółowe informacje na temat ochrony i zabezpieczeń stosowanych do danych osobowych, gdy są one przekazywane poza Wielką Brytanię, prosimy zapoznać się z powyższym punktem 5 „Przekazywanie danych osobowych w kontekście krajów znajdujących się poza obszarem EOG / Wielkiej Brytanii / Szwajcarii”.

**Prawo do złożenia skargi do organu nadzorczego**

Użytkownik ma prawo złożyć skargę do organu ochrony danych.

Można się w tej sprawie skontaktować się z brytyjskim organem ochrony danych, tj. z Biurem Komisarza ds. Informacji, pod adresem: Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF, numer telefonu: + 44 (0) 303 123 1113, adres e-mail: [casework@ico.org.uk.](mailto:casework@ico.org.uk)

**C. Szwajcarskie prawo ochrony danych**

**Prawo dostępu** – użytkownik ma prawo zażądać wydania kopii swoich danych osobowych. Prawo to ma zastosowanie zawsze, ale istnieją pewne wyjątki od jego stosowania, co oznacza, że nie zawsze użytkownik może otrzymać wszystkie informacje, których zażąda. Kiedy użytkownik zażąda dostępu do swoich danych osobowych, określa się to jako złożenie wniosku o dostęp do danych osoby, której dane dotyczą (DSAR).

**Prawo do sprostowania danych** – użytkownik ma prawo zażądać sprostowania danych osobowych, które uważa za niedokładne. Użytkownik ma również prawo zażądać uzupełnienia informacji, które uważa za niekompletne.

**Prawo do usunięcia danych** – w pewnych okolicznościach użytkownik ma prawo zażądać usunięcia swoich danych osobowych. Zastrzegamy sobie prawo odmowy spełnienia żądania usunięcia danych, jeśli przetwarzamy dane osobowe z jednego z następujących powodów:

* W związku z korzystaniem z prawa do wolności wypowiedzi i informacji.
    
* W celu spełnienia obowiązku prawnego.
    
* W związku z wykonywaniem zadań w interesie publicznym lub w imieniu władz publicznych.
    
* W celu archiwizacji w interesie publicznym, badań naukowych, badań historycznych lub celów statystycznych.
    
* W celu dochodzenia lub obrony roszczeń prawnych.

**Prawo do ograniczenia przetwarzania danych** – w pewnych okolicznościach użytkownik może zażądać ograniczenia przetwarzania danych osobowych. W takim przypadku nadal będziemy przechowywać dane, ale nie będziemy ich dalej przetwarzać. Prawo to jest alternatywą dla prawa do usunięcia danych. Jeśli ma zastosowanie jeden z poniższych warunków, użytkownik może skorzystać z prawa do ograniczenia przetwarzania danych:

* Kwestionowana jest dokładność danych osobowych.
    
* Przetwarzanie danych osobowych jest niezgodne z prawem.
    
* Nie potrzebujemy już przetwarzać danych osobowych, ale dane osobowe są wymagane jako część procesu prawnego.
    
* Użytkownik skorzystał z prawa do sprzeciwu, a przetwarzanie jest ograniczone do czasu podjęcia decyzji o statusie przetwarzania.

**Prawo do sprzeciwu wobec przetwarzania danych** – użytkownik ma prawo w pewnych okolicznościach sprzeciwić się przetwarzaniu swoich danych osobowych. Użytkownik może również wyrazić sprzeciw, jeśli przetwarzanie odbywa się w związku z zadaniem wykonywanym w interesie publicznym, zadaniem wykonywanym na mocy powierzonej użytkownikowi władzy publicznej lub naszymi prawnie uzasadnionymi interesami (lub interesami strony trzeciej).

**Prawo do sprzeciwu wobec przetwarzania danych do celów marketingu bezpośredniego** – użytkownik może również w dowolnym momencie sprzeciwić się przetwarzaniu jego danych osobowych w celach reklamowych („sprzeciw dotyczący reklam”). Należy wziąć pod uwagę, iż ze względów organizacyjnych może wystąpić nakładanie się wniesionego przez użytkownika sprzeciwu i wykorzystania jego danych w kontekście już trwającej kampanii.

**Prawo do przenoszenia danych** – to prawo ma zastosowanie tylko wtedy, gdy przetwarzanie ma miejsce na podstawie zgody użytkownika lub w celu wykonania umowy oraz jest przeprowadzane w zautomatyzowany sposób.

Jeśli użytkownik chce skorzystać z któregokolwiek ze swoich praw, prosimy o skontaktowanie się z nami z użyciem informacji podanych w sekcji „Kontakt”. W takiej sytuacji należy podać wystarczające informacje, które umożliwią nam jednoznaczną identyfikację użytkownika.

**Informacje kontaktowe**

Jeśli użytkownik chce skorzystać z któregokolwiek ze swoich praw lub ma pytania dotyczące wykorzystywania przez nas swoich danych osobowych, prosimy o skontaktowanie się z nami z użyciem informacji podanych w sekcji „Kontakt”. W takiej sytuacji należy podać wystarczające informacje, które umożliwią nam jednoznaczną identyfikację użytkownika.

Warto pamiętać, że wyznaczyliśmy przedstawiciela w Szwajcarii, z którym można kontaktować się zgodnie z art 14 nDSG (nowej szwajcarskiej ustawy o ochronie danych): Treforma AG c/o MLL Legal; Grabenstrasse 25; 6340 Baar; Szwajcaria; [meetgroup@dsg-mll.com](mailto:meetgroup@dsg-mll.com)

**Przekazywanie danych osobowych poza Szwajcarię**

Aby uzyskać szczegółowe informacje na temat ochrony i zabezpieczeń stosowanych do danych osobowych, gdy są one przekazywane poza Szwajcarię, prosimy zapoznać się z powyższym punktem 5 „Przekazywanie danych osobowych w kontekście krajów znajdujących się poza obszarem EOG / Wielkiej Brytanii / Szwajcarii”.

**Prawo do złożenia skargi do organu nadzorczego**

Użytkownik ma prawo złożyć skargę do organu ochrony danych.

Użytkownik może również kontaktować się z właściwym organem nadzorczym ochrony danych w Szwajcarii. Jest to

federalny komisarz ds. ochrony danych i informacji (FDPIC).

Zachęcamy do kontaktowania się z nim pod adresem:

[https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/de/home/deredoeb/kontakt/kontaktformular\_bgoe.html](https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/de/home/deredoeb/kontakt/kontaktformular_bgoe.html)

**The Meet Group, Inc.**

Privacybeleid voor gebruikers die in de Europese Economische Ruimte of het Verenigd Koninkrijk wonen
====================================================================================================

_Laatst bijgewerkt: October 8, 2024_

The Meet Group, Inc., zijn merken, gelieerde bedrijven en dochterondernemingen vinden je privacy belangrijk. Dit Privacybeleid (' **Beleid** ') beschrijft hoe The Meet Group, Inc. (' **TMG** ', ' **we** ', ' **wij** ' of ' **ons** ') de in dit beleid beschreven persoonlijke gegevens (soms ook persoonsgegevens genoemd) verzamelen, gebruiken, verstrekken en anderszins verwerken, en de rechten en opties die je hebt met betrekking tot dergelijke persoonlijke gegevens.

Zie voor meer informatie over de privacyopties die je met betrekking tot je persoonlijke gegevens hebt paragraaf 7 'Je privacyopties', en paragraaf 15 'Aanvullende privacyinformatie voor bepaalde rechtsgebieden', die aanvullende informatie over privacyrechten bevat voor inwoners van bepaalde rechtsgebieden.

Als je inwoner van de Europese Unie (EU) of de Europese Economische Ruimte (EER) bent, dan vind je in paragraaf 15.A 'Aanvullende informatie voor inwoners van de EU/EER' meer informatie over je rechten volgens de Algemene Verordening Gegevensbescherming ('AVG') .

Als je inwoner van het Verenigd Koninkrijk (VK) bent, dan vind je in paragraaf 15.B 'Aanvullende informatie voor inwoners van het VK' meer informatie over je rechten volgens de General Data Protection Regulation zoals opgenomen in de wetgeving van het Verenigd Koninkrijk krachtens paragraaf 3 van de 'European Union (Withdrawal) Act 2018' ('UK GDPR') van het Verenigd Koninkrijk.

Als je inwoner van Zwitserland bent, dan vind je in paragraaf 15.C 'Aanvullende informatie voor inwoners van Zwitserland' meer informatie over je rechten volgens de nieuwe Zwitserse gegevensbeschermingswet ('nDSG').

Als je op een van onze Diensten een profiel aanmaakt, dan kunnen sommige van je persoonlijke gegevens, zoals gebruikersnaam, naam, leeftijd, geslacht en seksuele geaardheid, in overeenstemming met je privacyinstellingen ook zichtbaar zijn voor gebruikers van de betreffende Dienst en van onze andere Diensten, en andere applicaties die ons eigendom zijn en andere applicaties en websites die geen eigendom van ons zijn waarmee we ons live platform delen. Die andere gebruikers kunnen zich overal ter wereld bevinden. Klik [hier](https://talent.tagged.com/partner-policy-tagged.html) voor een lijst van onze huidige live partners.

Op je gebruik van de Diensten zijn onze [Algemene Voorwaarden](https://secure.tagged.com/terms_of_service.html) inclusief de toepasselijke voorwaarden met betrekking tot de beperking van schadevergoedingen en de beslechting van geschillen van toepassing.

**Inhoudsopgave**

1. Toepassingsgebied
    
2. Verzamelde persoonlijke gegevens
    
3. Doelen van verzameling en verwerking
    
4. Verstrekking van persoonlijke gegevens
    
5. Doorgiftes van persoonlijke gegevens in de context van landen buiten EER/VK/CH
    
6. Cookies, targeting en analyses
    
7. Je privacyopties
    
8. Bewaartermijn van persoonlijke gegevens
    
9. Externe links en functies
    
10. Door gebruikers gegenereerde content
    
11. Beveiliging
    
12. Privacy van kinderen
    
13. Wijzigingen in dit beleid
    
14. Contact Us
    
15. Aanvullende privacyinformatie voor bepaalde rechtsgebieden

**1\. Toepassingsgebied**

Tenzij hieronder anders beschreven, is dit Beleid van toepassing op de persoonlijke gegevens die TMG verzamelt en verwerkt met betrekking tot: bezoekers van onze website waarop dit Beleid is geplaatst, inclusief al onze websites die naar dit Beleid linken of het plaatsen (de ' **Sites** '); personen die onze mobiele applicatie downloaden (' **Mobiele App** ', bijvoorbeeld de Tagged-app of de Pets-app); personen die zich registreren voor of deelnemen aan onze evenementen, enquêtes, onderzoeken, promoties en sweepstakes die door ons worden uitgevoerd; en personen die interacteren of op andere wijze communiceren met ons of de via onze Sites, Mobiele App of andere online Diensten beschikbare Diensten (gezamenlijk de ' **Diensten** ').

**2\. Verzamelde persoonlijke gegevens**

Zoals hieronder nader beschreven, kunnen we persoonlijke gegevens rechtstreeks via jou, via externe bronnen en automatisch via je gebruik van onze Diensten verzamelen.

**Rechtstreeks via jou verzamelde persoonlijke gegevens.** Welke persoonlijke gegevens we verzamelen, varieert afhankelijk van je gebruik van onze Diensten en onze interacties met jou, maar in het algemeen kunnen we de volgende categorieën persoonlijke gegevens rechtstreeks via jou verzamelen:

* **Contactgegevens** . Als je contact met ons opneemt, bijvoorbeeld als je ons een bericht stuurt of als je je registreert voor meer informatie over onze Diensten, dan kunnen we je naam, e-mailadres, telefoonnummer en andere vergelijkbare identificatiegegevens verzamelen, evenals je bericht, de aard van je vraag en alle andere gegevens die je besluit te verstrekken.
    
* **Account- en profielgegevens.** Als je je registreert voor een account in verband met onze Diensten (bijvoorbeeld voor een Tagged-account), dan kunnen we je naam, e-mailadres, telefoonnummer, adres (zoals postcode), gebruikersnaam en wachtwoord, geboortedatum, geslacht, seksuele geaardheid, profielafbeelding en -foto en factuuradres verzamelen, evenals alle andere gegevens die verstrekt worden in verband met het aanmaken of onderhouden van je account of die je anderszins via je account aan ons verstrekt.

Als je ervoor gekozen hebt je aan te melden via een externe provider zoals Facebook of Apple of per sms, dan voer je tijdens het registratieproces geen e-mailadres of wachtwoord in. Gebruikers krijgen vervolgens toegang tot onze Diensten met het e-mailadres dat ze verstrekt hebben en het wachtwoord dat ze gekozen hebben (aanmeldgegevens), of met de aanmeldgegevens van de externe provider.

**Registreren via Facebook ('Facebook-aanmelding')**

We bieden eenmalige aanmelding via Facebook. Dankzij deze optie kun je je registreren via je Facebook-account. Als je deze functie gebruikt, ontvangen en verwerken we van Facebook de volgende verificatiegegevens voor de aanmelding: je e-mailadres, profielnaam, geslacht, geboortedatum en de daar opgeslagen profielfoto. Hierbij worden gegevens doorgegeven.

Als je je op onze website of in onze app aanmeldt met Facebook, dan zal Facebook ook gegevens uit externe scripts verzamelen, en deze voor analyse door Facebook verwerken of doorgeven aan derden. Het Privacybeleid van Facebook beschrijft de gegevens die verzameld kunnen worden als je je aanmeldt via Facebook.Dit betreft onder andere gegevens over je toestel, je gebruik van onze Dienst, de websites die je hebt bezocht en de advertenties die je hebt gezien. Deze verwerking in verband met onze Dienst kun je technisch gezien helaas niet weigeren. Als je niet wilt dat Facebook gegevens over jou met betrekking tot je gebruik van ons onlineaanbod verzamelt en voor eigen doeleinden gebruikt, meld je dan niet via Facebook aan.

Je kunt je Tagged-account op elk gewenst moment loskoppelen van je Facebook-account. In dat geval dien je de eerdergenoemde toegangsgegevens te verstrekken.

Meer informatie over het doel en het toepassingsgebied van de verzameling, de verdere verwerking en het gebruik van je gegevens door Facebook en je rechten en instellingsopties voor de bescherming van je gegevens vind je in het Privacybeleid van Facebook: [http://www.facebook.com/policy.php](http://www.facebook.com/policy.php).

**Registreren/aanmelden via Google**

Als je een Android-toestel gebruikt, bieden wij je de mogelijkheid je via je Google-account te registreren of aan te melden bij onze Dienst. Als je dit doet, zal Google Ireland Limited, Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ierland ('Google') ons de voor het registreren of aanmelden vereiste gegevens (e-mailadres, naam en accountnaam en profielfoto van het Google-account) verstrekken.

Wij hebben geen controle over het toepassingsgebied van de gegevens die Google met aanmelden via Google verzamelt. Als je niet wilt dat Google gegevens over jou met betrekking tot je gebruik van ons onlineaanbod verzamelt en voor eigen doeleinden gebruikt, meld je dan niet via Google aan.

Meer informatie over het doel en het toepassingsgebied van de verzameling, de verdere verwerking en het gebruik van je gegevens door Google en je rechten en instellingsopties voor de bescherming van je gegevens vind je in het Privacybeleid van Google: [https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=nl](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

**Registreren/aanmelden via Apple**

Als je een iOS-toestel gebruikt, bieden wij je de mogelijkheid je via Apple te registreren of aan te melden bij onze Dienst. Als je ervoor kiest dat te doen, zal Apple Inc., One Apple Park Way, Cupertino, 95014, California, VS ('Apple') ons de gegevens verstrekken die je selecteert en die nodig zijn voor het registreren of aanmelden (bijvoorbeeld door Apple gegenereerd e-mailadres of naam).

Wij hebben geen controle over het toepassingsgebied van de gegevens die Apple met aanmelden via Apple verzamelt. Als je niet wilt dat Apple gegevens over jou met betrekking tot je gebruik van ons onlineaanbod verzamelt en voor eigen doeleinden gebruikt, meld je dan niet via Apple aan.

Meer informatie over het doel en het toepassingsgebied van de verzameling, de verdere verwerking en het gebruik van je gegevens door Apple en je rechten en instellingsopties voor de bescherming van je gegevens vind je in het Privacybeleid van Apple: [https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/nl/sign-in-with-apple/](https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/en/sign-in-with-apple/).

**Registreren/aanmelden via telefonische verificatie**

Bij registreren/aanmelden via telefonische verificatie bieden we je de mogelijkheid je via je telefoonnummer te verifiëren. Daartoe moet je ons je mobiele telefoonnummer verstrekken. We sturen je dan een sms met een verificatiecode die je in de app moet invoeren om het registratieproces te voltooien. Wanneer je je wilt aanmelden, sturen we je een sms met een code die je kunt gebruiken om je aan te melden bij je account. Daarnaast vindt er ook een verificatieprocedure plaats. Deze service wordt geleverd door Sinch America, Inc. (a Delaware corporation), Legal Department, 3500 Lenox Rd NE, Ste. 1875, Atlanta, GA 30326, Georgia, VS

en is alleen mogelijk als je ons vooraf je toestemming hebt gegeven.

Meer informatie over het doel en het toepassingsgebied van de verwerking van je gegevens door Sinch vind je in het privacybeleid van Sinch: [https://www.sinch.com/privacy-notice/](https://www.sinch.com/privacy-notice/)

* **Aankopen, betalingen en beloningen** . Als je een aankoop of betaling doet via onze Diensten (bijvoorbeeld in verband met onze Pets-game), dan kunnen we gegevens verzamelen zoals type betaling, betaalkaartgegevens, facturering, aankoopgegevens en andere financiële of commerciële gegevens die nodig zijn voor het faciliteren van onze Diensten.
    
* **Communicatie en interacties** . Als je e-mailt, belt of op andere manieren communiceert of interacties hebt met ons of met andere TMG-gebruikers, bijvoorbeeld als je je aanmeldt voor onze mailinglijsten, formulieren op onze Sites of in onze Mobiele App invult, gebruikmaakt van onze socialemediapagina's, een review of testimonial plaatst, content in online discussiegroepen plaatst of op andere manieren informatie invoert in publiek toegankelijke opmerkingenvelden, blogs of communityforums die gesponsord worden door of gelieerd zijn aan TMG, dan kunnen we je contactgegevens, berichten en interacties, je posts of bijdragen en indien van toepassing onze antwoorden verzamelen, ontvangen en bewaren.
    
* **Promotionele informatie** . Als je ermee instemt marketingcommunicatie van ons te ontvangen, dan kunnen we je naam, e-mailadres, telefoonnummer, voorkeuren en, indien relevant, gegevens over je account en profiel verzamelen, inclusief de Diensten en functies die je gebruikt. Als je deelneemt aan speciale activiteiten, aanbiedingen, programma's of promoties die wij aanbieden, kunnen we ook bepaalde contactgegevens, je leeftijd en andere gegevens verzamelen die mogelijk wettelijk vereist zijn. Als je een promotie wint, moeten we mogelijk ook bepaalde belastinggegevens en/of vrijstellingen en kwijtscheldingen verzamelen, afhankelijk van de prijs.
    
* **Antwoorden en feedback** . Als je deelneemt aan enquêtes, vragenlijsten of onderzoeksactiviteiten of -initiatieven die door ons worden uitgevoerd, bijvoorbeeld over gebruikerstevredenheid of voor andere soortgelijke doeleinden, kunnen wij je antwoorden en feedback verzamelen, evenals alle andere gegevens die je besluit te verstrekken.
    
* **Evenementen en registratiegegevens** . We kunnen ook persoonlijke gegevens verzamelen met betrekking tot je deelname aan onze evenementen en andere verzoeken die je bij ons indient met betrekking tot onze Diensten. Als je je bijvoorbeeld inschrijft voor of deelneemt aan een evenement dat wij organiseren of sponsoren, dan kunnen we gegevens verzamelen met betrekking tot je registratie voor en deelname aan een dergelijk evenement.
    
* **Voorkeuren en andere verzoeken** . We kunnen ook gegevens verzamelen over je voorkeuren, inclusief communicatievoorkeuren, voorkeuren met betrekking tot je gebruik van onze Diensten en eventuele andere voorkeuren of verzoeken die je doorgeeft tijdens je interacties met ons.

Over het algemeen ben je niet verplicht om ons je persoonlijke gegevens te verstrekken. Maar voor het gebruik van bepaalde Diensten of aspecten van onze Diensten kan het nodig zijn dat er persoonlijke gegevens worden verstrekt, bijvoorbeeld bij de registratie voor een Tagged-account. Als dat het geval is, zullen we je daarop wijzen. Als je ons de vereiste gegevens niet wilt verstrekken, kun je helaas geen gebruik maken van de betreffende Dienst.

**Via derden verzamelde persoonlijke gegevens** . We kunnen ook bepaalde persoonlijke gegevens over je verzamelen en ontvangen van externe bronnen, zoals van zakelijke partners, vooral bij gebruik van appstore-aanbieders voor aankopen, en van andere TMG-gebruikers, gegevensanalyse- en marketingaanbieders, besturingssystemen en socialemediaplatforms, vooral bij gebruik van de hierboven beschreven inlogfuncties. Verder kunnen we de volgende gegevens verzamelen van externe bronnen:

* **Socialemedia- en platformregistratiegegevens** . Als je onze Diensten gebruikt, kun je ervoor kiezen om informatie of content te delen, in te loggen of je aan te melden bij de Diensten via verschillende socialemediaplatforms, socialenetwerkdiensten of andere functies van derden of geïntegreerde diensten. Als je verbinding maakt met onze Diensten via je socialemedia-accounts of andere soortgelijke geïntegreerde diensten en functies, dan kunnen we persoonlijke gegevens over je verzamelen of ontvangen die je aan dat socialemedia-account, die dienst of die functie hebt verstrekt. We kunnen bijvoorbeeld gegevens verzamelen van je account en profiel, zoals je naam, e-mailadres, gebruikers-ID, profielfoto, vriendenlijst en andere soortgelijke gegevens die beschikbaar zijn op je profiel. Je dient je privacyinstellingen op elk socialemediaplatform, elke functie of elke geïntegreerde dienst te controleren om meer inzicht te krijgen in de manier waarop je persoonlijke gegevens kunnen worden gebruikt, verstrekt of anderszins verwerkt door deze derden.
    
* **Doorverwijzingsgegevens** . We kunnen je de mogelijkheid bieden om vrienden uit te nodigen of andere gebruikers door te verwijzen voor toegang tot of gebruik van onze Diensten. Als je dat doet, kunnen we bepaalde persoonlijke gegevens over je verzamelen en ontvangen, onder meer van andere huidige of potentiële TMG-gebruikers en van klanten die zich op soortgelijke wijze met deze activiteiten bezighouden.

**Automatisch verzamelde persoonlijke gegevens** . Wij en onze externe dienstverleners kunnen automatisch persoonlijke gegevens met betrekking tot je gebruik van onze Diensten over je verzamelen of afleiden, bijvoorbeeld door het gebruik van cookies, pixeltags en andere soortgelijke technologieën.De persoonlijke gegevens die we automatisch kunnen verzamelen, zijn onder andere:

* **Toestel- en browsegegevens** . Als je onze Diensten gebruikt, kunnen we browsertype, domeinnaam, paginaweergaven, toegangstijden, datum- en tijdstempels, besturingssysteem, taal, toesteltype, unieke ID, internetprovider, verwijzende en uitgaande URL's, clickstreamgegevens en vergelijkbare toestel- en browsegegevens verzamelen.
    
* **Activiteiten en gebruik** . We kunnen ook aan je gebruik van de Diensten gerelateerde activiteitsgegevens verzamelen, zoals informatie over aangeklikte links, zoekopdrachten, gebruikte functies, bekeken items, doorgebrachte tijd binnen de Diensten, je interacties met ons en anderen binnen de Diensten en andere soortgelijke activiteits- en gebruiksgegevens.
    
* **Locatiegegevens** . We kunnen ook algemene locatiegegevens over je verzamelen of afleiden, bijvoorbeeld via je IP-adres.

Zie voor meer informatie over ons gebruik van cookies en andere soortgelijke technologieën paragraaf 6 'Cookies, targeting en analyses' hieronder.

**3\. Doelen van verzameling en verwerking**

De categorieën persoonlijke gegevens die we verzamelen, kunnen we in het algemeen verzamelen, gebruiken, verstrekken en anderszins verwerken voor de volgende doeleinden:

* **Diensten en ondersteuning** . Om onze Diensten te leveren en uit te voeren (bijvoorbeeld Tagged of de Pets-gamefunctie), je account te beheren, met je te communiceren over je gebruik van de Diensten, problemen op te lossen, technische ondersteuning te bieden of voor vergelijkbare ondersteuningsdoeleinden, om op je vragen te reageren, aan je verzoeken te voldoen, de verwerking van betalingen mogelijk te maken en anderszins om onze dagelijkse activiteiten uit te voeren. Dit omvat onder andere het zichtbaar maken van een deel van je persoonlijke gegevens, zoals je gebruikers-ID, je gebruikersnaam en de in je privacyinstellingen geselecteerde contactgegevens voor gebruikers van de betreffende Dienst of onze andere Diensten, en andere applicaties die ons eigendom zijn en andere applicaties en websites die geen eigendom van ons zijn, maar waarmee we ons liveplatform delen. TMG beroept zich op de grondslag 'uitvoering van een overeenkomst' (art.6 (1) (b) van de AVG en de UK GDPR en art. 31 (2) (b) nDSG). Voor zover we je persoonlijke gegevens verwerken om die zichtbaar te maken voor gebruikers van onze andere Diensten, en andere applicaties die ons eigendom zijn en andere applicaties en websites die geen eigendom van ons zijn, maar waarmee we ons live platform delen, beroept TMG zich op de grondslag 'uitvoering van een overeenkomst' (art. 6 (1) (b) van de AVG en de UK GDPR en art. 31 (2) (b) nDSG).

Met betrekking tot locatiegegevens is TMG afhankelijk van je toestemming (art. 6 (1) (a), art. 7 AVG).

Met betrekking tot seksuele geaardheid is TMG afhankelijk van je expliciete toestemming (art. 6 (1) (a), art. 7, art. 9 (2) (a) AVG/UK GDPR) of van de uitzondering in art. 9 (2) (e) AVG/UK GDPR mits je je seksuele geaardheid publiekelijk bekendgemaakt hebt (bijvoorbeeld in een livestream).

* **Analyses en verbeteringen** . Om meer inzicht te krijgen in de manier waarop gebruikers de Diensten benaderen en gebruiken, en voor andere onderzoeks- en analytische doeleinden, zoals het evalueren en verbeteren van de Site, onze Diensten en bedrijfsactiviteiten, inclusief het ontwikkelen van onze Diensten en de functies ervan, en voor interne kwaliteitscontrole- en opleidingsdoeleinden.TMG beroept zich op de grondslag 'gerechtvaardigde belangen' (art.6 (1) (f) AVG/UK GDPR en art. 31 (1) nDSG). In dit opzicht streeft TMG zijn belang na om te begrijpen hoe de dienst vanuit zakelijk perspectief presteert.

**Communicatie** . Om je vragen te beantwoorden en om je aangevraagde materialen of informatie en materialen met betrekking tot onze Diensten en aanbiedingen te sturen. We kunnen deze gegevens ook gebruiken om je administratieve informatie te sturen, bijvoorbeeld informatie over de Diensten en wijzigingen in onze algemene voorwaarden en beleidsregels. TMG beroept zich op de grondslag 'uitvoering van een overeenkomst' (art. 6 (1) (b) AVG/UK GDPR en art. 31 (2) (a) nDSG) of, als er geen contract tussen de betreffende gebruiker en TMG bestaat, op 'gerechtvaardigde belangen' (art. 6 (1) (f) AVG/UK GDPR en art. 31 (1) nDSG). Waar TMG zich op 'gerechtvaardigde belangen' beroept, streeft TMG zijn belangen na in het bieden van ondersteuning en het beantwoorden van verzoeken om de gebruikerstevredenheid te waarborgen.

* **Aanpassingen en personalisatie** . Om content die we op de Diensten kunnen verzenden of weergeven af te stemmen op de gebruiker, bijvoorbeeld om aanpassingen op basis van locatie te bieden en om je ervaringen en aanbiedingen op andere wijze te personaliseren. TMG beroept zich op de grondslag 'uitvoering van een overeenkomst' (art. 6 (1) (b) van de AVG en de UK GDPR en art. 31 (2) (b) nDSG.
    
* Socialemedia- en andere platformcommunicatie. Om je in staat te stellen informatie of content te delen, je aan te melden bij of te registreren voor de Diensten via verschillende socialemediaplatforms, socialenetwerkdiensten of andere functies van derden of geïntegreerde diensten. Om je in staat te stellen je aan te melden bij of te registreren voor de Diensten, beroept TMG zich op de grondslag 'uitvoering van een overeenkomst' (art. 6 (1) (b) van de AVG en de UK GDPR en art. 31 (2) (b) nDSG). Voor het overige beroept TMG zich op de grondslag 'gerechtvaardigde belangen' (art. 6 (1) (f) AVG/UK GDPR en art. 31 (1) nDSG). In dit opzicht streeft TMG zijn belang na om gebruikers in staat te stellen bepaalde communicatie te initiëren met socialemediaplatforms, socialenetwerkdiensten of andere functies of geïntegreerde diensten van derden als dat is wat zij willen doen.
    
* **Marketing en reclame** . Voor marketing-, reclame- en promotionele doeleinden. Bijvoorbeeld om je promotionele informatie over onze Diensten te sturen, zoals nieuwsbrieven, informatie over TMG-evenementen, webinars, presentaties, uitverkoop, aanbiedingen, kortingen en nieuwe producten of diensten, evenals alle andere informatie waarvoor je je aanmeldt om die te ontvangen. TMG beroept zich op de grondslag 'toestemming' (art. 6 (1) (a), art. 7 AVG en UK GDPR en art. 31 (1) nDSG.

Ten behoeve van eigen reclame/direct marketing middels promotionele e-mails en/of pushberichten, (gebruikers-)enquêtes en geïndividualiseerde handleidingen (uitsluitend TMG-producten). (De grondslag is het legitieme belang van TMG bij direct marketing voor zijn eigen producten en artikel 7 (3) van de Duitse Gesetz gegen den unlauteren Wettbewerb (UWG).)

* **Onderzoek en enquêtes** . Om enquêtes en vragenlijsten af te nemen, zoals voor marktonderzoek, gebruikerstevredenheid of andere soortgelijke doeleinden. TMG beroept zich op de grondslag 'toestemming' (art. 6 (1) (a), art. 7 AVG en UK GDPR en art. 31 (1) nDSG.
    
* **Ontwikkeling van inzicht en verbetering van gegevens** . We kunnen via de Diensten verzamelde persoonlijke gegevens combineren met andere informatie die wij of derden in andere contexten over je verzamelen. In de meeste gevallen kunnen consumenten niet rechtstreeks geïdentificeerd worden aan de hand van de informatie die we kunnen combineren met de voor marktonderzoek via de Diensten verzamelde persoonlijke gegevens, zoals demografische gegevens. TMG beroept zich op de grondslag 'gerechtvaardigde belangen' (art. 6 (1) (f) AVG/UK GDPR en art. 31 (1) nDSG). In dit opzicht streeft TMG zijn belang na om te begrijpen hoe de dienst vanuit zakelijk perspectief presteert.
    
* **Gebruik en opslag van gegevens op het toestel van gebruikers.** We kunnen informatie op je toestel gebruiken of bewaren. TMG beroept zich op de grondslag 'toestemming' art. 5 (3) E-privacyrichtlijn en PECR-verordening 6(4) wanneer dit niet strikt noodzakelijk is voor de werking van onze website en voor het aanbieden van telemediadiensten die uitdrukkelijk door de gebruiker worden aangevraagd.
    
* **Evenementen plannen en beheren** . Voor het plannen van evenementen en andere beheerdoeleinden zoals registratie voor en deelname aan evenementen, om je in contact te brengen met andere deelnemers aan evenementen en TMG-gebruikers en om contact met je op te nemen over relevante evenementen, presentaties en onze Diensten. We kunnen persoonlijke gegevens ook gebruiken voor het faciliteren van speciale evenementen, sweepstakes, wedstrijden en promoties, die hun eigen specifieke regels voor deelname kunnen hebben. TMG beroept zich op de grondslag 'toestemming' (art. 6 (1) (a), art. 7 AVG en UK GDPR en art. 31 (1) nDSG.
    
* **Beveiliging en bescherming van rechten** . Om de Diensten en onze bedrijfsactiviteiten, onze rechten en die van onze belanghebbenden en investeerders te beschermen, om fraude, ongeoorloofde activiteiten en toegang tot en ander misbruik van onze Site te voorkomen en te detecteren, inclusief wanneer we dat nodig achten voor het onderzoeken, voorkomen of ondernemen van actie met betrekking tot illegale activiteiten, vermoedelijke fraude, situaties met potentiële bedreigingen voor de veiligheid of wettelijke rechten van een persoon of derde, of schendingen van onze Algemene Voorwaarden. TMG beroept zich op de grondslag 'gerechtvaardigde belangen' (art. 6 (1) (f) AVG/UK GDPR en art. 31 (1) nDSG. Het gerechtvaardigd belang van TMG en de TMG-gebruikers dat de TMG-dienst niet wordt misbruikt voor contractuele en/of illegale handelingen van derden. Ons gerechtvaardigd belang is ook de bescherming van onze eigen systemen ter beveiliging van de informatietechnologie van TMG en daarmee uiteindelijk de bescherming van persoonlijke gegevens van de gebruikers van TMG. Met betrekking tot seksuele geaardheid beroept TMG zich bovendien op de grondslag 'instellen, uitoefenen of verdedigen van juridische claims' (art. 9 (2) (f) AVG/UK GDPR).
    
* **Naleving en rechtsgang** . Om te voldoen aan verplichtingen onder toepasselijke wet- of regelgeving, waaronder wettelijke bewaarplichten of als onderdeel van een gerechtelijke procedure, om te reageren op een dagvaarding, bevelschrift, gerechtelijk bevel of andere juridische procedure, of als onderdeel van een onderzoek of verzoek, formeel of informeel, van een wetshandhavings- of overheidsinstantie. TMG beroept zich op de grondslag (i) 'voldoen aan wettelijke verplichtingen' (art. 6 (1) (c) AVG/UK GDPR en art. 31 (2) (a) nDSG) als deze verplichting voortvloeit uit wetgeving van de EU of een EU-lidstaat of (ii) 'gerechtvaardigde belangen' (art. 6 (1) (f) AVG/UK GDPR en art. 31(1) nDSG) als deze verplichting voortvloeit uit andere jurisdicties. Waar gerechtvaardigde belangen relevant zijn, streeft TMG zijn belangen na bij het voldoen aan de wettelijke verplichtingen waaraan TMG is onderworpen. Met betrekking tot seksuele geaardheid beroept TMG zich bovendien op de grondslag 'instellen, uitoefenen of verdedigen van juridische claims' (art. 9 (2) (f) AVG/UK GDPR).
    
* **Auditing, rapportage en andere interne activiteiten** . Voor het uitvoeren van financiële, fiscale en boekhoudkundige audits en beoordelingen van onze activiteiten, zoals onze privacy-, beveiligings- en financiële controles, en voor risico- en nalevingsdoeleinden. We kunnen persoonlijke gegevens ook gebruiken om een correcte bedrijfsadministratie bij te houden en om onze beleidsregels en procedures af te dwingen. TMG beroept zich op de grondslag 'gerechtvaardigde belangen' (art. 6 (1) (f) AVG/UK GDPR en art. 31 (1) nDSG. Het gerechtvaardigd belang van TMG is het waarborgen van de bedrijfsvoering en het regelmatig controleren of aan rapportage- en nalevingsverplichtingen wordt voldaan.
    
* **Algemene zakelijke en operationele ondersteuning** . Voor het beoordelen en implementeren van fusies, overnames, reorganisaties, faillissementen en andere zakelijke transacties zoals financieringen, en voor het uitvoeren van onze bedrijfs-, boekhoudkundige, audit-, nalevings-, administratieve en juridische functies. TMG beroept zich op de grondslag 'gerechtvaardigde belangen' (art. 6(1)(f) DSGVO en art. 31(1) nDSG). In deze context heeft TMG belang bij het verstrekken en anderszins verwerken van gegevens over zijn activa en activiteiten aan potentiële kopers of verwervers en hun externe adviseurs om de verkoop van die activa en/of activiteiten te faciliteren.

De doeleinden die wij nastreven in verband met het gebruik van cookies en vergelijkbare technologieën, met name met betrekking tot targeting en analyses, worden beschreven in paragraaf 6 'Cookies, targeting en analyses'.

Als de grondslag voor verwerking jouw toestemming is, heb je het recht om op elk gewenst moment je toestemming in te trekken. Deze intrekking heeft echter geen invloed op de rechtmatigheid van enige verwerking die voorafgaand aan je intrekking is uitgevoerd op basis van je toestemming. Als de grondslag een gerechtvaardigd belang is, heb je in het algemeen ook het recht om op elk moment bezwaar te maken tegen de verwerking van je persoonlijke gegevens om redenen die voortvloeien uit jouw specifieke situatie. Verder heb je te allen tijde het recht om bezwaar te maken tegen de verwerking van je persoonlijke gegevens voor directmarketingdoeleinden. Artikel 21 AVG/UK GDPR is in dit verband van toepassing.

Je kunt tijdens de registratie of op enig later moment bezwaar maken tegen ons gebruik van je e-mailadres voor promotionele doeleinden of persoonlijke begeleiding.

**4\. Vertrekking van persoonlijke gegevens**

We kunnen de voor de hierboven beschreven doeleinden verzamelde persoonlijke gegevens verstrekken om je onze Diensten te leveren, om te reageren op en te voldoen aan je verzoeken, zoals anderszins door jou aangegeven of met jouw toestemming, en met de volgende ontvangers:

* **Merken, gelieerde bedrijven en dochterondernemingen** . De persoonlijke gegevens die we verzamelen, kunnen we verstrekken aan onze merken, gelieerde bedrijven en dochterondernemingen.
    
* **Zakelijke partners** . In bepaalde omstandigheden kan TMG samenwerken met andere bedrijven om zijn Diensten aan te bieden, zoals het faciliteren van bepaalde programma's of speciale aanbiedingen, en kunnen we persoonlijke gegevens verstrekken aan die zakelijke partners.
    
* **Leveranciers en dienstverleners** . De persoonlijke gegevens die we verzamelen, kunnen we verstrekken aan leveranciers en dienstverleners die namens ons functies uitvoeren, zoals IT en websitehosting, betalingsverwerkers, aanbieders van marketing en marktonderzoek, klantondersteuning, gegevensopslag, aanbieders van gegevensanalyse, auditors, consultants, adviseurs, agenten en advocaten.
    
* **Andere TMG-gebruikers** . Met andere gebruikers van de Diensten in de context van specifieke functionaliteiten die sociaal van aard zijn. Als je bijvoorbeeld anderen uitnodigt om onze Diensten te gebruiken of als je informatie verzendt of beschikbaar stelt via onze publiek toegankelijke, interactieve functies, communityforums of discussieblogs, zoals wanneer je reviews of testimonials plaatst, kunnen bepaalde persoonlijke gegevens beschikbaar en doorzoekbaar zijn voor andere gebruikers van de Diensten. Als je bijvoorbeeld aan Pets deelneemt, kunnen andere gebruikers van het Pets-spel persoonlijke gegevens zien, zoals je profielfoto, geslacht, waarde, cash, bezittingen, eigendom van en aantal huisdieren.
    
* **Externe marketing- en analyseaanbieders** . We kunnen je persoonlijke gegevens zoals toestel-, browse-, activiteits- en gebruiksgegevens ook verstrekken aan externe marketing- en gegevensanalyseaanbieders en andere bedrijven die namens ons marketing-, advertentie-, campagnebeheer- of analysediensten leveren. Zie ons Consent Management Platform in de app voor een gedetailleerd overzicht van de specifieke ontvangers.

We kunnen je persoonlijke gegevens ook verstrekken in de volgende omstandigheden:

* **Ter ondersteuning van bedrijfsoverdrachten** . Als wij of onze gelieerde bedrijven zijn of kunnen worden overgenomen door of gefuseerd met, of investeringen ontvangen of kunnen ontvangen van een ander bedrijf, of als activa van ons worden of kunnen worden overgedragen aan een ander bedrijf, als onderdeel van een faillissements- of insolventieprocedure of anderszins, dan kunnen we de persoonlijke gegevens die we van je hebben verzameld conform de toepasselijke wetgeving verstrekken of overdragen aan het andere bedrijf. We kunnen voorafgaand aan de voltooiing van een dergelijke transactie of andere zakelijke transactie zoals een financiering of herstructurering bepaalde persoonlijke gegevens indien nodig ook verstrekken aan kredietverstrekkers, auditors en externe adviseurs, zoals advocaten en consultants.
    
* **Naleving en wettelijke verplichtingen** . We kunnen persoonlijke gegevens ook verstrekken aan derden voor zover vereist door toepasselijke wetgeving en wettelijke verplichtingen. We kunnen bijvoorbeeld gegevens verstrekken in antwoord op dagvaardingen, gerechtelijke bevelen en andere wettige verzoeken van toezichthouders, overheidsinstanties en wetshandhavingsinstanties, waaronder in antwoord op openbaarmakingsvereisten vanwege nationale veiligheid of wetshandhaving of zoals anderszins door wet of rechtsgang vereist. Bovendien en indien van toepassing kunnen we de namen van winnaars van sweepstakes en prijsvragen verstrekken in overeenstemming met toepasselijke wetgeving.
    
* **Beveiliging en bescherming van rechten** . Waar wij van mening zijn dat dit noodzakelijk is om de Diensten, onze rechten en eigendommen of de rechten, eigendommen en veiligheid van anderen te beschermen. We kunnen bijvoorbeeld persoonlijke gegevens verstrekken ten behoeve van het voorkomen, detecteren en onderzoeken van en reageren op (i) fraude, ongeoorloofde activiteiten en toegang, illegale activiteiten en misbruik van de Diensten, (ii) situaties rond potentiële bedreigingen voor de gezondheid, veiligheid of wettelijke rechten van personen of derden of (iii) voor het handhaven, detecteren, onderzoeken en actie ondernemen als reactie op schendingen van onze Algemene Voorwaarden.We kunnen ook persoonlijke gegevens verstrekken met betrekking tot rechtszaken en andere juridische claims of procedures waarbij we betrokken zijn, evenals voor onze interne boekhoudkundige, audit-, nalevings-, administratieve en juridische functies.
    
* **Andere verstrekkingen** . We kunnen persoonlijke gegevens verstrekken op andere dan de hierboven beschreven manieren waarover we je informeren of waarvoor we je toestemming verkrijgen, of die anderszins wettelijk toegestaan of vereist zijn.

Niettegenstaande al het in dit Beleid beschreven overige kunnen we geaggregeerde, geanonimiseerde en andere niet-identificeerbare gegevens met betrekking tot ons bedrijf en de Diensten gebruiken en verstrekken voor kwaliteitscontrole-, analyse-, onderzoeks-, ontwikkelings- en andere doeleinden. Als we geanonimiseerde gegevens (gegevens die niet langer redelijkerwijs gekoppeld of koppelbaar zijn aan een geïdentificeerde of identificeerbare natuurlijke persoon, huishouden of persoonlijk of huishoudelijk toestel) gebruiken, verstrekken of verwerken, zullen we de gegevens in geanonimiseerde vorm bewaren en gebruiken en niet proberen de gegevens opnieuw te identificeren, behalve om te bepalen of onze anonimiseringsprocedures volgens de toepasselijke privacywetten redelijk en adequaat zijn.

**5\. Doorgiftes van persoonlijke gegevens in de context van landen buiten EER/VK/CH**

Ontvangers van persoonlijke gegevens kunnen zich buiten EER/VK/Zwitserland bevinden.Als persoonlijke gegevens worden doorgegeven naar locaties buiten EER/VK/Zwitserland (zoals doorgiftes van ons in de VS als verwerkingsverantwoordelijke in het kader van de AVG/UK GDPR/nDSG naar ontvangers in de VS of andere landen buiten EER/VK/Zwitserland, die niet onder het toepassingsgebied van de AVG/UK GDPR/nDSG vallen), zullen wij zoals vereist door de wet zorgen dat je privacyrechten adequaat worden beschermd, hetzij doordat de Europese Commissie heeft bepaald dat het land waarnaar persoonlijke gegevens worden doorgegeven een adequaat beschermingsniveau biedt (art. 45 AVG/UK GDPR), hetzij doordat op de doorgifte passende waarborgen (bijvoorbeeld met de ontvanger afgesloten modelcontracten van de Europese Unie) (art. 46 AVG/UK GDPR) van toepassing zijn, tenzij de AVG/UK GDPR voorziet in een uitzondering (art. 49 AVG/UK GDPR). In aanvulling hierop zijn wij voornemens om waar nodig met ontvangers aanvullende maatregelen overeen te komen om een adequaat gegevensbeschermingsniveau te waarborgen. Zie ook art. 16 f. nDSG met betrekking tot de verstrekking van persoonlijke gegevens buiten Zwitserland.

Indien nodig stellen we met onze contractpartners ook een overeenkomstig 'UK Addendum' op conform de vereisten van de Britse Information Commissioner's Office (ICO), en een overeenkomstig 'CH Addendum' conform de vereisten van de Zwitserse Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner (FDPIC).

Kopieën van passende waarborgen (voor zover we ons daarop beroepen) en een lijst met ontvangers buiten EER/VK/Zwitserland kunnen worden opgevraagd via [support@themeetgroup.com](mailto:support@themeetgroup.com).Dergelijke kopieën kunnen geredigeerd zijn voor zover dat nodig is om bedrijfsgeheimen of andere vertrouwelijke informatie te beschermen.

**6\. Cookies, targeting en analyses**

Wij en onze externe dienstverleners gebruiken cookies, pixels, lokale opslagobjecten, logboekbestanden en andere trackingmechanismen om automatisch browse-, activiteits-, toestel- en andere soortgelijke gegevens binnen onze Diensten te verzamelen. We gebruiken deze gegevens om te analyseren en inzicht te krijgen in de manier waarop gebruikers onze Diensten benaderen, gebruiken en ermee interacteren, om bugs en fouten in onze Diensten te identificeren en te verhelpen, om onze Diensten te beoordelen, te beveiligen, te beschermen, te optimaliseren en de prestaties ervan te verbeteren, voor marketing- en analysedoeleinden en om de content binnen onze Diensten te personaliseren. Afhankelijk van je locatie zal het merendeel hiervan alleen plaatsvinden als je toestemming hebt gegeven met behulp van ons CMP in de app-instellingen, waarmee je je toestemming en voorkeuren met betrekking tot cookies, gerichte advertenties en andere soortgelijke trackingmechanismen binnen onze Diensten kunt beheren. Zie paragraaf 7 'Je privacyopties' hieronder. Veel van deze opties zijn specifiek voor een bepaalde browser en een bepaald toestel, zodat je je voorkeuren mogelijk apart moet instellen voor alle browsers en toestellen die je gebruikt om toegang te krijgen tot onze Diensten. Als je cookies verwijdert of blokkeert, moet je deze voorkeuren bovendien mogelijk opnieuw toepassen in elke browser en/of op elk toestel.

**Cookies** . 'Cookies' zijn kleine tekstbestanden die op het toestel van gebruikers (zoals een computer of smartphone) worden opgeslagen door een website die zij bezoeken. Cookies worden aangemaakt door de server van de website en naar de browser van de gebruiker gestuurd, waar ze worden opgeslagen voor toekomstig gebruik. Sommige cookies dienen om het navigeren door onze Diensten gemakkelijker voor je te maken en andere cookies worden gebruikt om je sneller te kunnen aanmelden, de beveiliging en prestaties van de Diensten te ondersteunen of ons in staat te stellen om geaggregeerde en statistische gegevens over gebruikersactiviteit binnen de Diensten bij te houden.

**Pixeltags** . Pixeltags (soms webbakens of clear GIF's genoemd) zijn kleine afbeeldingen met een unieke identificator. Ze hebben een vergelijkbare functie als cookies. Het verschil is dat cookies lokaal op je toestel worden opgeslagen en pixeltags ingesloten zijn in webpagina's en online content. We kunnen ze in verband met onze Diensten onder andere gebruiken om de activiteiten van gebruikers bij te houden, content te beheren en gebruiksgegevens te genereren. We kunnen ze ook in onze e-mails gebruiken om te zien wanneer die geopend of doorgestuurd zijn, zodat we de responspercentages kunnen volgen en de effectiviteit van onze communicatie kunnen meten.

**Logboekbestanden** . We kunnen bepaalde activiteitsgegevens verzamelen vanuit logboekbestanden. Logboekgegevens worden automatisch verzameld als je onze Sites bezoekt. We registreren bepaalde gegevens uit deze logboekbestanden, zoals webverzoeken, IP-adres, browsertype en -versie, taalgegevens, verwijzende en uitgaande URL's, aangeklikte links, bekeken pagina's en andere soortgelijke gegevens.

**Externe analyses** . We kunnen geautomatiseerde, door externe bedrijven beheerde apparaten, applicaties en tools zoals Google Analytics gebruiken om het gebruik van onze Diensten te evalueren. Deze externe bedrijven kunnen cookies, pixels en andere trackingtechnologieën gebruiken om gebruiksgegevens over onze Diensten te verzamelen en ons rapporten en statistieken te verstrekken waarmee we het gebruik van onze Diensten kunnen evalueren en de prestaties en gebruikerservaringen kunnen verbeteren. Zie het privacybeleid van Google op [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners?hl=nl](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/) voor meer informatie over de privacypraktijken van Google. Je kunt ook de Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on downloaden op [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=nl](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) om te voorkomen dat je gegevens worden gebruikt door Google Analytics. In ons CMP in de app-instellingen vind je een lijst van de derden die wij in deze context hebben ingeschakeld.

**Advertenties van derden** . We werken samen met externe advertentienetwerken, marketingpartners, mobiele advertentienetwerken en andere ('externe advertentiebedrijven') om content te personaliseren en advertenties weer te geven binnen onze Diensten en om onze advertenties op websites van derden te beheren.Wij en deze externe advertentiebedrijven kunnen cookies, pixeltags, SDK's (softwareontwikkelingskits) en andere tools gebruiken om browse- en activiteitsgegevens binnen onze Diensten (en op sites en in diensten van derden), IP-adressen, unieke ID's, cookie- en advertentie-ID's en andere online identificatoren te verzamelen. Wij en deze externe advertentiebedrijven gebruiken die gegevens om je relevantere advertenties en content binnen onze Diensten en op sites van derden te bieden en om het succes van dergelijke advertenties en content te evalueren. In ons CMP in de app-instellingen vind je een lijst van de externe advertentiebedrijven.

**Gebruik op meerdere toestellen** . Wij en onze externe dienstverleners kunnen de gegevens die we (rechtstreeks vanuit onze Sites of Mobiele App, via je toestel(len) of via externe bronnen) over je verzamelen, gebruiken om andere toestellen die je gebruikt (bijvoorbeeld een mobiele telefoon, tablet, andere computer enzovoort) te identificeren. Wij en onze externe dienstverleners kunnen de gegevens over gebruik op meerdere toestellen en andere gegevens die we over je verkrijgen ook gebruiken om gerichte advertenties te bieden of content binnen onze Diensten te personaliseren.

**Klantenlijsten en matching** . We kunnen bepaalde klantenlijstgegevens (zoals je naam, e-mailadres en andere contactgegevens) delen met of beschikbaar stellen aan derden zodat we advertenties en content op externe websites, platforms en diensten beter op jou kunnen afstemmen. In sommige gevallen kunnen deze derden ons helpen onze klantenlijsten uit te breiden met aanvullende demografische of andere vergelijkbare gegevens, zodat we onze advertentie- en marketingcampagnes beter kunnen afstemmen.

**7\. Je privacyopties**

**Je voorkeuren beheren** . We bieden je verschillende manieren om je voorkeuren en privacyopties te beheren, zoals hieronder beschreven:

* **Account en profiel** . Sommige van de persoonlijke gegevens die we over je bijhouden, kun je controleren en bijwerken door je aan te melden bij je account en je account- en profielgegevens bij te werken.
    
* **Marketingcommunicatie** . We kunnen je van tijd tot tijd promotionele e-mails, content of andere soortgelijke communicatie sturen. Je kunt je afmelden voor deze communicatie door de instructies te volgen die in de communicatie worden vermeld. Als je je afmeldt voor het ontvangen van promotionele content van ons, kunnen we je nog wel berichten sturen over je account of over diensten die je aangevraagd of van ons ontvangen hebt. Bovendien kun je je communicatievoorkeuren beheren in je account- en profielinstellingen.
    
* **Pushmeldingen** . Je kunt beheren welk soort pushmeldingen je van ons ontvangt door de instellingen van je mobiele toestel aan te passen of door de instellingen in onze Mobiele App te wijzigen. Dit zijn berichten die we je sturen tijdens het uitvoeren van het contract, maar ook promotionele informatie.

**Cookie- en trackingvoorkeuren/gerichte advertenties/analyses** . We bieden je ook verschillende manieren om je voorkeuren met betrekking tot cookies, gerichte advertenties, analyses en andere soortgelijke trackingmechanismen binnen onze Diensten te beheren. Veel van deze opties zijn specifiek voor een bepaalde browser en een bepaald toestel, zodat je je voorkeuren mogelijk apart moet instellen voor alle browsers en toestellen die je gebruikt om toegang te krijgen tot onze Diensten.Als je cookies verwijdert of blokkeert, moet je deze voorkeuren bovendien mogelijk opnieuw toepassen in elke browser en/of op elk toestel. Bovendien betekent het afmelden voor cookies en advertenties niet dat je geen advertenties van ons ontvangt. Je kunt nog steeds generieke of 'contextuele' advertenties van ons ontvangen.

* **Consent Management Platform (CMP).** Om te voorkomen dat cookies of trackingmechanismen die niet strikt noodzakelijk zijn je activiteit op onze Sites of in onze Mobiele App bijhouden, kun je het Consent Management Platform (CMP, toestemmingsbeheerplatform) gebruiken dat wordt aangeboden voordat de cookies en trackingmechanismen toegepast worden. Als je eenmaal toestemming hebt gegeven, kun je die altijd met vooruitwerkende kracht intrekken. Zie voor meer informatie paragraaf 15 'Aanvullende privacyinformatie voor bepaalde rechtsgebieden', die aanvullende informatie over privacyrechten bevat voor inwoners van bepaalde rechtsgebieden.
    
* **Cookie-instellingen** . Om te voorkomen dat cookies je activiteit op onze Sites of bezoeken aan meerdere websites volgen, kun je in je browser instellen dat bepaalde cookies worden geblokkeerd of dat je een melding krijgt als er een cookie wordt geplaatst.Je kunt cookies ook verwijderen. In het menu 'Help' in de werkbalk van de meeste browsers kun je lezen hoe je kunt voorkomen dat je toestel nieuwe cookies accepteert, hoe je de browser je kunt laten waarschuwen als je een nieuwe cookie ontvangt en hoe je cookies kunt verwijderen. Bezoekers van onze Sites die cookies uitschakelen, kunnen de Site blijven gebruiken, maar sommige functies werken dan mogelijk niet.
    
* **Browsersignalen** . Voor zover vereist door toepasselijke wetgeving zullen we, als onze Sites detecteren dat je browser een afmeldsignaal zoals een GPC-signaal ('global privacy control') verzendt, dat signaal toepassen om die specifieke browser op je toestel af te melden voor gerichte cookies op onze Sites. Als je via een ander toestel of via een andere browser op hetzelfde toestel naar onze Sites komt, moet je GPC ook voor die browser en/of dat toestel toepassen.
    
* **Advertentiekeuzeprogramma's van de branche** . Je kunt ook bepalen hoe deelnemende externe advertentiebedrijven de gegevens gebruiken die zij verzamelen over je bezoeken aan onze Sites en die van derden om je relevantere gerichte advertenties te tonen. Ga naar [www.YourOnlineChoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/) voor meer informatie en hulp met betrekking tot webtrackingmechanismen.

Inwoners van bepaalde rechtsgebieden kunnen aanvullende rechten met betrekking tot hun persoonlijke gegevens hebben zoals hieronder uiteengezet in paragraaf 15 'Aanvullende privacyinformatie voor bepaalde rechtsgebieden'.

**8\. Bewaartermijn van persoonlijke gegevens**

We bewaren je persoonlijke gegevens zo lang als dat nodig is voor de doeleinden die worden genoemd in paragraaf 3 'Doelen van verzameling en verwerking' en paragraaf 6 'Cookies, targeting en analyses' of zo lang we een gerechtvaardigd belang hebben bij het voortzetten van de opslag. In alle overige gevallen verwijderen we je persoonlijke gegevens, met uitzondering van de gegevens die we moeten blijven bewaren om te voldoen aan wettelijke bewaartermijnen (bijvoorbeeld vanwege belasting- of handelswetten, zoals met betrekking tot facturen). We beperken de verwerking van persoonlijke gegevens die alleen vanwege een bewaarplicht worden bewaard.

In ons CMP in de app-instellingen vind je informatie over de bewaartermijnen voor cookies en andere trackingmechanismen.

**9\. Externe links en functies**

Onze Diensten kunnen links naar websites of functies van derden bevatten of verbindingen of geïntegreerde diensten van derden bieden. De toegang tot en het gebruik van zulke gelinkte websites of functies valt niet onder dit Beleid, maar onder het privacybeleid van die derden. Wij zijn niet verantwoordelijk voor de informatiepraktijken van zulke derden, zoals het door hen verzamelen, gebruiken en verstrekken van je persoonlijke gegevens. Je dient het privacybeleid en de voorwaarden van derden te lezen voordat je naar die websites gaat of die functies gebruikt.

**10\. Door gebruikers gegenereerde content**

We kunnen publiek toegankelijke interactieve functies, communityforums of discussieblogs in verband met onze Diensten bieden waarmee je informatie over de Diensten of andere interessante kwesties (bijvoorbeeld reviews, testimonials en vragen) kunt delen. Communicatie die je op dergelijke interactieve functies op de Diensten indient of plaatst, kan zichtbaar en doorzoekbaar zijn voor anderen, zoals TMG-gebruikers en andere bezoekers. Als je op dergelijke publiek toegankelijke functies content indient of plaatst, erken je dat je geen privacy of vertrouwelijkheid verwacht met betrekking tot de content die je voor dergelijke functies indient, ongeacht of die content wel of geen persoonlijke gegevens over jou bevat.

**11\. Beveiliging**

We hebben redelijke voorzorgsmaatregelen genomen om de verzamelde gegevens te beschermen tegen verlies, misbruik, ongeoorloofde toegang, openbaarmaking, wijziging en vernietiging. Ondanks onze inspanningen kunnen maatregelen voor de bescherming van gegevens nooit veiligheid garanderen.

**12\. Privacy van kinderen**

Onze Diensten zijn niet bedoeld voor kinderen en we verzamelen niet bewust persoonlijke gegevens van kinderen jonger dan achttien (18) jaar. Als we vernemen dat er op de Diensten persoonlijke gegevens van personen jonger dan 18 jaar zijn verzameld, zullen we passende stappen ondernemen om die gegevens te verwijderen. Als je een ouder of wettelijke voogd bent en denkt dat we in strijd met de toepasselijke wetgeving gegevens van je kind verzameld hebben, neem dan contact met ons op via de onderstaande contactgegevens.

**13\. Wijzigingen in dit beleid**

Dit Beleid is geactualiseerd op de vermelde datum. We kunnen dit Beleid van tijd tot tijd wijzigen of aanpassen, dus kom hier geregeld even terug. We zullen eventuele wijzigingen van dit beleid hier publiceren.Als we wijzigingen in dit Beleid aanbrengen die een wezenlijke invloed hebben op onze praktijken met betrekking tot ons gebruik van de persoonlijke gegevens die we eerder van je hebben verzameld, zullen we proberen je hiervan op de hoogte te stellen, bijvoorbeeld door je een e-mail te sturen of door een prominente kennisgeving te plaatsen op onze Sites, in onze Mobiele App of binnen de Diensten.

**14\. Contact opnemen**

Als je vragen of opmerkingen over dit Beleid of onze privacypraktijken hebt, kun je een e-mail sturen naar [support@themeetgroup.com](mailto:support@themeetgroup.com) of contact opnemen via:

The Meet Group, Inc.

100 Union Square Drive

New Hope, PA 18938, VS

Je kunt onze functionaris gegevensbescherming bereiken via:

ePrivacy GmbH vertegenwoordigd door Prof. Dr. Christoph Bauer, Große Bleichen 21, 20354 Hamburg, Duitsland, [privacy@themeetgroup.com](mailto:privacy@themeetgroup.com)

Voor alle verzoeken met betrekking tot de beveiliging van je gegevens kun je contact opnemen met onze functionaris gegevensbescherming via [privacy@themeetgroup.com](mailto:privacy@themeetgroup.com).

Onze EU-vertegenwoordiger volgens art. 27 AVG kun je bereiken via: ParshipMeet Holding GmbH, Speersort 10, 20095 Hamburg, Duitsland, e-mail: [privacy@parshipmeet.com](mailto:privacy@parshipmeet.com)

De gegevens van onze Britse vertegenwoordiger volgens art. 27 UK GDPR worden vermeld in paragraaf 15.B 'Aanvullende informatie voor inwoners van het VK'.

De gegevens van onze Zwitserse vertegenwoordiger volgens art. 14 nDSG (nieuwe Zwitserse gegevensbeschermingswet) worden vermeld in paragraaf 15.C'Aanvullende informatie voor inwoners van Zwitserland'.

Treforma AG c/o MLL Legal, Grabenstrasse 25, 6340 Baar, Zwitserland, [meetgroup@dsg-mll.com](mailto:meetgroup@dsg-mll.com)

**15\. Aanvullende privacyinformatie voor bepaalde rechtsgebieden**

Inwoners van bepaalde rechtsgebieden hebben aanvullende rechten onder toepasselijke privacywetten, zoals uiteengezet in deze paragraaf.

**A. AVG**

Als je inwoner van de Europese Unie bent, heb je onder de AVG de volgende rechten, mits wordt voldaan aan de wettelijke vereisten daarvan:

**Recht op inzage:** je kunt informatie over de verwerking van je persoonlijk gegevens en een kopie van de verwerkte persoonlijke gegevens opvragen, mits die kopie geen afbreuk doet aan de rechten en vrijheden van anderen en er geen andere uitzondering van toepassing is.

**Recht op rectificatie:** je kunt verzoeken om correctie van je persoonlijke gegevens als ze onjuist zijn en/of om aanvulling als ze onvolledig zijn.

**Recht op gegevens verwijderen:** je kunt verzoeken om verwijdering van je persoonlijke gegevens, met name als

* de persoonlijke gegevens niet langer nodig zijn in verband met de doeleinden waarvoor ze zijn verzameld of anderszins verwerkt,
    
* je je toestemming hebt ingetrokken waarop de verwerking gebaseerd was en er geen andere grondslag voor de verwerking is,
    
* je bezwaar gemaakt hebt tegen de verwerking die is gebaseerd op de grondslag 'gerechtvaardigde belangen' en er geen zwaarder wegende grondslagen voor de verwerking zijn, of je bezwaar gemaakt hebt tegen de verwerking voor directmarketingdoeleinden,
    
* je persoonlijke gegevens onrechtmatig verwerkt zijn of
    
* je persoonlijke gegevens gewist moeten worden om te voldoen aan een wettelijke verplichting die op ons van toepassing is.

Maar het recht op gegevens verwijderen geldt met name niet als de verwerking van je persoonlijke gegevens noodzakelijk is om te voldoen aan een wettelijke verplichting of voor het instellen, uitoefenen of verdedigen van juridische claims.

**Recht op beperking van de verwerking:** je kunt verzoeken om beperking van de verwerking

* gedurende de periode waarin wij de juistheid van je persoonlijke gegevens verifiëren als je de juistheid van de persoonlijke gegevens betwist;
    
* als de verwerking onrechtmatig is en je verzoekt om beperking van de verwerking in plaats van verwijdering van de gegevens;
    
* als wij de persoonlijke gegevens niet langer nodig hebben, maar jij de gegevens nodig hebt voor het instellen, uitoefenen of verdedigen van juridische claims;
    
* als je bezwaar gemaakt hebt tegen de verwerking die is gebaseerd op de grondslag 'gerechtvaardigde belangen' totdat geverifieerd is of onze gerechtvaardigde grondslagen zwaarder wegen dan jouw belangen, rechten en vrijheden.

**Recht op dataportabiliteit:** je kunt verzoeken om je persoonlijke gegevens die je aan ons hebt verstrekt, te ontvangen in een gestructureerd, veelgebruikt en machineleesbaar formaat en die gegevens ongehinderd door ons door te geven aan een andere verwerkingsverantwoordelijke als de verwerking op basis van toestemming of de uitvoering van een overeenkomst plaatsvindt en de verwerking op geautomatiseerde wijze plaatsvindt. In deze gevallen kun je ook verzoeken om de persoonlijke gegevens rechtstreeks naar een andere verwerkingsverantwoordelijke te laten verzenden als dat technisch haalbaar is.

Verder heb je de volgende rechten:

**Recht om toestemming in te trekken:** je kunt je toestemming altijd met vooruitwerkende kracht intrekken als de verwerking gebaseerd is op je toestemming, zonder dat dit invloed heeft op de rechtmatigheid van de verwerking die voorafgaand aan je intrekking is uitgevoerd op basis van je toestemming.

**Recht van bezwaar:**

**Je hebt altijd het recht om op grond van redenen die verband houden met jouw specifieke situatie bezwaar te maken tegen de verwerking van je persoonlijke gegevens die gebaseerd is op ons gerechtvaardigde belang of dat van een derde (art. 6 (1) (f)AVG). We zullen je persoonlijke gegevens dan niet langer verwerken voor het doel waartegen je bezwaar gemaakt hebt, tenzij wij overtuigende gerechtvaardigde belangen voor de verwerking die zwaarder wegen dan jouw belangen, rechten en vrijheden of voor het instellen, uitoefenen of verdedigen van juridische claims kunnen aantonen.**

**Verder heb je te allen tijde het recht om bezwaar te maken tegen de verwerking van je persoonlijke gegevens voor directmarketingdoeleinden. Als je bezwaar maakt tegen de verwerking voor directmarketingdoeleinden, zullen we je persoonlijke gegevens niet langer voor dergelijke doeleinden verwerken.**

* * *

**Recht om een klacht in te dienen:** je kunt een klacht indienen bij een toezichthoudende autoriteit, met name in de lidstaat van je verblijfplaats, werkplek of plaats van vermeende inbreuk als je van mening bent dat de verwerking van je persoonlijke gegevens inbreuk maakt op de AVG.

De voor ons bevoegde gegevensbeschermingsautoriteit is:

Der Hamburgische Beauftragte für Datenschutz und Informationsfreiheit, Ludwig-Erhard-Str. 22, 20459 Hamburg, Duitsland, e-mail: [mailbox@datenschutz.hamburg.de](mailto:mailbox@datenschutz.hamburg.de)

**B. UK GDPR**

Als je je in het Verenigd Koninkrijk bevindt, heb je rechten op grond van de UK GDPR en gegevensbeschermingswetten. Of en in welke mate de rechten van toepassing zijn, kan afhankelijk zijn van de omstandigheden. Neem contact met ons op via onderstaande contactgegevens als je deze rechten wilt uitoefenen. De rechten zijn:

**Je recht op informatie:** je hebt het recht om beknopte, transparante, begrijpelijke en gemakkelijk toegankelijke informatie te ontvangen over je persoonlijke gegevens en ons gebruik ervan. Dit Beleid is onze manier om je over die informatie te informeren, maar als je nog vragen of opmerkingen hebt, kun je contact met ons opnemen via onderstaande contactgegevens.

**Je recht op inzage:** je hebt het recht om ons om kopieën van je persoonlijke gegevens te vragen. Dit recht is altijd van toepassing, maar er zijn uitzonderingen op de toepassing ervan, waardoor je mogelijk niet altijd alle gegevens ontvangt die je opgevraagd hebt. Als je je persoonlijke gegevens opvraagt, doe je een toegangsverzoek door de betrokkene, oftewel een 'data subject access request' (DSAR). Nadat we je DSAR ontvangen hebben, moeten we je misschien om een legitimatie vragen om je identiteit te verifiëren.

**Je recht op rectificatie:** je hebt het recht ons te vragen persoonlijke gegevens te corrigeren waarvan je denkt dat die onjuist zijn. Je hebt ook het recht om te vragen de gegevens aan te vullen waarvan je denkt dat ze onvolledig zijn.

**Je recht op gegevens verwijderen:** onder bepaalde omstandigheden heb je het recht ons te vragen je persoonlijke gegevens te verwijderen. We hebben het recht om te weigeren gevolg te geven aan een verzoek tot verwijdering als we de persoonlijke gegevens verwerken om een van de volgende redenen:

* Om het recht op vrijheid van meningsuiting en informatie uit te oefenen.
    
* Om te voldoen aan een wettelijke verplichting.
    
* Om een taak van algemeen belang uit te voeren of officieel gezag uit te oefenen.
    
* Voor archiveringsdoeleinden in het algemeen belang, wetenschappelijk onderzoek, historisch onderzoek of statistische doeleinden.
    
* Voor het uitoefenen of verdedigen van juridische claims.

**Je recht op beperking van de verwerking:** onder bepaalde omstandigheden heb je het recht ons te vragen de verwerking van je persoonlijke gegevens te beperken. In dat geval bewaren we de gegevens nog wel, maar verwerken we ze niet meer. Dit recht is een alternatief voor het recht op gegevens verwijderen. Je kunt het recht op beperking van de verwerking uitoefenen als een van de volgende voorwaarden van toepassing is:

* De juistheid van de persoonlijke gegevens wordt betwist.
    
* De verwerking van de persoonlijke gegevens is onrechtmatig.
    
* We hebben de persoonlijke gegevens niet meer nodig voor verwerking, maar de persoonlijke gegevens zijn nog wel nodig voor een deel van een juridische procedure.
    
* Het recht van bezwaar is uitgeoefend en de verwerking is beperkt in afwachting van een beslissing over de status van de verwerking.

**Je recht van bezwaar tegen verwerking: onder bepaalde omstandigheden heb je het recht om bezwaar te maken tegen verwerking, inclusief direct marketing. Je kunt ook bezwaar maken als de verwerking gebaseerd is op onze gerechtvaardigde belangen (of die van een derde). We zullen je persoonlijke gegevens dan niet langer verwerken voor het doel waartegen je bezwaar gemaakt hebt, tenzij we overtuigende gerechtvaardigde belangen voor de verwerking die zwaarder wegen dan jouw belangen, rechten en vrijheden of voor het instellen, uitoefenen of verdedigen van juridische claims kunnen aantonen.**

**Je recht op dataportabiliteit:** dit is het recht om je persoonlijke gegevens te ontvangen in een gestructureerd, veelgebruikt en machineleesbaar formaat, maar het is alleen van toepassing als we gegevens op basis van je toestemming of voor de uitvoering van een contract verwerken en de verwerking geautomatiseerd is.

**Recht om toestemming in te trekken:** je kunt je toestemming altijd met vooruitwerkende kracht intrekken als de verwerking gebaseerd is op je toestemming, zonder dat dit invloed heeft op de rechtmatigheid van de verwerking die voorafgaand aan je intrekking is uitgevoerd op basis van je toestemming.

**Contactgegevens**

Als je een van je rechten wilt uitoefenen of vragen hebt over ons gebruik van je persoonlijke gegevens, neem dan contact met ons op via de gegevens onder Contact opnemen. Als je dat doet, zorg dan dat je ons voldoende informatie verstrekt om je duidelijk te kunnen identificeren.

We hebben een Britse vertegenwoordiger aangesteld met wie je namens ons contact kunt opnemen overeenkomstig art. 27 UK GDPR: eHarmony UK Ltd., 6-10 Great Portland Street, Londen W1W 8QL, Groot-Brittannië.

**Doorgifte van persoonlijke gegevens buiten het Verenigd Koninkrijk**

Zie paragraaf 5 'Doorgiftes van persoonlijke gegevens in de context van landen buiten EER/VK/CH' hierboven voor meer informatie over de bescherming en beveiligingsmaatregelen die van toepassing zijn op je persoonlijke gegevens wanneer die worden doorgegeven buiten het Verenigd Koninkrijk.

**Recht om een klacht in te dienen bij een toezichthoudende autoriteit**

Je hebt het recht om een klacht in te dienen bij een gegevensbeschermingsautoriteit.

Je kunt contact opnemen met de Britse gegevensbeschermingsautoriteit, de Information Commissioner's Office, via: Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF, Groot-Brittannië, telefoon: + 44 (0) 303 123 1113, e-mail: [casework@ico.org.uk](mailto:casework@ico.org.uk).

**C. Zwitserse gegevensbeschermingswet.**

**Je recht op inzage:** je hebt het recht om ons om kopieën van je persoonlijke gegevens te vragen. Dit recht is altijd van toepassing, maar er zijn uitzonderingen op de toepassing ervan, waardoor je mogelijk niet altijd alle gegevens ontvangt die je opgevraagd hebt. Als je je persoonlijke gegevens opvraagt, doe je een toegangsverzoek door de betrokkene.

**Je recht op rectificatie:** je hebt het recht ons te vragen persoonlijke gegevens te corrigeren waarvan je denkt dat die onjuist zijn. Je hebt ook het recht om te vragen de gegevens aan te vullen waarvan je denkt dat ze onvolledig zijn.

**Je recht op gegevens verwijderen:** onder bepaalde omstandigheden heb je het recht ons te vragen je persoonlijke gegevens te verwijderen. We hebben het recht om te weigeren gevolg te geven aan een verzoek tot verwijdering als we de persoonlijke gegevens verwerken om een van de volgende redenen:

* Om het recht op vrijheid van meningsuiting en informatie uit te oefenen.
    
* Om te voldoen aan een wettelijke verplichting.
    
* Om een taak van algemeen belang uit te voeren of officieel gezag uit te oefenen.
    
* Voor archiveringsdoeleinden in het algemeen belang, wetenschappelijk onderzoek, historisch onderzoek of statistische doeleinden.
    
* Voor het uitoefenen of verdedigen van juridische claims.

**Je recht op beperking van de verwerking:** onder bepaalde omstandigheden heb je het recht ons te vragen de verwerking van je persoonlijke gegevens te beperken. In dat geval bewaren we de gegevens nog wel, maar verwerken we ze niet meer. Dit recht is een alternatief voor het recht op gegevens verwijderen. Je kunt het recht op beperking van de verwerking uitoefenen als een van de volgende voorwaarden van toepassing is:

* De juistheid van de persoonlijke gegevens wordt betwist.
    
* De verwerking van de persoonlijke gegevens is onrechtmatig.
    
* We hebben de persoonlijke gegevens niet meer nodig voor verwerking, maar de persoonlijke gegevens zijn nog wel nodig voor een deel van een juridische procedure.
    
* Het recht van bezwaar is uitgeoefend en de verwerking is beperkt in afwachting van een beslissing over de status van de verwerking.

**Je recht van bezwaar tegen verwerking:** onder bepaalde omstandigheden heb je het recht om bezwaar te maken tegen verwerking. Je kunt ook bezwaar maken als de verwerking plaatsvindt voor een taak die uitgevoerd wordt in het algemeen belang, de uitoefening van officieel gezag dat bij jou berust of onze gerechtvaardigde belangen (of die van een derde).

**Je recht van bezwaar tegen direct marketing:** je kunt ook altijd bezwaar maken tegen de verwerking van je persoonlijke gegevens voor advertentiedoeleinden ('advertentiebezwaar'). Houd er rekening mee dat er vanwege organisatorische redenen een overlap kan bestaan tussen je herroeping en het gebruik van je gegevens in het kader van een al lopende campagne.

**Je recht op dataportabiliteit:** dit recht is alleen van toepassing als we gegevens op basis van je toestemming of voor de uitvoering van een contract verwerken en de verwerking geautomatiseerd is.

Als je een van je rechten wilt uitoefenen, neem dan contact met ons op via de gegevens onder Contact opnemen. Als je dat doet, zorg dan dat je ons voldoende informatie verstrekt om je duidelijk te kunnen identificeren.

**Contactgegevens**

Als je een van je rechten wilt uitoefenen of vragen hebt over ons gebruik van je persoonlijke gegevens, neem dan contact met ons op via de gegevens onder Contact opnemen. Als je dat doet, zorg dan dat je ons voldoende informatie verstrekt om je duidelijk te kunnen identificeren.

We hebben een Zwitserse vertegenwoordiger volgens art. 14 nDSG (nieuwe Zwitserse gegevensbeschermingswet) aangesteld: Treforma AG c/o MLL Legal, Grabenstrasse 25, 6340 Baar, Zwitserland, [meetgroup@dsg-mll.com](mailto:meetgroup@dsg-mll.com)

**Doorgifte van persoonlijke gegevens buiten Zwitserland**

Zie paragraaf 5 'Doorgiftes van persoonlijke gegevens in de context van landen buiten EER/VK/CH' hierboven voor meer informatie over de bescherming en beveiligingsmaatregelen die van toepassing zijn op je persoonlijke gegevens wanneer die worden doorgegeven buiten Zwitserland.

**Recht om een klacht in te dienen bij een toezichthoudende autoriteit**

Je hebt het recht om een klacht in te dienen bij een gegevensbeschermingsautoriteit.

Je kunt contact opnemen met de bevoegde toezichthoudende autoriteit voor gegevensbescherming in Zwitserland. Dat is de:

Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner (FDPIC).

Je kunt contact met hen opnemen via:

[https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/de/home/deredoeb/kontakt/kontaktformular\_bgoe.html](https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/de/home/deredoeb/kontakt/kontaktformular_bgoe.html)

**The Meet Group Inc.**

Az Európai Gazdasági Térségben vagy az Egyesült Királyságban lakóhellyel rendelkező felhasználókra vonatkozó Adatvédelmi szabályzat
===================================================================================================================================

_Utolsó frissítés: October 8, 2024_

A The Meet Group, Inc., annak márkái, társvállalatai és leányvállalatai nagyra értékelik az Ön adatainak védelmét. A jelen Adatvédelmi szabályzat („Szabályzat”) leírja, hogy a The Meet Group, Inc. („ **TMG** ”, „ **mi** ”, „ **miénk** ”vagy „ **bennünket** ”) hogyan gyűjti, használja, hozza nyilvánosságra és kezeli más módon a jelen szabályzatban leírt személyes információkat (egyes joghatóságok személyes adatoknak is nevezik), valamint az Ön jogait és választási lehetőségeit az ilyen személyes információkkal kapcsolatban.

Ha további információra van szüksége a személyes adataival kapcsolatos adatvédelmi döntéseiről, tekintse át a 7. szakaszt: Az Ön adatvédelmi választásai, valamint a 15. szakasz: A További adatvédelmi információk egyes joghatóságokhoz című részt, amelyek további információkat tartalmaznak az egyes joghatóságok lakosainak adatvédelmi jogairól.

Ha Ön az EU/Európai Gazdasági Térség (EGT) lakója, kérjük, olvassa el a 15.A. szakaszt: További információk az EU/EGT lakosainak az Általános adatvédelmi rendelet („GDPR”) szerinti jogokról című részt.

Ha Ön az Egyesült Királyság lakója, kérjük, olvassa el a 15.B. szakaszt:További információk az Egyesült Királyság lakosainak az Általános adatvédelmi rendelet („GDPR”) szerinti jogaikról. Az Egyesült Királyság 2018. évi Európai Uniós (kilépésről szóló) törvényének (UK GDPR) 3. szakasza értelmében az Egyesült Királyság jogába átültetett rendelet című részt.

Ha Ön Svájcban rendelkezik lakóhellyel, kérjük, olvassa el a 15.C. szakaszt: További információk svájci lakosok számára az új svájci adatvédelmi törvényben („nDSG”) foglalt jogaikról című részt.

Amikor Ön profilt létesít valamelyik Szolgáltatásunkon, az Ön személyes információinak egy része, mint például a felhasználónév, név, életkor, nem és szexuális irányultság az Ön adatvédelmi beállításainak megfelelően láthatóvá válhat az adott Szolgáltatás és egyéb Szolgáltatásaink felhasználói számára is, valamint más olyan alkalmazások számára, amelyek a mi tulajdonunkat képezik, illetve más, nem a mi tulajdonunkban lévő alkalmazások és weboldalak számára, amelyekkel közösen osztozunk az élő platformunkon. Ez a többi felhasználó a világon bárhol lehet. Jelenlegi partnerlistánkat [ide](https://talent.tagged.com/partner-policy-tagged.html) kattintva találja.

A Szolgáltatásaink Ön által történő használatára a [Szolgáltatási feltételek](https://secure.tagged.com/terms_of_service.html) vonatkoznak, beleértve a vonatkozó kárkorlátozási és vitarendezési feltételeket.

**Tartalomjegyzék**

1. Hatály
    
2. A gyűjtött személyes adatok
    
3. A gyűjtés és feldolgozás céljai
    
4. A személyes adatok közzététele
    
5. Személyes adatok továbbítása az EGT/UK/CH területén kívüli országokba
    
6. Sütik, célzás és elemzés
    
7. Az Ön adatvédelmi választásai
    
8. A személyes adatok tárolási időszaka
    
9. Külső hivatkozások és szolgáltatások
    
10. A felhasználó által generált tartalom
    
11. Biztonság
    
12. Gyermekek adatvédelme
    
13. Jelen szabályzat változásai
    
14. Kapcsolatfelvétel
    
15. További adatvédelmi információk bizonyos joghatóságok felé

**1\. Hatály**

Az alábbiakban leírtak kivételével a jelen Szabályzat a TMG által gyűjtött és feldolgozott személyes információkra vonatkozik: azaz a jelen Szabályzatot közzétevő weboldalunk látogatóira, beleértve bármely olyan weboldalunkat, amely a jelen Szabályzatra hivatkozással mutat vagy azt közzéteszi („ **Oldalak** ”); azokra a személyekre, akik letöltik és használják mobil alkalmazásunkat („ **Mobile App** ”, pl. a Tagged vagy a Pets alkalmazás); magánszemélyekre, akik regisztrálnak vagy részt vesznek a rendezvényeinken, felméréseiken, kutatásainkban, promócióinkban és nyereményjátékainkban; és magánszemélyekre, akik velünk vagy az Oldalainkon, a Mobilalkalmazásunkon vagy más online szolgáltatásainkon keresztül elérhető szolgáltatásokkal kommunikálnak vagy más módon kapcsolatba lépnek velünk vagy azokban részt vesznek (a továbbiakban együttesen „ **Szolgáltatások** ”).

**2\. A gyűjtött személyes adatok**

Az alábbiakban részletezettek szerint a személyes adatokat közvetlenül Öntől, harmadik féltől, illetve automatikusan is gyűjthetjük, a Szolgáltatásaink használatán keresztül.

**A közvetlenül Öntől begyűjtött személyes adatok** . Habár az általunk gyűjtött személyes információk a Szolgáltatásaink Ön általi használatától és az Önnel való interakciónktól függően változnak, általánosságban az alábbi kategóriájú személyes adatokat gyűjthetjük közvetlenül Öntől:

* **Elérhetőség** . Amikor kapcsolatba lép velünk, ideértve azt, ha üzenetet küld nekünk, vagy regisztrál, hogy többet tudjon meg a Szolgáltatásainkról, gyűjthetjük az Ön nevét, e-mail-címét, telefonszámát vagy más hasonló azonosító adatokat, valamint az Ön üzenetét, a megkeresés jellegét és bármely egyéb olyan információt, amelyet Ön rendelkezésünkre bocsát.
    
* **Fiók- és profilinformációk** . Amikor Ön egy fiókot regisztrál a Szolgáltatásainkhoz kapcsolódóan (pl. egy Tagged-fiók), begyűjthetjük az Ön nevét, e-mail címét, telefonszámát, címét (pl., irányítószámot ), felhasználónevét és jelszavát, születési dátumát, valamint nemét, szexuális orientációját, profilképét és fényképét, számlázási címének adatait, valamint bármely más olyan információt, amelyet a fiók létrehozásával vagy fenntartásával kapcsolatban ad meg, vagy amelyet Ön egyébként a fiókján keresztül megad nekünk.

Ha a harmadik fél szolgáltatókon, például Facebookon vagy Apple-ön vagy SMS-en keresztül történő bejelentkezést választotta, akkor a regisztrációs folyamat során nem kell megadnia e-mail-címét vagy jelszavát. A felhasználók ezután a megadott e-mail-címmel és a választott jelszóval (bejelentkezési adatok), vagy a harmadik fél szolgáltatójának bejelentkezési adatai segítségével férnek hozzá a Szolgáltatásunkhoz.

**Regisztráció Facebookon keresztül („Facebook bejelentkezés”)**

A Facebookon keresztül egyszeri bejelentkezést biztosítunk. Ez lehetőséget ad arra,

hogy Facebook-fiókján keresztül regisztráljon. Ha igénybe veszi a funkciót, a regisztrációhoz a Facebooktól a következő hitelesítési adatokat

kapjuk és dolgozzuk fel

az Ön e-mail-címe, profilneve, neme, születési dátuma és az ott tárolt profilképe. Az adatátvitel ebben a vonatkozásban történik.

Amikor Ön a Facebook használatával jelentkezik be weboldalunkra vagy alkalmazásunkba, a Facebook is adatokat fog gyűjteni harmadik féltől származó szkriptekből, feldolgozza azokat Facebook analitikai célokra, vagy harmadik feleknek továbbítja azokat. A Facebook Adatvédelmi szabályzata ismerteti a Facebook-bejelentkezés során gyűjthető adatokat. Ez magában foglalja az Ön eszközére, a Szolgáltatásunk használatára, az Ön által felkeresett weboldalakra és a megtekintett hirdetésekre vonatkozó adatokat. Sajnos Ön technikailag nem tudja visszautasítani ezt a Szolgáltatásunkhoz kapcsolódó feldolgozást. Ha nem szeretné, hogy a Facebook adatokat gyűjtsön Önről online ajánlatunk használatával kapcsolatban, és azokat saját céljaira használja , akkor ne éljen a Facebook-bejelentkezés lehetőségével.

A Tagged-fiókot bármikor leválaszthatja a Facebook-fiókjáról. Ebben az esetben szükséges, hogy megadja a fent említett hozzáférési adatot.

Az adatgyűjtés céljáról és köréről, valamint az Ön adatainak Facebook általi további feldolgozásáról és felhasználásáról, valamint az Ön jogairól és az adatai védelmét szolgáló beállítási lehetőségekről további információkat talál a Facebook Adatvédelmi szabályzatában: [http://www.facebook.com/policy.php](http://www.facebook.com/policy.php).

**Regisztráció/Bejelentkezés a Google-ön keresztül**

Ha Ön Androidos készüléket használ, lehetőséget kínálunk Önnek arra, hogy Google-fiókján keresztül regisztráljon vagy jelentkezzen be a Szolgáltatásunkba. Ha Ön így tesz, a Google Ireland Limited, Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Írország („Google”) megadja nekünk a regisztrációhoz vagy bejelentkezéshez szükséges adatokat (e-mail-cím, név, Google-fiók azonosító és Google-fiók profilkép).

Nincs ráhatásunk a Google által a Google bejelentkezés használatával gyűjtött adatok körére. Ha nem szeretné, hogy a Google adatokat gyűjtsön Önről online ajánlatunk használatával kapcsolatban, és azokat saját céljaira használja , akkor ne éljen a Google-bejelentkezés lehetőségével.

Az adatgyűjtés céljáról és köréről, valamint az Ön adatainak a Google általi további feldolgozásáról és felhasználásáról, valamint az Ön jogairól és az adatai védelmét szolgáló beállítási lehetőségekről további információkat talál a Google adatvédelmi szabályzatában: [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

**Regisztráció/Bejelentkezés az Apple Sign-In funkción keresztül**

Ha Ön iOS készüléket használ, lehetőséget kínálunk Önnek arra, hogy Apple-ön keresztül regisztráljon vagy jelentkezzen be Szolgáltatásunkba. Ha úgy dönt, eszerint jár el, akkor az Apple Inc., One Apple Park Way, Cupertino, Kalifornia, USA, 95014 („Apple”) megadja nekünk az Ön által választott és a regisztrációhoz vagy bejelentkezéshez szükséges adatokat (pl. az Apple által generált e-mail-címet, nevet).

Nincs ráhatásunk az Apple által az Apple bejelentkezés használatával gyűjtött adatok körére. Ha nem szeretné, hogy az Apple adatokat gyűjtsön Önről online ajánlatunk használatával kapcsolatban, és azokat saját céljaira használja , akkor ne éljen az Apple-bejelentkezés lehetőségével.

Az adatgyűjtés céljáról és köréről, valamint az Ön adatainak az Apple általi további feldolgozásáról és felhasználásáról, valamint az Ön jogairól és az adatai védelmét szolgáló beállítási lehetőségekről további információkat talál az Apple adatvédelmi szabályzatában: [https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/en/sign-in-with-apple/](https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/en/sign-in-with-apple/).

**Telefonos hitelesítéssel történő regisztráció/belépés esetén**

Telefonos hitelesítéssel történő regisztráció/belépés esetén felkínáljuk a mobilszámával történő hitelesítést, ezért meg kell adnia a mobilszámát. Ezután SMS-t küldünk Önnek egy ellenőrző kóddal, amelyet az alkalmazásban meg kell adnia a folyamat befejezéséhez. Amikor be kíván jelentkezni, SMS-t küldünk egy kóddal, amellyel bejelentkezhet fiókjába. Ezenkívül ellenőrzésre is sor kerül. A szolgáltatást a Delaware-i Sinch America Inc., vállalat jogi osztálya, 3500 Lenox Rd NE, Ste. 1875, Atlanta, GA 30326, Georgia, USA címen nyújtja,

és csak akkor lehetséges, ha Ön ehhez előzetesen hozzájárult.

Az Ön adatainak Google általi feldolgozásának céljáról és köréről további információkat a Sinch adatvédelmi szabályzatában talál: [https://www.sinch.com/privacy-notice/](https://www.sinch.com/privacy-notice/)

* **Vásárlások, fizetések és jutalmak** . Amikor Ön vásárlást vagy fizetést eszközöl a Szolgáltatásainkon keresztül (pl. a Pets játékunkkal kapcsolatban), olyan információkat gyűjthetünk, mint például a fizetés típusa, a fizetésre használt kártya adatai, számlázási, vásárlási információk, és bármilyen más pénzügyi vagy kereskedelmi vonatkozású információ, amely szükséges a Szolgáltatásaink támogatásához.
    
* **Kommunikáció és interakciók** . Amikor Ön e-mailt ír, felhív bennünket, vagy más módon kommunikál, kapcsolatba lép velünk vagy más TMG-felhasználókkal, beleértve, ha feliratkozik a levelezési listáinkra, kitölti az űrlapokat az oldalainkon vagy a mobilalkalmazásunkon, kapcsolatba lép a közösségi média oldalainkon, véleményt vagy értékelést ír, tartalmat küld bármely online vitacsoportba, vagy más módon információkat küld be nyilvános hozzászólási mezőkbe, blogokba vagy közösségi fórumokba, amelyeket a TMG szponzorál vagy amelyekhez kapcsolódik, gyűjthetjük, fogadhatjuk és megőrizhetjük az Ön kapcsolattartási adatait, kommunikációját és interakcióit, az Ön hozzászólásait vagy elküldött adatai, és adott esetben a mi válaszainkat.
    
* **Promóciós információk** . Ha hozzájárul ahhoz, hogy marketingkommunikációt kapjon tőlünk, akkor gyűjthetjük az Ön nevét, e-mail címét, telefonszámát, preferenciáit, és ha releváns, az Ön fiókjára és profiljára vonatkozó információkat, beleértve az Ön által használt Szolgáltatásokat és funkciókat. Ha Ön részt vesz az általunk kínált speciális tevékenységekben, ajánlatokban, programokban vagy nyereményjátékokban, akkor bizonyos elérhetőségi adatokat, az életkorát és egyéb, a jogszabályok által megkövetelt információt is gyűjthetjük. Ha Ön megnyer egy nyereményjátékot, a nyereménytől függően bizonyos adóügyi információkat és/vagy lemondó nyilatkozatokat és mentességeket is be kell gyűjtenünk.
    
* **Válaszok és visszajelzések** . Ha Ön felmérésekben, kérdőívekben vagy általunk végzett kutatási programokban vagy kezdeményezésekben vesz részt, például a felhasználói elégedettség vagy más hasonló célok érdekében, gyűjthetjük az Ön válaszait és visszajelzéseit, valamint bármely más, Ön által megadott információt.
    
* **Események és a regisztráció részletei** . Személyes információkat is gyűjthetünk a rendezvényeinken történő részvételével kapcsolatban, illetve olyan kérelmeket illetően, amelyeket a Szolgáltatásainkkal kapcsolatban nyújt be hozzánk. Például, ha Ön regisztrál vagy részt vesz egy olyan eseményen, amelynek mi vagyunk a házigazdái vagy szponzorai, gyűjthetünk az Ön regisztrációjával és az eseményen való részvételével kapcsolatos információkat.
    
* **Preferenciák és egyéb kérések** . Ezen kívül gyűjthetünk információkat az Ön preferenciáiról, köztük a kommunikációs preferenciákról, a Szolgáltatásaink használatával kapcsolatos preferenciákról, valamint bármely más preferenciáról vagy kérésről, amelyet a velünk folytatott kommunikáció során megad.

Általánosságban elmondható, hogy nem köteles megadni személyes adatait. Bizonyos Szolgáltatások vagy Szolgáltatásaink elemeinek használata azonban megkövetelheti személyes adatok megadását, például Tagged-fiók regisztrálásához. Ha ez az eset áll fenn, akkor erre felhívjuk a figyelmet. Ha nem szeretné megadni nekünk a kért információkat, akkor sajnos nem fogja tudni használni az adott Szolgáltatást.

**Harmadik felektől gyűjtött személyes adatok** . Bizonyos személyes adatokat gyűjthetünk vagy fogadhatunk Önről harmadik felektől is, például üzleti partnerektől, különösen akkor, ha alkalmazás-áruház szolgáltatókat használ vásárlásokhoz, vagy más TMG-felhasználóktól, adatelemző és marketingszolgáltatóktól, operációs rendszerektől és közösségi média platformoktól különösen a fent leírt bejelentkezési funkciók használatakor. Ezen túl harmadik felektől a következő információkat gyűjthetjük:

* **Közösségi média és felület regisztrációs információk** . A Szolgáltatásaink használata során Ön dönthet úgy, hogy információkat vagy tartalmakat oszt meg, bejelentkezik vagy regisztrál a Szolgáltatásokba a különböző közösségi média felületeken, közösségi hálózati szolgáltatásokon vagy más harmadik féltől származó funkciókon vagy más integrált szolgáltatásokon keresztül. Amikor a Szolgáltatásainkhoz az Ön közösségi média fiókjai vagy más hasonló integrált szolgáltatások és funkciók használatával csatlakozik, akkor gyűjthetünk vagy kaphatunk olyan személyes adatokat Önről, amelyeket Ön az adott közösségi média fiók, szolgáltatás vagy funkció számára megadott. Például információkat gyűjthetünk az Ön fiókjából és profiljából, mint például az Ön neve, e-mail-címe, felhasználói azonosítója, profilképe, barátainak listája és más hasonló információk, amelyek az Ön profilján elérhetőek. Minden egyes közösségi média felületen, funkcióban vagy integrált szolgáltatásban ellenőrizze az adatvédelmi beállításokat, hogy jobban átlássa, hogyan használhatják, adhatják ki vagy kezelhetik más módon az Ön személyes adatait ezek a felek.
    
* **Ajánlásokkal kapcsolatos információk** . Lehetőséget kínálhatunk Önnek arra, hogy meghívja barátait vagy más felhasználókat ajánljon a Szolgáltatásainkhoz való hozzáféréshez vagy azok használatára. Eközben gyűjthetünk és kaphatunk bizonyos személyes adatokat Önről, beleértve más jelenlegi vagy potenciális TMG-felhasználóktól és ügyfelektől, akik hasonlóan vesznek részt ezekben a tevékenységekben.

**Automatikusan gyűjtött személyes adatok** . Mi és harmadik felek szolgáltatóink automatikusan gyűjthetünk vagy szerezhetünk Önről személyes információkat a Szolgáltatásaink használatával kapcsolatban, egyebek között sütik, pixelcímkék és más hasonló technológiák segítségével. Az általunk automatikusan gyűjthető személyes adatok a következők:

* **Eszköz- és böngészési információk** . Amikor igénybe veszi a Szolgáltatásainkat, gyűjthetjük a böngésző típusát, a domain nevet, az oldalmegtekintéseket, a hozzáférési időtartamokat, időpont-/időbélyegeket, az operációs rendszert, a nyelvet, az eszköz típusát, az egyedi azonosítót, az internetszolgáltatót, a hivatkozó és kilépő URL-címeket, kattintási adatokat, a nyelvet és hasonló eszköz- és böngészési információkat.
    
* **Tevékenységek és használat** . A Szolgáltatások Ön által történő használatához kapcsolódó tevékenységadatokat is gyűjthetünk, például a kattintott hivatkozásokra, keresésekre, a használt funkciókra, a megtekintett elemekre, a Szolgáltatásokban eltöltött időre, a velünk és másokkal a Szolgáltatásokon belül folytatott interakciókra, valamint más hasonló tevékenységekre és használatra vonatkozó információkat.
    
* **Helyre vonatkozó információ** . Általános helymeghatározásra vonatkozó információkat is gyűjthetünk vagy származtathatunk Önről, például az IP-címen keresztül.

A sütik és más hasonló technológiák használatára vonatkozó további információkért kérjük, olvassa el a 6. szakasz: Sütik, célzás és elemzés című részt.

**3\. A gyűjtés és feldolgozás céljai**

Általánosságban elmondható, hogy az általunk gyűjtött személyes adat kategóriákat a következő célokra gyűjthetjük, használhatjuk, hozhatjuk nyilvánosságra és dolgozhatjuk fel más módon:

* **Szolgáltatások és támogatás** . Szolgáltatásaink (pl. a Tagged vagy a Pets játék) nyújtása és működtetése, az Ön fiókjának kezelése, kommunikáció Önnel a Szolgáltatások használatáról, hibaelhárítás, technikai támogatás vagy hasonló támogatás céljára, az Ön megkereséseire való válaszadás, az Ön kéréseinek teljesítése, a fizetés feldolgozásának megkönnyítése, és a napi működésünk működtetése céljára. Ez magában foglalja az Ön néhány személyes információjának, például a felhasználó-azonosítójának, a felhasználónevének, az adatvédelmi beállításokban kiválasztott elérhetőségi információinak láthatóvá tételét az adott szolgáltatás vagy más szolgáltatásaink, valamint más, a tulajdonunkban lévő alkalmazások és más, nem a tulajdonunkban lévő alkalmazások és weboldalak felhasználói számára, akikkel közösen osztozunk az élő platformon. A TMG a „szerződés teljesítése” jogalapra hivatkozik (GDPR 6. cikk (1) bekezdés b) pontja), UK GDPR, és nDSG 31. cikk (2). bekezdése. Amennyiben az Ön személyes adatait azért dolgozzuk fel, hogy azokat láthatóvá tegyük más Szolgáltatásaink felhasználói számára, valamint a birtokunkban lévő más alkalmazások és egyéb, nem a mi tulajdonunkban lévő alkalmazások és weboldalak számára, akikkel osztozunk az élő platformunkon, a TMG a „szerződés teljesítése” jogalapra hivatkozik (GDPR 6. cikk (1) bekezdésének b) pontja), UK GDPR és nDSG 31. cikk (2) bekezdése.

A helyadatok tekintetében a TMG az Ön hozzájárulására támaszkodik (GDPR 6. cikk (1) bekezdés a) pontja).

A szexuális irányultság tekintetében a TMG az Ön kifejezett hozzájárulására támaszkodik (GDPR/UK GDPR 6. cikk (1) bekezdés a) pontja, 7. cikke, 9. cikk (2) bekezdés a) pontja vagy a GDPR/UK GDPR 9. cikk (2) bekezdés e) pontja szerinti kivétellel, feltéve, hogy Ön nyilvánosan felfedte szexuális irányultságát (pl. élő közvetítésben).

* **Elemzés és fejlesztés** . Annak érdekében, hogy jobban megértsük, hogyan férnek hozzá a felhasználók a Szolgáltatásokhoz és hogyan használják azokat, valamint egyéb kutatási és elemzési célokra, például a Weboldal, a Szolgáltatásaink és az üzleti műveletek értékelésére és javítására, beleértve a Szolgáltatásaink és funkcióinak fejlesztését, valamint belső minőség-ellenőrzési és képzési célokra. A TMG a „jogos érdek” jogalapra (GDPR/UK GDPR 6. cikk (1) bekezdés f) pontja és nDSG 31. cikk (1) bekezdése hivatkozik. Ebben a tekintetben a TMG azon érdekét képviseli, hogy megértse, hogyan teljesít a szolgáltatás üzleti szempontból.

**Kommunikáció** . Az Ön kérdéseinek megválaszolására, a kért anyagok, valamint a Szolgáltatásainkkal és ajánlatainkkal kapcsolatos információk és anyagok elküldésére. Ezeket az adatokat arra is felhasználhatjuk, hogy adminisztratív információkat küldjünk Önnek, például a Szolgáltatásokkal kapcsolatos információkat, illetve a feltételeink, kikötéseink és szabályzataink változásait. A TMG a „szerződés teljesítése” jogalapra hivatkozik (a GDPR/UK GDPR 6. cikk (1) bekezdés (b) pontja, és nDSG 31. cikk (2) bekezdés a) pontja, vagy - amennyiben az érintett felhasználó és a TMG között nem áll fenn szerződés - a „jogos érdek” jogalapra (GDPR/UK GDPR 6. cikk (1) bekezdés f) pontja és nDSG 31. cikk (1) bekezdése. Amennyiben a TMG "jogos érdekekre" hivatkozik, a TMG a támogatás nyújtásához, valamint a kérések megválaszolásához fűződő érdekeit érvényesíti a felhasználói elégedettség biztosítása érdekében.

* **Testreszabás és személyre szabás** . A tartalom testreszabása céljából küldhetünk vagy megjeleníthetünk a Szolgáltatásban információkat, beleértve a hely testreszabását, illetve az Ön élményének és ajánlatainak más módon történő személyre szabása céljából. A TMG a „szerződés teljesítése” jogalapra hivatkozik (GDPR 6. cikk (1) bekezdés b) pontja, UK GDPR és nDSG 31. cikk (2) bekezdés b) pontja.
    
* Közösségi média és egyéb platformkommunikáció. Annak érdekében, hogy Ön információkat vagy tartalmakat oszthasson meg, bejelentkezhessen vagy regisztrálhasson a Szolgáltatásokba különböző közösségi média platformokon, közösségi hálózati szolgáltatásokon, vagy más harmadik féltől származó funkciókkal vagy integrált szolgáltatásokkal. A Szolgáltatásokba való bejelentkezés vagy regisztráció lehetővé tétele vonatkozásában a TMG a „szerződés teljesítése” jogalapra hivatkozik (GDPR 6. cikk (1) bekezdés b) pontja), UK GDPR és nDSG 31. cikk (2) bekezdése). Egyéb esetben a TMG a „jogos érdek” jogalapra hivatkozik (GDPR/UK GDPR 6. cikk (1) bekezdés f) pontja és nDSG 31. cikk (1) bekezdése). Ebben a tekintetben a TMG arra törekszik, hogy ha a felhasználók szeretnék, lehetővé tegye számukra, hogy adott kommunikációt kezdeményezzenek közösségi platformokkal, közösségi hálózati szolgáltatásokkal vagy más harmadik féltől származó funkciókkal vagy integrált szolgáltatásokkal.
    
* **Marketing és reklámozás** . Marketing, reklám és promóciós célokra. Például, hogy promóciós információkat küldjünk Önnek a Szolgáltatásainkról, beleértve a hírleveleket, információt TMG eseményekről, webináriumokról, prezentációkról, akciókról, ajánlatokról, kedvezményekről és új ajánlatokról, valamint bármely más olyan információt, amelyre Ön feliratkozott. A TMG a „belegyezés” jogalapra támaszkodik, GDPR 6. cikk (1) bekezdés (a) pontja, GDPR 7. cikk, UK GDPR és nDSG 31. cikk (1) bekezdése.

Önmagunk reklámozása / direkt marketing céljából, promóciós e-mailek és/vagy push-üzenetek, (felhasználói) felmérések és személyre szabott útmutatások (kizárólag TMG termékek) útján. (A jogalap TMG törvényes érdeke a saját termékei közvetlen reklámozásához, valamint a németországi tisztességtelen verseny elleni törvény 7. § (3) bekezdése (UWG).

* **Kutatások és felmérések** . Felmérések és kérdőívek készítése, például piackutatás, felhasználói elégedettség vagy más hasonló célra. A TMG a „belegyezés” jogalapra támaszkodik, GDPR 6. cikk (1) bekezdés (a) pontja, GDPR 7. cikk, UK GDPR és nDSG 31. cikk (1) bekezdése.
    
* **Statisztikák fejlesztése és adatok javítása** . A Szolgáltatásokon keresztül gyűjtött személyes adatokat más olyan információkkal kombinálhatjuk, amelyeket mi vagy harmadik felek más kontextusban gyűjtünk Önről. A legtöbb esetben az általunk a Szolgáltatásokon keresztül piackutatás céljából gyűjtött személyes adatokkal kombinált információk, például demográfiai információk, nem alkalmasak a fogyasztók közvetlen azonosítására. A TMG a „jogos érdek” jogalapra (GDPR/UK GDPR 6. cikk (1) bekezdés f) pontja és nDSG 31. cikk (1) bekezdése hivatkozik. Ebben a tekintetben a TMG azon érdekét képviseli, hogy megértse, hogyan teljesít a szolgáltatás üzleti szempontból.
    
* **Információk tárolása és elérése végfelhasználók eszközén.** Az Ön végfelhasználói készülékén lévő információkhoz hozzáférhetünk vagy azokat eltárolhatjuk. A TMG a „beleegyezés” jogalapra támaszkodik az elektronikus adatvédelmi irányelv 5. cikk (3) bekezdése és a PECR rendelet 6. cikk (4) bekezdése alapján, amennyiben ez nem feltétlenül szükséges a weboldalunk működéséhez, valamint a felhasználó által kifejezetten kért telemédiás szolgáltatások nyújtásához.
    
* **Események tervezése és lebonyolítása** . Az események szervezéséhez és egyéb, az azokkal kapcsolatos célokra, mint például az eseményekre való regisztráció és részvétel céljára, illetve hogy összekössük Önt az esemény többi résztvevőjével és a TMG felhasználókkal, valamint az Önnel való kapcsolatfelvétel céljára a vonatkozó eseményekkel, előadásokkal és a Szolgáltatásainkkal kapcsolatban. A személyes adatokat felhasználhatjuk különleges események, sorsolások, nyereményjátékok, versenyek és promóciók lebonyolítására is, saját külön részvételi szabályzattal. A TMG a „belegyezés” jogalapra támaszkodik, GDPR 6. cikk (1) bekezdés (a) pontja, GDPR 7. cikke, UK GDPR és nDSG 31. cikk (1) bekezdése.
    
* **Biztonság és a jogok védelme** . A Szolgáltatások és üzleti tevékenységünk, jogaink, valamint partnereink és befektetőink jogainak védelme, a csalás, a jogosulatlan tevékenységek és hozzáférés, valamint a Weboldalunkkal való egyéb visszaélések megelőzése és észlelése érdekében, beleértve azokat az eseteket, amikor úgy véljük, szükséges az illegális tevékenységek, csalás gyanúja, bármely személy vagy harmadik fél biztonságát vagy jogait potenciálisan fenyegető helyzetek, vagy a Felhasználási feltételeink megsértésének kivizsgálása, megelőzése vagy az azokkal kapcsolatos intézkedések megtétele. A TMG a „jogos érdek” jogalapra (GDPR/UK GDPR 6. cikk (1) bekezdés f) pontja és nDSG 31. cikk (1) bekezdése) hivatkozik. A TMG és a TMG felhasználóinak jogos érdeke, hogy a TMG szolgáltatásával ne éljenek vissza harmadik felek szerződéses és/vagy jogellenes cselekmények céljából. Jogos érdekünk továbbá a TMG saját informatikai rendszerének védelme, és így ezáltal a TMG felhasználók személyes adatainak védelme is. A szexuális irányultság tekintetében a TMG emellett a jogi igények megállapításának, érvényesítésének vagy védelmének jogalapjára támaszkodik (GDPR/UK GDPR 9. cikk (2) bekezdés f) pontja).
    
* **Megfelelés és jogi eljárás** . Az alkalmazandó jogi vagy szabályozási kötelezettségeknek való megfelelés érdekében, beleértve a törvényes adatmegőrzési kötelezettséget, vagy bírósági eljárás részeként, idézésre, végzésre, bírósági végzésre vagy más jogi eljárásra való reagálás céljára, vagy a bűnüldöző szervek vagy kormányzati hatóságok hivatalos vagy nem hivatalos vizsgálatának vagy kérésének részeként. a TMG a következő jogalapra támaszkodik: (i) „jogi kötelezettségeknek való megfelelés” (GDPR/UK GDPR 6. cikk (1) bekezdés c) pontja, valamint a 31. cikk (2) bekezdés a) pontja nDSG), ha ez a kötelezettség EU vagy EU tagállami jogból ered, vagy ii) „jogos érdek” (GDPR/UK GDPR 6. cikk (1) bekezdés f) pontja), valamint 31(1) nDSG), ha ez a kötelezettség más joghatóságtól ered. Ahol a jogos érdekek fennállnak, a TMG azon jogi kötelezettségeknek való megfeleléshez fűződő érdekeit követi, melyek a TMG-re vonatkoznak. A szexuális irányultság tekintetében a TMG emellett a jogi igények megállapításának, érvényesítésének vagy védelmének jogalapjára támaszkodik (GDPR/UK GDPR 9. cikk (2) bekezdés f) pont).
    
* **Auditálás, jelentések és egyéb belső műveletek** . Pénzügyi, adó- és számviteli ellenőrzések, könyvvizsgálatok és a működésünk értékelése, beleértve az adatvédelmi, biztonsági és pénzügyi ellenőrzéseket, valamint kockázati és megfelelési célokból. A személyes adatokat felhasználhatjuk a megfelelő üzleti nyilvántartások vezetésére, valamint szabályzataink és eljárásaink érvényesítésére is. A TMG a „jogos érdek” jogalapra (GDPR/UK GDPR 6. cikk (1) bekezdés f) pontja és nDSG 31. cikk (1) bekezdése) hivatkozik. A TMG jogos érdeke az üzleti tevékenység védelmének biztosítása, valamint annak rendszeres ellenőrzése, hogy a jelentési és megfelelési kötelezettségek teljesülnek-e.
    
* **Általános üzleti és működési támogatás** . Az egyesülések, felvásárlások, átszervezések, csődeljárások és egyéb üzleti tranzakciók, például finanszírozások felmérése és végrehajtása, valamint az üzleti, számviteli, ellenőrzési, megfelelőségi, nyilvántartási és jogi funkciók ellátása céljára. A TMG a „jogos érdek” jogalapra (DSGVO 6. (1) bekezdés f) pontja és nDSG 31. cikk (1) bekezdése). Ebben a környezetben a TMG-nek érdekében áll, hogy a potenciális vevőkkel vagy felvásárlókkal és külső tanácsadóikkal információkat osszon meg és más módon feldolgozza az eszközeire és tevékenységeire vonatkozó információkat annak érdekében, hogy megkönnyítse ezen eszközök és/vagy tevékenységek eladását.

A sütik és hasonló technológiák használatával kapcsolatos céljainkat, különösen a célzással és az elemzéssel kapcsolatban a 6. szakasz: Sütik, célzás és elemzés című részben ismertetjük.

Ha az adatkezelés jogalapja az Ön hozzájárulása, Önnek jogában áll hozzájárulását bármikor visszavonni. Ugyanakkor a hozzájárulás visszavonása nem érinti az Ön visszavonás előtti hozzájárulása alapján végzett adatkezelés jogszerűségét. Ha a jogalap jogos érdek , akkor Ön jogosult arra is, hogy általános jelleggel bármikor tiltakozzon személyes adatai feldolgozása ellent az Ön egyedi helyzetéből adódó okokból. Ezenkívül jogában áll bármikor tiltakozni személyes adatainak közvetlen marketing célú feldolgozása ellen. E tekintetben a GDPR 21. cikke / UK GDPR alkalmazandó.

Regisztrációkor vagy később is bármikor tiltakozhat az ellen, hogy e-mail-címét promóciós célokra vagy személyes útmutatásra használjuk.

**4\. A személyes adatok közzététele**

Az általunk a fent leírt célokból összegyűjtött személyes adatokat továbbadhatjuk, Szolgáltatásaink nyújtása céljára, hogy válaszoljunk és teljesítsük kéréseit, az Ön egyéb utasításai vagy beleegyezése szerint, a következő címzettekkel:

* **Márkák, társvállalatok és leányvállalatok** . A gyűjtött személyes adatokat megoszthatjuk márkáinkkal, társvállalatainkkal és leányvállalatainkkal.
    
* **Üzleti partnerek** . Bizonyos körülmények között a TMG együttműködhet más vállalatokkal a Szolgáltatások nyújtása érdekében, többek között bizonyos programok vagy speciális ajánlatok elősegítése érdekében, és ezeknek az üzleti partnereknek személyes adatokat adhatunk át.
    
* **Beszállítók és szolgáltatók** . Az általunk gyűjtött személyes információkat átadhatjuk olyan beszállítóknak és szolgáltatóknak, akik a nevünkben látnak el funkciókat, mint például IT és weboldal hosting, fizetési szolgáltatók, marketing és marketingkutatási szolgáltatók, ügyfélszolgálati, adattárolási, adatelemzési szolgáltatók, könyvvizsgálók, tanácsadók, szakértők és ügynökök, valamint jogi tanácsadók.
    
* **Egyéb TMG-felhasználók** . A Szolgáltatások más felhasználóival a közösségi természetű funkciók kontextusában. Például, ha Ön meghív másokat a Szolgáltatásaink használatára, vagy ha Ön nyilvános, interaktív funkcióinkon, közösségi fórumokon vagy vitablogokon keresztül nyújt be vagy tesz elérhetővé információkat, beleértve azt is, amikor Ön értékeléseket vagy véleményeket tesz közzé, bizonyos személyes adatok a Szolgáltatások más felhasználói számára elérhetővé és kereshetővé válhatnak. Például, ha Ön részt vesz a Pets játékban, a Pets többi felhasználója láthatja személyes adatait, például az Ön profilképét, nemét, értékét, készpénzét, vagyontárgyait, amelyek tulajdonosa és a Pets kisállatok számát.
    
* **Harmadik fél marketing- és elemzési szolgáltatók** . Ezenkívül személyes adataidat, például az eszközzel és a böngészéssel, valamint a tevékenységgel és a használattal kapcsolatos információkat továbbíthatjuk olyan harmadik fél marketing- és adatelemző szolgáltatóknak, valamint más vállalatoknak, amelyek marketing-, reklám-, kampánykezelési vagy elemzési szolgáltatásokat nyújtanak a mi megbízásunkból. A címzettek részletes ismertetését lásd a hozzájárulásokat kezelő platformon az alkalmazásban.

Személyes adatait az alábbi körülmények között adhatjuk ki:

* **Üzletek átadásának támogatására** . Ha minket vagy kapcsolt vállalatainkat egy másik vállalat felvásárolja vagy megszerzi, azzal összeolvad vagy abba befektetnek, vagy ha bármelyik vagyontárgyunkat egy másik vállalatra ruházzák vagy ruházhatják át, akár csőd- vagy fizetésképtelenségi eljárás részeként, akár más módon, akkor az Öntől általunk gyűjtött személyes adatokat a másik vállalat számára a vonatkozó törvényeknek megfelelően átadhatjuk vagy továbbíthatjuk. Az ilyen tranzakció vagy más vállalati tranzakció, például finanszírozás vagy átszervezés befejezése előtt szükség esetén bizonyos személyes adatokat is átadhatunk hitelezőknek, könyvvizsgálóknak és harmadik fél tanácsadóknak, beleértve az ügyvédeket és szakértőket is.
    
* **Megfelelés és jogi kötelezettségek** . A személyes információkat harmadik feleknek is átadhatjuk, amennyiben ezt az alkalmazandó jogszabályok és jogi kötelezettségek megkövetelik. Például, megoszthatunk a szabályozó és kormányzati szervek, bűnüldöző szervek kérésére információkat idézés, bírósági végzés vagy más törvényes kérés kapcsán, beleértve a nemzetbiztonsági vagy bűnüldözési ügyek által megkövetelt megosztást, vagy a törvény vagy jogi eljárás által megkövetelt információkat. Ezen kívül és adott esetben a vonatkozó jogszabályoknak megfelelően nyilvánosságra hozhatjuk a nyereményjátékok és a vetélkedők nyerteseinek nevét.
    
* **Biztonság és a jogok védelme** . Amikor úgy gondoljuk, hogy a Szolgáltatások, jogaink és tulajdonunk, vagy mások jogainak, tulajdonának és biztonságának védelme érdekében szükséges. Például, megoszthatunk személyes adatokat (i) csalás, jogosulatlan tevékenységek és hozzáférés, illegális tevékenységek és a Szolgáltatásokkal való visszaélés megelőzése, észlelése, kivizsgálása és azokra történő reagálás céljára, (ii) bármely személy vagy harmadik fél egészségét, biztonságát vagy jogait potenciálisan veszélyeztető helyzetekben, vagy (iii) a Felhasználási feltételeink megsértése esetén történő végrehajtás, észlelés, kivizsgálás és intézkedések megtétele érdekében. Személyes adatokat adhatunk ki peres és egyéb jogi követelésekkel vagy bírósági eljárásokkal kapcsolatban is, amelyekben érintettek vagyunk, valamint belső számviteli, ellenőrzési, megfelelési, nyilvántartási és jogi feladataink ellátása céljából.
    
* **Egyéb információk** . Személyes adatokat más, a fentiektől eltérő módon is kiadhatunk, amiről értesítjük Önt, vagy amihez az Ön beleegyezését kérjük, vagy amire egyébként felhatalmazást kaptunk, illetve amit törvény ír elő.

A jelen Szabályzatban foglaltaktól függetlenül felhasználhatunk és hozzáférhetővé tehetünk összesített, nem azonosított és egyéb, nem azonosítható adatokat a vállalkozásunkkal és a Szolgáltatásokkal kapcsolatban minőség-ellenőrzési, elemzési, kutatási, fejlesztési és más célokra. Amennyiben álnevesített adatokat (olyan adatokat, amelyek már ésszerűen nem kapcsolhatók vagy nem kapcsolhatók azonosított vagy azonosítható természetes személyhez, háztartáshoz vagy személyes vagy háztartási eszközhöz) használunk fel, osztunk meg vagy dolgozunk fel, az adatokat álnevesített formában őrizzük és használjuk fel, és nem kíséreljük meg újra beazonosítani az adatokat, kivéve annak meghatározása céljából, hogy az álnevesítő eljárások ésszerűek és megfelelőek-e az alkalmazandó adatvédelmi jogszabályok szerint.

**5\. Személyes adatok továbbítása az EGT/UK/CH területén kívüli országokba**

A személyes adatok fogadói az EGT/UK/Svájc területén kívül is lehetnek. Amennyiben a személyes adatokat az EGT/UK/Svájc területén kívüli helyekre továbbítjuk (beleértve a GDPR/UK GDPR/nDSG hatálya alá tartozó adatkezelőként az Egyesült Államokban található USA-beli címzetteknek vagy más, az EGT/UK/Svájc területén kívüli, a GDPR/UK GDPR/nDSG hatálya alá nem tartozó országokba történő továbbítást), a törvény által előírt módon biztosítjuk, hogy az Ön adatvédelmi jogai megfelelő védelmet élvezzenek, vagy azért, mert az Európai Bizottság úgy döntött, hogy az az ország, ahová a személyes adatokat továbbítják, megfelelő szintű védelmet biztosít (GDPR 45. cikk/UK GDPR), vagy az adattovábbítás megfelelő biztosítékok (pl. az Európai Unió szabványos adatvédelmi záradékai, amelyekről a fogadóval megállapodtak) hatálya alá tartozik (GDPR/ 46. cikke/UK GDPR), kivéve, ha a GDPR/UK GDPR kivételt tesz (GDPR/ 49. cikke/UK GDPR). Ezen túlmenően szükség esetén további intézkedésekről szándékozunk megállapodni a címzettekkel a megfelelő szintű adatvédelem biztosítása érdekében. Lásd még az nDSG 16. cikk f. pontját a személyes adatok Svájcon kívül történő közlésére vonatkozóan.

Szükség esetén szerződéses partnereinkkel is kötünk egy megfelelő „UK Kiegészítést” az Adatvédelmi Biztos Hivatala (ICO) követelményeinek megfelelően, valamint egy megfelelő „CH Kiegészítést” a svájci Szövetségi Adatvédelmi és Információs Biztos (FDPIC) követelményeinek megfelelően.

A megfelelő biztosítékok másolatát (amennyiben erre támaszkodunk) és az EGT/UK/Svájc területén kívüli címzettek listáját a [support@themeetgroup.com](mailto:support@themeetgroup.com) címen kérheti. Felhívjuk figyelmét, hogy az üzleti titkok vagy más bizalmas információk védelme érdekében az ilyen másolatok a szükséges mértékben cenzúrázhatók.

**6\. Sütik, célzás és elemzés**

Mi és harmadik fél szolgáltatók sütiket, pixeleket, helyi tárolóobjektumokat, naplófájlokat és egyéb nyomon követési mechanizmusokat használunk, hogy Szolgáltatásainkban automatikusan gyűjtsük a böngészési, aktivitási, eszköz- és egyéb hasonló információkat. Ezeket az információkat arra használjuk, hogy elemezzük és megértsük, hogyan férnek hozzá a felhasználók a Szolgáltatásainkhoz, hogyan használják azokat, és hogyan lépnek kapcsolatba azokkal, hogy beazonosítsuk és megoldjuk a Szolgáltatásainkban lévő programhibákat és hibákat, hogy felmérjük a biztonságot, hogy megvédjük, optimalizáljuk és javítsuk a Szolgáltatásaink teljesítményét, valamint marketing és elemzési célokra használjuk azokat, és személyre szabjuk a Szolgáltatásaink tartalmát. Az Ön tartózkodási helyétől függően ez többnyire csak akkor történik meg , ha Ön a CMP használatával hozzájárulását adta, amelyet az alkalmazás beállításaiban talál , ahol kezelheti a hozzájárulását/preferenciáit a Szolgáltatásainkban a sütikkel, célzott hirdetésekkel és más hasonló nyomon követési mechanizmusokkal kapcsolatban , lásd a 7. szakaszt: Az Ön adatvédelmi választásai című részt alább. Számos ilyen választás böngésző- és eszközspecifikus, ami azt jelenti, hogy Önnek minden egyes böngészőhöz és eszközhöz, amelyet a Szolgáltatásaink eléréséhez használ, meg kell adnia a beállításokat. Ezenkívül, ha Ön törli vagy blokkolja a sütiket, előfordulhat, hogy ezeket a beállításokat újra meg kell adnia minden egyes böngészőre és/vagy eszközre.

**Sütik** . A „sütik” kisméretű szöveges fájlok, amelyeket a felhasználó eszközén (például számítógépen vagy okostelefonon) tárol az általa felkeresett webhely. A sütiket a weboldal szervere hozza létre, és elküldi a felhasználó böngészőjének, ahol későbbi hivatkozás céljából elmentésre kerül. Egyes sütik lehetővé teszik számunkra, hogy megkönnyítsük az Ön számára a Szolgáltatásainkban való navigálást, miközben másokat például a gyorsabb bejelentkezés biztosítása, a Szolgáltatások biztonságának és teljesítményének támogatása, vagy a Szolgáltatásokon belüli felhasználói aktivitással kapcsolatos összesített és statisztikai információk nyomon követése céljából használunk.

**Pixelcímkék** . A pixelcímkék (amelyeket néha webes jelzőfájloknak vagy clear GIF-eknek is neveznek) apró grafikák egyedi azonosítóval, funkciójukban pedig hasonlítanak a sütikhez. Míg a sütiket helyileg tároljuk az Ön eszközén, addig a pixelcímkéket láthatatlanul építjük be a weboldalakba és az online tartalmakba. Felhasználhatjuk ezeket a Szolgáltatásainkkal kapcsolatban, többek között a felhasználók tevékenységének nyomon követésére, valamint a tartalom kezelésének és a felhasználási statisztikák összeállításához. Ezeket az e-mailjeinkben is felhasználhatjuk, hogy megtudjuk, ha azokat megnyitották vagy továbbították, így nyomon követhetjük a válaszadási arányokat és felmérhetjük a kommunikációnk hatékonyságát.

**Naplófájlok** . A naplófájlokból bizonyos tevékenységi információkat gyűjthetünk. A naplófájlok adatait automatikusan gyűjtjük, amikor Ön hozzáfér a Weboldalainkhoz. Ezekből a naplófájlokból bizonyos információkat rögzítünk, beleértve a webes kéréseket, az IP-címet, a böngésző típusát és verzióját, a nyelvre vonatkozó információt, a hivatkozó és kilépő URL-címeket, a kattintott linkeket, a megtekintett oldalakat és más hasonló információkat.

**Harmadik féltől származó elemzések** . A Szolgáltatásaink használatának értékeléséhez automatizált készülékeket, alkalmazásokat és eszközöket használhatunk, például a Google Analyticset, amelyeket harmadik fél által üzemeltetett cégek működtetnek. Eme harmadik fél vállalatok sütiket, pixeleket és egyéb nyomkövető technológiákat használhatnak a Szolgáltatásainkkal kapcsolatos használati adatok gyűjtésére, valamint olyan jelentések és mérőszámok szolgáltatására, amelyek segítenek a Szolgáltatásaink használatának értékelésében, valamint a teljesítmény és a felhasználói élmény javításában. Ha többet szeretne megtudni a Google adatvédelmi gyakorlatairól, tekintse át a Google adatvédelmi irányelveit a [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)címen. A [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) címen letöltheti a Google Analytics letiltó böngészőbővítményt is, hogy megakadályozza adatainak a Google Analytics általi felhasználását. Az általunk e téren bevont harmadik felek listája megtalálható a CMP-ben, amelyet az alkalmazás beállításaiban találhat.

**Harmadik fél hirdetési vállalatok** . Harmadik fél hirdetési hálózatokkal, marketing partnerekkel, mobil hirdetési hálózatokkal és másokkal („harmadik fél hirdetési vállalatok”) együtt dolgozunk a tartalom személyre szabása és a Szolgáltatásainkban szereplő hirdetések megjelenítése, valamint a harmadik fél weboldalainkon megjelenő hirdetéseink kezelése céljából. Mi és ezen harmadik fél hirdető cégek sütiket, pixelcímkéket, SDK-ket (szoftverfejlesztő készleteket) és egyéb eszközöket használhatnak a böngészési és tevékenységi információk gyűjtésére a Szolgáltatásainkon belül (valamint harmadik fél weboldalain és szolgáltatásain), valamint IP-címet, egyedi azonosítót, süti- és reklámazonosítókat és egyéb online azonosítókat. Mi és ezek a harmadik féltől származó hirdetési cégek arra használjuk ezeket az információkat, hogy megfelelőbb hirdetéseket és tartalmakat nyújtsunk Önnek a Szolgáltatásainkban és harmadik fél webhelyein, valamint hogy kiértékeljük az ilyen hirdetések és tartalmak eredményességét. A harmadik fél hirdető vállalatok listája megtalálható a CMP-ben, amelyet az alkalmazás beállításaiban találhat.

**Eszközök közötti használat** . Mi és harmadik fél szolgáltatóink felhasználhatják az Önről gyűjtött információkat (akár közvetlenül az oldalainkon vagy mobilalkalmazásunkon keresztül, az Ön eszközén (eszközein) keresztül vagy harmadik féltől származó forrásokból), hogy segítségünkre legyenek nekünk és harmadik fél szolgáltatóinknak azonosítani az Ön által használt további eszközöket (pl. mobiltelefon, táblagép, másik számítógép stb.). Mi és harmadik fél szolgáltatóink arra is felhasználhatjuk az eszközök közötti használatot és az Önről szerzett egyéb információkat, hogy célzott hirdetéseket vagy személyre szabott tartalmat nyújtsunk Szolgáltatásainkban.

**Egyéni listák és egyezés** . Megoszthatunk vagy elérhetővé tehetünk bizonyos ügyféllistán szereplő információkat (például az Ön nevét, e-mail-címét és egyéb kapcsolattartási adatait) harmadik féllel, hogy jobban meg tudjuk célozni a hirdetéseket és a tartalmat az Ön számára harmadik fél weboldalain, platformjain és szolgáltatásain keresztül. Bizonyos esetekben ezek a harmadik felek segíthetnek nekünk abban, hogy ügyféllistáinkat újabb demográfiai vagy más ehhez hasonló információkkal bővítsük, hogy reklám- és marketingkampányainkat jobban tudjuk célozni.

**7\. Az Ön adatvédelmi választásai**

**A preferenciák kezelése** . Az alábbiakban leírtak szerint többféle módon is lehetősége van arra, hogy preferenciáit és adatvédelmi választásait kezelje:

* **Fiók és profil** . Az általunk Önről tárolt személyes adatok egyes részeit felülvizsgálhatja és frissítheti, ha bejelentkezik a fiókjába, és frissíti a fiók- és profiladatait.
    
* **Marketing kommunikáció** . Időnként promóciós e-maileket, tartalmat vagy más hasonló kommunikációt küldhetünk Önnek. Ezekről a kommunikációkról leiratkozhat, ha követi a kommunikációban megadott utasításokat. Ha nem szeretne tőlünk promóciós tartalmakat kapni, ennek ellenére továbbra is küldhetünk Önnek üzeneteket a fiókjával vagy a tőlünk kért vagy kapott szolgáltatásokkal kapcsolatban. Ezenkívül a fiók- és profilbeállításokban is kezelheti kommunikációs beállításait.
    
* **Push értesítések** . A tőlünk kapott push értesítések típusát a mobilkészülék beállításainak módosításával vagy a Mobilalkalmazásban található beállítások módosításával tudja kezelni. Ezek olyan üzenetek, amelyeket a szerződés teljesítése során küldünk Önnek, valamint promóciós információt tartalmaznak.

**Süti- és követési beállítások/célzott hirdetések/elemzések** . Az alábbiakban leírtak szerint többféle módon is lehetősége van arra, hogy a Szolgáltatásainkban lévő sütikkel, célzott hirdetésekkel, elemzésekkel és más hasonló követési mechanizmusok preferenciáit kezelje. Számos ilyen választás böngésző- és eszközspecifikus, ami azt jelenti, hogy Önnek minden egyes böngészőhöz és eszközhöz, amelyet a Szolgáltatásaink eléréséhez használ, meg kell adnia a beállításokat. Ezenkívül, ha Ön törli vagy blokkolja a sütiket, előfordulhat, hogy ezeket a beállításokat újra meg kell adnia minden egyes böngészőre és/vagy eszközre. Továbbá, ha leiratkozik a sütikről és reklámokról, az nem jelenti azt, hogy többé nem kap reklámtartalmat tőlünk, és továbbra is kaphat általános vagy „kontextusfüggő” hirdetéseket.

* **Hozzájárulásokat kezelő platform (CMP).** Annak érdekében, hogy a sütik vagy más követési mechanizmusok, amelyek nem feltétlenül szükségesek, ne tudják követni az Ön tevékenységét az oldalainkon vagy a mobilalkalmazásunkban, használja a Hozzájárulásokat kezelő platformot, amelyet a sütik és a követési mechanizmusok használata előtt kínálunk Önnek. A hozzájárulást a jövőre nézve bármikor vissza lehet vonni. Részletesebb információkért lásd a 15. szakaszt: A További adatvédelmi információk egyes joghatóságokhoz című részt, amelyek további információkat tartalmaznak az egyes joghatóságok lakosainak adatvédelmi jogairól.
    
* **Sütibeállítások** . Annak érdekében, hogy a sütik ne követhessék nyomon az Ön tevékenységét a weboldalainkon vagy a több weboldalon tett látogatásait, beállíthatja a böngészőjét úgy, hogy bizonyos sütiket blokkoljon, vagy értesítse Önt, amikor egy süti beállításra kerül. A sütiket ki is törölheti. A legtöbb böngésző eszköztárának „Súgó” része tájékoztatja Önt arról, hogyan lehet megelőzni, hogy az eszköze új sütiket fogadjon el, hogyan lehet elérni, hogy a böngésző értesítse Önt, ha új sütit kap, vagy hogyan törölheti a sütiket. A sütiket letiltó látogatók böngészhetnek az oldalakon, de egyes funkciók nem fognak működni.
    
* **Böngészőjelzők** . Az alkalmazandó jogszabályok által megkövetelt mértékben, ha a weboldalaink azt észlelik, hogy az Ön böngészője egy opt-out preferencia jelzőt, például egy „globális adatvédelmi vezérlő” (vagy GPC) jelzőt továbbít, akkor ezt a jelet alkalmazzuk, hogy az adott böngésző az Ön eszközén ne használhassa a weboldalainkon lévő célzott sütiket. Ha egy másik eszközről vagy ugyanazon a készüléken egy másik böngészőből érkezik weboldalunkra, akkor ehhez a böngészőhöz és/vagy eszközhöz is alkalmaznia kell a GPC-t.
    
* **Iparági hirdetésválasztási programok** . Azt is ellenőrizheti, hogy a részt vevő harmadik fél hirdető cégek hogyan használják fel az általuk az Ön és harmadik felek webhelyein tett látogatásairól gyűjtött információkat annak érdekében, hogy relevánsabb célzott hirdetéseket jelenítsenek meg az Ön számára. A webes nyomkövetési mechanizmusokkal kapcsolatos információkért és segítségért keresse fel a [www.YourOnlineChoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/) oldalt.

Bizonyos joghatóságok lakosai további jogokkal rendelkezhetnek személyes adataik vonatkozásában, az alábbi, 15. szakaszban leírtak szerint. További adatvédelmi információk bizonyos joghatóságok felé

**8\. A személyes adatok tárolási időszaka**

Személyes adatait mindaddig tároljuk, amíg az szükséges a 3. szakasz: Gyűjtés és feldolgozás céljai és a 6. szakasz: Sütik, célzás és elemzés című részekben foglalt célok eléréséhez, vagy amíg jogos érdekünk fűződik a további tároláshoz. Minden egyéb esetben töröljük az Ön személyes adatait, kivéve az olyan adatokat, amelyeket továbbra is meg kell őriznünk a törvényes megőrzési határidők betartása érdekében (pl. az adó- vagy kereskedelmi jogszabályokból eredő, például számlákra vonatkozó adatok). Azon személyes adatok feldolgozását, amelyeket csak az őrzési kötelezettség miatt őrzünk meg, korlátozzuk.

A sütik és egyéb nyomkövetési mechanizmusok tárolási időtartamára vonatkozó információk a CMP-ben találhatók, amelyet az alkalmazás beállításaiban talál.

**9\. Külső hivatkozások és szolgáltatások**

A Szolgáltatásaink hivatkozásokat tartalmazhatnak harmadik fél webhelyeire vagy funkcióira, vagy bizonyos harmadik féltől származó kapcsolatokat vagy integrált szolgáltatásokat biztosíthatnak. Az ilyen kapcsolt weboldalakhoz vagy funkciókhoz való hozzáférés és azok használata nem tartozik a jelen Szabályzat hatálya alá, hanem az adott harmadik felek adatvédelmi irányelvei vonatkoznak rájuk. Nem vagyunk felelősek az ilyen harmadik felek információs gyakorlatáért, beleértve az Ön személyes adatainak gyűjtését, felhasználását és megosztását. Mielőtt továbblépne ezekre a weboldalakra vagy használná ezeket a funkciókat, tekintse át a harmadik felek adatvédelmi szabályzatát és feltételeit.

**10\. A felhasználó által generált tartalom**

Szolgáltatásainkkal kapcsolatban nyilvános interaktív funkciókat, közösségi fórumokat vagy vitablogokat kínálhatunk, amelyek lehetővé teszik, hogy információkat osszon meg a Szolgáltatásokkal vagy egyéb érdekes kérdésekkel kapcsolatban (pl. értékeléseket, véleményeket és kérdéseket). Tudatában kell lennie annak, hogy az Ön által a Szolgáltatások bármely ilyen interaktív funkciójába beküldött vagy közzétett kommunikáció mások, így a TMG felhasználók és a nyilvánosság számára is megtekinthető és kereshető. Az ilyen nyilvános, interaktív funkciókba történő beküldéssel vagy közzététellel Ön tudomásul veszi, hogy az ilyen funkciókba beküldött tartalommal kapcsolatban nem számíthat adatvédelemre vagy titoktartásra, függetlenül attól, hogy az tartalmaz-e Önre vonatkozó személyes adatokat vagy sem.

**11\. Biztonság**

Észszerű óvintézkedéseket tettünk azért, hogy az általunk gyűjtött információkat megóvjuk az elvesztéstől, a visszaéléstől, a jogosulatlan hozzáféréstől, a nyilvánosságra hozataltól, a módosítástól és a megsemmisüléstől. Kérjük, vegye figyelembe, hogy minden erőfeszítésünk ellenére semmilyen adatbiztonsági intézkedés sem garantálja a biztonságot.

**12\. Gyermekek adatvédelme**

Szolgáltatásainkat nem gyermekek számára terveztük, és tudatosan nem gyűjtjük a tizennyolc (18) év alatti gyermekek adatait. Ha tudomást szerzünk arról, hogy személyes adatok gyűjtésére került sor a Szolgáltatásokon 18 év alatti személyektől, akkor megtesszük a megfelelő lépéseket ezen adatok törlésére. Ha Ön szülő vagy törvényes gyám, és úgy véli, hogy gyermeke információt a vonatkozó jogszabályok megsértésével gyűjtöttük, kérjük, vegye fel velünk a kapcsolatot az alább elérhetőségen.

**13\. Jelen szabályzat változásai**

Ez a szabályzat a fenti dátummal hatályos. A szabályzatot időről időre változtathatjuk, frissíthetjük vagy módosíthatjuk, ezért kérjük, rendszeresen látogasson ide. A jelen Szabályzat minden frissítését itt tesszük közzé. Ha a jelen Szabályzatban olyan változtatásokat végzünk, amelyek lényegesen befolyásolják az Öntől korábban gyűjtött személyes adatok felhasználására vonatkozó gyakorlatunkat, igyekszünk Önt erről értesíteni, például e-mailben vagy a weboldalainkon, a mobilalkalmazásunkban vagy a Szolgáltatásokon belül közzétett feltűnő értesítéssel.

**14\. Kapcsolattartás**

Ha bármilyen kérdése vagy aggálya van jelen Szabályzattal vagy az adatvédelmi gyakorlatunkkal kapcsolatban, küldjön e-mailt a [support@themeetgroup.com](mailto:support@themeetgroup.com) címre, vagy vegye fel velünk a kapcsolatot ezen a címen:

The Meet Group, Inc.

100 Union Square Drive

New Hope, PA 18938

Adatvédelmi biztosunkat a következő címen érheti el:

ePrivacy GmbH, képviselője Prof. Dr. Christoph Bauer, Große Bleichen 21, 20354 Hamburg, [privacy@themeetgroup.com](mailto:privacy@themeetgroup.com)

Az adatai biztonságával kapcsolatos bármilyen kéréssel forduljon adatvédelmi biztosunkhoz a [privacy@themeetgroup.com](mailto:privacy@themeetgroup.com) címen.

A GDPR 27. cikke szerinti EU képviselőnket a következő címen érheti el: ParshipMeet Holding GmbH, Speersort 10, 20095 Hamburg, e-mail: [privacy@parshipmeet.com](mailto:privacy@parshipmeet.com)

Az Egyesült Királyságbeli képviselőnk adatait a UK GDPR 27. cikke szerint a 15.B. szakasz tartalmazza. További információk az Egyesült Királyság lakosai számára

Svájci képviselőnk adatait az nDSG (új svájci adatvédelmi törvény) 14. cikke szerint a 15.C. szakasz tartalmazza.További információk Svájc lakosai számára.

Treforma AG c/o MLL Legal; Grabenstrasse 25; 6340 Baar; Switzerland; [meetgroup@dsg-mll.com](mailto:meetgroup@dsg-mll.com)

**15\. További adatvédelmi információk bizonyos joghatóságok felé**

Bizonyos joghatóságok lakosai további jogokkal rendelkezhetnek a vonatkozó adatvédelmi szabályzatok értelmében, a jelen szakaszban leírtak szerint.

**A. GDPR**

Ha Ön az Európai Unió lakosa, a GDPR értelmében az alábbi jogokkal rendelkezik, feltéve, hogy az abban foglalt jogi követelmények teljesültek:

**Hozzáférés joga** - Ön tájékoztatást kérhet személyes adatai kezeléséről, valamint kérheti a feldolgozott személyes adatainak másolatát, amennyiben ez a másolat nem érinti hátrányosan mások jogait és szabadságait, és nem vonatkozik más kivétel.

**Helyesbítéshez való jog** - Ön kérheti személyes adatainak helyesbítését és/vagy a hiányos adatok kiegészítését.

**Törléshez való jog** - Ön kérheti adatainak törlését, különösen akkor, ha

* a személyes adatokra már nincs szükség azokra a célokra, amelyekhez azokat gyűjtötték vagy más módon feldolgozták,
    
* Ön visszavonta az adatkezelés alapjául szolgáló hozzájárulását, és az adatkezelésnek nincs másik jogalapja,
    
* Ön tiltakozott az adatkezelés ellen, amelynek jogalapja „jogos érdeken” alapul, és az adatkezelésre nincs nyomós jogos indok, vagy tiltakozott a direkt marketing célú adatkezelés ellen,
    
* személyes adatait jogellenesen kezelték, vagy
    
* az Ön személyes adatait törölni kell a ránk vonatkozó jogi kötelezettség teljesítése érdekében.

A törléshez való jog azonban nem alkalmazható különösen akkor, ha az Ön személyes adatainak feldolgozása jogi kötelezettség teljesítéséhez vagy jogi igények előterjesztéséhez, érvényesítéséhez vagy védelméhez szükséges.

**Az adatkezelés korlátozásához való jog** - Ön kérheti az adatkezelés korlátozását

* arra az időtartamra, ameddig az Ön személyes adatai pontosságát ellenőrizzük, amennyiben Ön vitatta a személyes adatok pontosságát,
    
* ha az adatkezelés jogellenes, és az adatok törlése helyett az adatkezelés korlátozását kéri,
    
* ha már nincs szükségünk a személyes adatokra, de Ön kéri azokat jogi igények előterjesztéséhez, érvényesítéséhez vagy védelméhez, vagy
    
* Ön tiltakozott az adatkezelés ellen, amelynek jogalapja „jogos érdeken” alapul, amíg nem kerül ellenőrzésre, hogy a mi jogos indokaink felülírják-e az Ön érdekeit, jogait és szabadságait.

**Az adathordozhatósághoz való jog** - Ön kérheti, hogy az Ön által rendelkezésünkre bocsátott adatait szervezett, széles körben használt géppel olvasható formátumban megkapja, és ezeket akadályoztatásunk nélkül továbbítsa egy másik adatkezelőnek , ahol az adatkezelésre hozzájárulás alapján vagy szerződés teljesítése alapján kerül sor, és az adatkezelés automatizált módon történik; ezekben az esetekben kérheti a személyes adatok közvetlen továbbítását egy másik adatkezelőhöz, amennyiben az technikailag megvalósítható.

Ezenkívül Önnek jogában állnak az alábbiak:

**Hozzájárulás visszavonásának joga -** A hozzájárulását a jövőben bármikor visszavonhatja, ha az adatkezelés alapját az Ön hozzájárulása képezi, anélkül, hogy ez befolyásolná a visszavonás előtti hozzájáruláson alapuló adatkezelés jogszerűségét.

**A tiltakozás joga -**

**Ön jogosult arra, hogy az Ön egyedi helyzetével kapcsolatos okokra hivatkozva bármikor tiltakozzon személyes adatainak olyan kezelése ellen, amely a mi vagy egy harmadik fél jogos érdekén alapul (GDPR 6. cikk (1) bekezdés f) pontja). Ezután nem kezeljük tovább az Ön személyes adatait arra a célra, amely ellen Ön tiltakozott, kivéve, ha bizonyítani tudjuk, hogy az adatkezelést olyan kényszerítő erejű jogalap indokolja, amely elsőbbséget élvez az Ön érdekeivel, jogaival és szabadságaival szemben, vagy jogi igények előterjesztéséhez, érvényesítéséhez vagy védelméhez szükséges.**

**Ezenkívül jogában áll bármikor tiltakozni személyes adatainak közvetlen marketing célú feldolgozása ellen. Ha tiltakozik a direkt marketing célú adatkezelés ellen, személyes adatait a továbbiakban már nem kezeljük ilyen célból.**

* * *

**Panasztétel joga –** Ön panasszal élhet felügyeleti hatóságnál, különösen a tartózkodási helye, munkahelye vagy az állítólagos jogsértés helye szerinti tagállamban , ha úgy véli, hogy személyes adatainak kezelése sérti a GDPR-t.

A számunkra illetékes adatvédelmi hatóság:

Free and Hanseatic City of Hamburg, The Hamburg Commissioner for Data Protection and Freedom of Information, Ludwig-Erhard-Str. 22, 20459 Hamburg, e-mail: [mailbox@datenschutz.hamburg.de](mailto:mailbox@datenschutz.hamburg.de)

**B. UK GDPR**

Ha Ön az Egyesült Királyságban lakik, az Egyesült Királyság GDPR-je és az adatvédelmi törvények értelmében Önnek különbözői jogai vannak. Az, hogy a jogok érvényesülnek-e, és milyen mértékben, a körülmények függvénye. Ezen jogok bármelyikének gyakorlásához kérjük, használja az alábbi elérhetőségeket. A jogok a következők:

**Tájékoztatáshoz való jog** -- Önnek joga van ahhoz, hogy tömör, átlátható, közérthető és könnyen hozzáférhető tájékoztatást kapjon személyes adatairól és azok felhasználásáról. Jelen Szabályzat célja az, hogy tájékoztassuk Önt ezekről az információkról, de további kérdés esetén használja az alábbi elérhetőségeket.

**A hozzáférés joga** -- Önnek jogában áll másolatot kérni személyes adatairól. Ez a jog minden esetben él, néhány kivételtől eltekintve, ami azt jelenti, hogy nem mindig fogja megkapni a kért információt. Személyes adatainak igénylésekor ennek megnevezése az adatalany hozzáférési kérelme (DSAR). Személyazonosító okmányt kérhetünk Öntől annak érdekében, hogy igazolhassuk személyazonosságát, amikor Öntől DSAR érkezik.

**Helyesbítéshez való jog** -- Önnek jogában áll, hogy kérje tőlünk az Ön szerint pontatlan személyes adatok helyesbítését. Önnek továbbá ahhoz is joga van, hogy olyan adatok kiegészítését kérje tőlünk, amelyekről úgy gondolja, hogy hiányosak.

**Törléshez való jog** -- Önnek jogában áll azt kérni, hogy bizonyos körülmények között töröljük az Ön személyes adatait. Jogunk van megtagadni a törlési kérelem teljesítését, ha a személyes adatot az alábbi okok valamelyike miatt dolgozzuk fel:

* A véleménynyilvánítás és az információszabadság gyakorlására.
    
* Jogi kötelezettségnek való megfeleléshez.
    
* Közérdekű feladat ellátására vagy hatósági jogkör gyakorlására.
    
* Közérdekű archiválási, tudományos kutatási, történeti kutatási vagy statisztikai célra.
    
* Jogi igények érvényesítésére vagy védelmére.

**Jog az adatkezelés korlátozásához** -- Önnek jogában áll kérnie személyes adatai kezelésének korlátozását bizonyos körülmények között. Ilyen esetben továbbra is megőrizzük az adatokat, de a továbbiakban nem dolgozzuk fel azokat. Ez a jog a törléshez való jog alternatívája. Ha az alábbi feltételek valamelyike fennáll, Ön gyakorolhatja az adatkezelés korlátozásának jogát:

* A személyes adatok pontossága vitatható.
    
* A személyes adatok kezelése jogellenes.
    
* A személyes adatokra már nincs szükségünk a feldolgozáshoz, viszont a személyes adatokra jogi eljárás részeként szükség van.
    
* A tiltakozási jog gyakorlása megtörtént és az adatkezelés státuszára vonatkozó döntés meghozataláig az adatkezelés korlátozott.

**Jog a feldolgozás elleni tiltakozáshoz -- Önnek jogában áll tiltakozni a feldolgozás ellen bizonyos körülmények között, beleértve a direkt marketinget is. Akkor is tiltakozhat, ha az adatkezelés a mi (vagy egy harmadik fél) érdekén alapul. Ezután nem kezeljük tovább az Ön személyes adatait arra a célra, amely ellen Ön tiltakozott, kivéve, ha bizonyítani tudjuk, hogy az adatkezelést olyan kényszerítő erejű jogalap indokolja, amely elsőbbséget élvez az Ön érdekeivel, jogaival és szabadságaival szemben, vagy jogi igények előterjesztéséhez, érvényesítéséhez vagy védelméhez szükséges.**

**Adathordozhatósághoz való jog** -- Ez a jog arra vonatkozik, hogy személyes adatait szervezett, széles körben használt és géppel olvasható formátumban, de csak akkor érvényes, ha az Ön hozzájárulása alapján vagy szerződés teljesítése érdekében dolgozzuk fel az információkat, vagy ha a feldolgozás automatizált.

**Hozzájárulás visszavonásának joga -** A hozzájárulását a jövőben bármikor visszavonhatja, ha az adatkezelés alapját az Ön hozzájárulása képezi, anélkül, hogy ez befolyásolná a visszavonás előtti hozzájáruláson alapuló adatkezelés jogszerűségét.

**Elérhetőség**

Ha bármelyik jogát gyakorolni kívánja, vagy bármilyen kérdése van az Ön személyes adatainak felhasználásával kapcsolatban, kérjük, használja a Kapcsolatfelvétel alatt található adatokat. Kérjük, gondoskodjon arról is, hogy a kapcsolatfelvételkor elegendő információt adjon meg ahhoz, hogy egyértelműen beazonosíthassuk Önt.

Felhívjuk figyelmét, hogy kijelöltünk egy képviselőt az Egyesült Királyságban, akivel kapcsolatba léphet a UK GDPR 27. cikke értelmében: eHarmony UK Ltd., 6-10 Great Portland Street, London W1W 8QL, Nagy-Britannia

**A személyes adatok Egyesült Királyságon kívülre továbbítása**

Az Ön adatainak Egyesült Királyságon kívülre történő továbbítása esetén alkalmazott védelemmel és biztosítékokkal kapcsolatos részletekért lásd a fenti 5. szakasz: A személyes adatok az EGT/UK/CH területén kívüli országokba történő továbbítása című részt.

**Panasz benyújtásának joga a felügyeleti hatósághoz**

Önnek jogában áll panaszt benyújtani adatvédelmi hatósághoz.

Kapcsolatba léphet az Egyesült Királyság adatvédelmi hatóságával, az adatvédelmi biztos irodájával a következő címen: Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF, Telefonszám: + 44 (0) 303 123 1113, E-mail: [casework@ico. org.uk](mailto:casework@ico.org.uk).

**C. Svájci adatvédelmi törvény**

**Hozzáférési joga** -- Önnek jogában áll másolatot kérni személyes adatairól. Ez a jog mindig érvényes, de vannak kivételek az alkalmazása alól, ami azt jelenti, hogy nem mindig kapja meg az Ön által kért összes információt. Adatok igénylésekor ennek megnevezése az adatalany hozzáférési kérelme (DSAR).

**Helyesbítéshez való jog** -- Önnek jogában áll, hogy kérje tőlünk az Ön szerint pontatlan személyes adatok helyesbítését. Önnek továbbá ahhoz is joga van, hogy olyan adatok kiegészítését kérje tőlünk, amelyekről úgy gondolja, hogy hiányosak.

**Törléshez való jog** -- Önnek jogában áll azt kérni, hogy bizonyos körülmények között töröljük az Ön személyes adatait. Jogunk van megtagadni a törlési kérelem teljesítését, ha a személyes adatot az alábbi okok valamelyike miatt dolgozzuk fel:

* A véleménynyilvánítás és az információszabadság gyakorlására.
    
* Jogi kötelezettségnek való megfeleléshez.
    
* Közérdekű feladat ellátására vagy hatósági jogkör gyakorlására.
    
* Közérdekű archiválási, tudományos kutatási, történeti kutatási vagy statisztikai célra.
    
* Jogi igények érvényesítésére vagy védelmére.

**Jog az adatkezelés korlátozásához** -- Önnek jogában áll kérnie személyes adatai kezelésének korlátozását bizonyos körülmények között. Ilyen esetben továbbra is megőrizzük az adatokat, de a továbbiakban nem dolgozzuk fel azokat. Ez a jog a törléshez való jog alternatívája. Ha az alábbi feltételek valamelyike fennáll, Ön gyakorolhatja az adatkezelés korlátozásának jogát:

* A személyes adatok pontossága vitatható.
    
* A személyes adatok kezelése jogellenes.
    
* A személyes adatokra már nincs szükségünk a feldolgozáshoz, viszont a személyes adatokra jogi eljárás részeként szükség van.
    
* A tiltakozási jog gyakorlása megtörtént és az adatkezelés státuszára vonatkozó döntés meghozataláig az adatkezelés korlátozott.

**Az Ön joga a feldolgozás elleni tiltakozáshoz** -- Önnek jogában áll bizonyos körülmények között tiltakoznia az adatkezelés ellen. Ön akkor is tiltakozhat, ha a feldolgozás közérdekű feladat, az Önre ruházott közhatalmi jogosultság gyakorlása vagy jogos érdekeink (vagy egy harmadik fél érdekei) miatt történik.

**A közvetlen marketing elleni tiltakozáshoz való jog** - Ön bármikor tiltakozhat személyes adatainak reklámcélú feldolgozása ellen is („reklám elleni tiltakozás”). Kérjük, vegye figyelembe, hogy szervezési okok miatt átfedés állhat fenn az Ön visszavonása és az Ön adatainak egy már folyamatban lévő kampány keretében történő felhasználása között.

**Adathordozhatóságához való jog** -- Ez a jog csak akkor érvényes, ha az Ön hozzájárulása alapján vagy szerződés teljesítése érdekében dolgozzuk fel az információkat , és az adatkezelés automatizált.

Ha élni szeretne bármely jogával, kérjük, használja a Kapcsolat alatt található adatokat. Kérjük, gondoskodjon arról is, hogy a kapcsolatfelvételkor elegendő információt adjon meg ahhoz, hogy egyértelműen beazonosíthassuk Önt.

**Elérhetőség**

Ha bármelyik jogát gyakorolni kívánja, vagy bármilyen kérdése van az Ön személyes adatainak felhasználásával kapcsolatban, kérjük, használja a Kapcsolatfelvétel alatt található adatokat. Kérjük, gondoskodjon arról is, hogy a kapcsolatfelvételkor elegendő információt adjon meg ahhoz, hogy egyértelműen beazonosíthassuk Önt.

Felhívjuk figyelmét, hogy svájci képviselőt jelöltünk ki az Art. 14 nDSG (új svájci adatvédelmi törvény) szerint: Treforma AG c/o MLL Legal; Grabenstrasse 25; 6340 Baar; Svájc; [meetgroup@dsg-mll.com](mailto:meetgroup@dsg-mll.com)

**A személyes adatok Svájcon kívülre továbbítása**

Az Ön adatainak Svájcon kívülre történő továbbítása esetén alkalmazott védelemmel és biztosítékokkal kapcsolatos részletekért lásd a fenti 5. szakasz: A személyes adatok az EGT-n/UK-n/CH-n kívüli országokba történő továbbítása című részt.

**Panasz benyújtásának joga a felügyeleti hatósághoz**

Önnek jogában áll panaszt benyújtani adatvédelmi hatósághoz.

Lépjen kapcsolatba a Svájcban illetékes adatvédelmi felügyeleti hatósággal . Ez a:

Szövetségi adatvédelmi és információs biztos (FDPIC).

Az alábbi elérhetőségen veheti fel vele a kapcsolatot:

[https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/de/home/deredoeb/kontakt/kontaktformular\_bgoe.html](https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/de/home/deredoeb/kontakt/kontaktformular_bgoe.html)

**The Meet Group Inc.**

Politica de confidențialitate pentru utilizatorii cu reședința în Spațiul Economic European sau în Regatul Unit
===============================================================================================================

_Ultima actualizare: October 8, 2024_

The Meet Group, Inc., mărcile, afiliații și filialele sale respectă confidențialitatea dvs. Această politică de confidențialitate („ **Politica** ”) descrie modul în care The Meet Group, Inc. („ **TMG** ”, „ **noi** ”, „ **nostru** ” sau „ **nouă** ”) colectează, utilizează, dezvăluie și procesează în orice alt mod informații cu caracter personal (denumite și date cu caracter personal în unele jurisdicții) descrise în această Politică, precum și drepturile și opțiunile pe care le aveți cu privire la aceste informații cu caracter personal.

Pentru informații suplimentare despre opțiunile de confidențialitate pe care le aveți cu privire la informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal, consultați Secțiunea 7. Opțiunile de confidențialitate, precum și Secțiunea 15. Informații suplimentare privind confidențialitatea pentru anumite jurisdicții, care includ informații suplimentare despre drepturile de confidențialitate pentru rezidenții anumitor jurisdicții.

Dacă sunteți rezident al UE/Spațiului Economic European (SEE), vă rugăm să consultați Secțiunea 15.A. Informații suplimentare pentru rezidenții din UE/SEE pentru informații despre drepturile dvs. conform Regulamentului general privind protecția datelor („GDPR”).

Dacă sunteți rezident al Regatului Unit, vă rugăm să consultați Secțiunea 15.B. Informații suplimentare pentru rezidenții din Regatul Unit pentru informații despre drepturile dvs. în temeiul Regulamentului general privind protecția datelor, astfel cum este încorporat în legislația Regatului Unit în temeiul secțiunii 3 din Legea Regatului Unit din 2018 privind Uniunea Europeană (Retragere) („UK GDPR”) .

Dacă sunteți rezident în Elveția, consultați Secțiunea 15.C. Informații suplimentare pentru rezidenții elvețieni pentru informații despre drepturile dvs. conform noii Legi elvețiene privind protecția datelor („nDSG”).

Atunci când creați un profil pe unul dintre serviciile noastre, unele dintre informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal, cum ar fi numele de utilizator, numele, vârsta, sexul și orientarea sexuală, în conformitate cu setările dvs. de confidențialitate, pot fi vizibile și pentru utilizatorii serviciului respectiv și altor servicii ale noastre și alte aplicații pe care le deținem și alte aplicații și site-uri web care nu sunt deținute de noi cu care partajăm platforma noastră live. Acești utilizatori au sediul în întreaga lume. Pentru o listă a partenerilor noștri actuali, faceți clic [aici](https://talent.tagged.com/partner-policy-tagged.html).

Utilizarea de către dvs. a serviciilor noastre este supusă [Termenilor și condițiilor](https://secure.tagged.com/terms_of_service.html) noastre, inclusiv termenilor aplicabili ai acestora care guvernează limitările privind daunele și soluționarea litigiilor.

**Cuprins**

1. Domeniul de aplicare
    
2. Informații cu caracter personal colectate
    
3. Scopuri de colectare și prelucrare
    
4. Dezvăluirea informațiilor cu caracter personal
    
5. Transferuri de date cu caracter personal în contextul țărilor situate în afara SEE/UK/CH
    
6. Module cookie, direcționare și analize
    
7. Opțiunile de confidențialitate
    
8. Perioada de stocare a informațiilor cu caracter personal
    
9. Legături externe și caracteristici
    
10. Conținut generat de utilizatori
    
11. Securitate
    
12. Confidențialitatea copiilor
    
13. Modificări ale acestei politici
    
14. CONTACTEAZĂ-NE
    
15. Informații suplimentare privind confidențialitatea pentru anumite jurisdicții

**1 Domeniul de aplicare**

Cu excepția cazului în care este descris altfel mai jos, această politică se aplică informațiilor cu caracter personal colectate și procesate de TMG în legătură cu: vizitatorii site-ului nostru web pe care este postată această politică, inclusiv oricare dintre site-urile noastre web care fac trimitere către sau postează această politică („ **site-urile** ”); persoanele care descarcă și utilizează aplicația noastră mobilă („ **aplicația mobilă** ”, de exemplu, aplicația Tagged sau aplicația Pets); persoanele care se înregistrează sau participă la evenimentele, sondajele, cercetările, promoțiile noastre și tombolele organizate de noi; și persoanele care comunică sau interacționează sau se implică în orice alt mod alături de noi sau cu serviciile disponibile prin site-urile noastre, aplicația mobilă sau alte servicii online (denumite în mod colectiv „ **serviciile** ”).

**2\. Informații personale colectate**

După cum este descris mai jos, este posibil să colectăm informații cu caracter personal direct de la dvs., din surse terțe și automat prin utilizarea de către dvs. a serviciilor noastre.

**Informații cu caracter personal colectate direct de la dvs.** Deși informațiile cu caracter personal pe care le colectăm variază în funcție de utilizarea de către dvs. a serviciilor noastre și de interacțiunile noastre cu dvs., în general, putem colecta următoarele categorii de informații cu caracter personal direct de la dvs.:

* **Informații de contact** . Când ne contactați, inclusiv dacă ne trimiteți un mesaj sau vă înscrieți pentru a afla mai multe despre serviciile noastre, este posibil să vă colectăm numele, adresa de e-mail, numărul de telefon sau alte date de identificare similare, precum și mesajul dvs., natura întrebării dvs. și orice alte informații pe care alegeți să le furnizați.
    
* **Informații despre cont și profil** . Când vă înregistrați pentru a deschide un cont în legătură cu serviciile noastre (de exemplu, pentru un cont Tagged), este posibil să vă colectăm numele, adresa de e-mail, numărul de telefon, adresa (de exemplu, codul poștal), numele de utilizator și parola, data nașterii și sexul, orientarea sexuală, imaginea de profil și fotografia și informațiile despre adresa de facturare, precum și orice alte informații furnizate în legătură cu crearea sau menținerea contului dvs. sau pe care ni le transmiteți în alt mod prin intermediul contului dvs.

Dacă ați ales o autentificare prin furnizori terți, cum ar fi Facebook sau Apple, ori SMS, nu introduceți adresa de e-mail sau parola în cadrul procesului de înregistrare. Utilizatorii accesează apoi serviciul nostru folosind adresa de e-mail pe care au furnizat-o și parola pe care au selectat-o (informații de autentificare) sau, alternativ, folosind informațiile de autentificare ale furnizorului terță parte.

**Înregistrare prin Facebook („autentificare Facebook”)**

Oferim autentificarea unică prin Facebook. Aceasta vă oferă opțiunea de a vă înregistra prin contul dvs. de Facebook. Dacă utilizați funcția, noi primim și procesăm următoarele date de autentificare de la Facebook pentru înregistrare: adresa dvs. de e-mail, numele profilului, sexul, data nașterii și fotografia de profil stocată acolo. Datele sunt transferate în acest sens.

Atunci când vă conectați la site-ul nostru web sau la aplicația noastră folosind Facebook, Facebook va colecta și date de la scripturi terțe, le va prelucra în scopuri de analiză Facebook sau le va transmite către terțe părți. Politica de confidențialitate a Facebook prezintă datele care pot fi colectate atunci când utilizați autentificarea prin Facebook. Acestea includ date despre dispozitivul dvs., utilizarea de către dvs. a serviciului nostru, site-urile web pe care le-ați vizitat și reclamele pe care le-ați vizualizat. Din păcate, din punct de vedere tehnic, nu puteți refuza această prelucrare în legătură cu serviciul nostru. Dacă nu doriți ca Facebook să colecteze date despre dvs. legate de utilizarea de către dvs. a ofertei noastre online și să le utilizeze în propriile sale scopuri, nu trebuie să utilizați conectarea prin intermediul Facebook.

Puteți disocia contul dvs. Tagged de contul dvs. Facebook în orice moment. În acest caz, va trebui să ne furnizați datele de acces menționate mai sus.

Mai multe informații despre scopul și domeniul de aplicare al colectării și prelucrarea și utilizarea ulterioară a datelor dvs. de către Facebook, precum și despre drepturile dvs. și opțiunile de configurare pentru protejarea datelor dvs. sunt disponibile în Politica de confidențialitate Facebook: [http://www.facebook.com/policy.php](http://www.facebook.com/policy.php).

**Înregistrare/autentificare prin Google**

Dacă utilizați un dispozitiv terminal Android, vă oferim opțiunea de a vă înregistra sau de a vă conecta la serviciul nostru prin contul dvs. Google. Dacă faceți acest lucru, Google Ireland Limited, Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Irlanda („Google”) ne va furniza datele necesare pentru înregistrare sau autentificare (adresă de e-mail, nume, ID-ul contului Google și poza de profil din contul Google).

Nu avem control asupra domeniului de aplicare a datelor colectate de Google folosind autentificarea prin Google. Dacă nu doriți ca Google să colecteze date despre dvs. legate de utilizarea de către dvs. a ofertei noastre online și să le utilizeze în propriile sale scopuri, nu trebuie să utilizați autentificarea prin intermediul Google.

Mai multe informații despre scopul și domeniul de aplicare al colectării și prelucrarea și utilizarea ulterioară a datelor dvs. de către Google, precum și despre drepturile dvs. și opțiunile de configurare pentru protejarea datelor dvs. sunt disponibile în Politica de confidențialitate Google: [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

**Înregistrare/autentificare prin Apple Sign-In**

Dacă utilizați un dispozitiv terminal iOS, vă oferim opțiunea de a vă înregistra sau de a vă conecta la serviciul nostru prin contul dvs. Apple. Dacă alegeți să faceți acest lucru, Apple Inc., One Apple Park Way, Cupertino, California, SUA, 95014 („Apple”) ne va furniza informațiile pe care le selectați și care sunt necesare pentru înregistrare sau autentificare (de ex., adresa de e-mail generată de Apple, numele).

Nu avem control asupra domeniului de aplicare a datelor colectate de Apple folosind autentificarea prin Apple. Dacă nu doriți ca Apple să colecteze date despre dvs. legate de utilizarea de către dvs. a ofertei noastre online și să le utilizeze în propriile sale scopuri, nu trebuie să utilizați autentificarea prin intermediul Apple.

Mai multe informații despre scopul și domeniul de aplicare al colectării și prelucrarea și utilizarea ulterioară a datelor dvs. de către Apple, precum și despre drepturile dvs. și opțiunile de configurare pentru protejarea datelor dvs. sunt disponibile în Politica de confidențialitate Apple: [https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/en/sign-in-with-apple](https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/en/sign-in-with-apple/).

**La înregistrarea/conectarea prin autentificare telefonică**

La înregistrarea/conectarea prin autentificare telefonică vă oferim autentificare prin numărul dvs. de mobil, prin urmare trebuie să ne furnizați numărul dvs. de telefon mobil. Vă vom trimite apoi un SMS cu un cod de verificare pe care trebuie să îl introduceți în aplicație pentru a finaliza procesul de înregistrare. Când doriți să vă autentificați, vă vom trimite un SMS cu un cod pe care îl puteți utiliza pentru a vă conecta în contul dvs. În plus, va avea loc un proces de verificare. Acest serviciu este oferit de Sinch America Inc., o corporație din Delaware, Departamentul Juridic, 3500 Lenox Rd NE, Ste. 1875, Atlanta, GA 30326, Georgia, SUA

și este posibil numai dacă ne-ați dat acordul dvs. prealabil.

Informații suplimentare despre scopul și domeniul de aplicare al prelucrării datelor dvs. de către Sinch pot fi găsite în politica de confidențialitate Sinch: [https://www.sinch.com/privacy-notice/](https://www.sinch.com/privacy-notice/)

* **Achiziții, plăți și recompense** . Când efectuați o achiziție sau plată prin intermediul serviciilor noastre (de exemplu, în legătură cu jocul Pets), este posibil să colectăm informații precum tipul de plată, detaliile cardului de plată, facturare, informații de cumpărare și orice alte informații financiare sau comerciale conexe necesare pentru facilitarea serviciilor noastre.
    
* **Comunicări și interacțiuni** . Când trimiteți un e-mail, sunați sau comunicați sau interacționați în orice alt mod cu noi sau cu alți utilizatori TMG, inclusiv dacă vă înscrieți pentru listele noastre de corespondență, completați formulare pe site-urile sau aplicația noastră mobilă, interacționați cu paginile noastre de rețele sociale, postați o recenzie sau o mărturie, trimiteți conținut în grupuri de discuție online sau introduceți în orice alt mod informații în câmpuri de comentarii publice, bloguri sau forumuri comunitare sponsorizate de TMG sau afiliate la TMG, este posibil să colectăm, să primim și să păstrăm înregistrări ale detaliilor dvs. de contact, comunicări și interacțiuni, postările sau trimiterile dvs., și răspunsurile noastre, dacă este cazul.
    
* **Informații promoționale** . Dacă sunteți de acord să primiți comunicări de marketing de la noi, este posibil să colectăm numele dvs., adresa de e-mail, numărul de telefon, preferințe și, dacă este relevant, informații despre contul și profilul dvs., inclusiv serviciile și caracteristicile pe care le utilizați. Dacă participați la activități speciale, oferte, programe sau promoții pe care le oferim, este posibil să colectăm, de asemenea, anumite detalii de contact, vârsta dvs. și orice alte informații care ar putea fi cerute de lege. În cazul în care câștigați o promoție, este posibil să fie nevoie, de asemenea, să colectăm anumite informații fiscale și/sau derogări și exonerări, în funcție de premiu.
    
* **Răspunsuri și feedback** . Dacă participați la sondaje, anchete sau activități de cercetare sau inițiative desfășurate de noi, cum ar fi cele pentru satisfacția utilizatorilor sau alte scopuri similare, este posibil să colectăm răspunsurile și feedback-ul dvs. și orice alte informații pe care alegeți să le furnizați.
    
* **Evenimente și detalii de înregistrare** . De asemenea, putem colecta informații personale legate de participarea dvs. la evenimentele noastre, precum și alte solicitări pe care ni le trimiteți legate de serviciile noastre. De exemplu, dacă vă înregistrați sau participați la un eveniment pe care îl găzduim sau îl sponsorizăm, este posibil să colectăm informații legate de înregistrarea dvs. pentru și participarea la un astfel de eveniment.
    
* **Preferințe și alte cereri** . De asemenea, putem colecta informații despre preferințele dvs., inclusiv preferințele de comunicare, preferințe legate de utilizarea de către dvs. a serviciilor noastre și orice alte preferințe sau cereri pe care le furnizați atunci când interacționați cu noi.

În general, nu aveți obligația să ne furnizați informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal. Cu toate acestea, utilizarea anumitor servicii sau aspecte ale serviciilor noastre poate necesita furnizarea de informații cu caracter personal, de exemplu, înregistrarea pentru un cont Tagged. Dacă acesta este cazul, vă vom indica acest lucru. Dacă nu doriți să ne furnizați informațiile necesare, din păcate nu veți putea utiliza serviciul respectiv.

**Informații cu caracter personal colectate de la terți** . De asemenea, este posibil să colectăm și să primim anumite informații cu caracter personal despre dvs. din surse terțe, cum ar fi de la parteneri de afaceri, în special atunci când folosim furnizori de magazine de aplicații pentru achiziții, alți utilizatori TMG, furnizori de analiză a datelor și marketing, sisteme de operare și platforme de rețele sociale , în special atunci când se utilizează funcțiile de conectare descrise mai sus. În plus, este posibil să colectăm următoarele informații din surse terțe:

* **Informații privind înregistrarea pe rețelele sociale și pe platforme** . În timp ce utilizați serviciile noastre, puteți alege să partajați informații sau conținut, să vă autentificați sau să vă conectați la servicii prin diverse platforme de rețele sociale, servicii de rețele sociale sau alte caracteristici terțe sau servicii integrate. Când vă conectați la serviciile noastre folosind conturile dvs. de rețele sociale sau alte servicii integrate și funcții similare, este posibil să colectăm sau să primim informații cu caracter personal despre dvs. pe care le-ați furnizat contului, serviciului sau funcției rețelei sociale respective. De exemplu, putem colecta informații din contul dvs. și din profilul dvs., cum ar fi numele dvs., e-mailul, ID-ul de utilizator, poza de profil, lista de prieteni și alte informații similare disponibile în profilul dvs. Trebuie să vă verificați setările de confidențialitate pe fiecare platformă, funcție sau serviciu integrat de rețele sociale pentru a înțelege mai bine cum informațiile dvs. personale pot fi utilizate, dezvăluite sau prelucrate în alt mod de către aceste părți.
    
* **Informații cu privire la recomandare.** Vă putem oferi posibilitatea de a invita prieteni sau de a recomanda altor utilizatori să acceseze sau să utilizeze serviciile noastre. Făcând acest lucru, este posibil să colectăm și să primim anumite informații cu caracter personal despre dvs., inclusiv de la alți utilizatori actuali sau potențiali TMG și de la utilizatori și clienți care se angajează în mod similar în aceste activități.

**Informații cu caracter personal colectate automat** . Noi și furnizorii noștri de servicii terți putem colecta sau obține automat informații cu caracter personal despre dvs. legate de utilizarea serviciilor noastre, inclusiv prin utilizarea modulelor cookie, etichetelor de pixeli și a altor tehnologii similare. Informațiile cu caracter personal pe care le putem colecta automat includ:

* **Informații despre dispozitiv și navigare** . Când utilizați serviciile noastre, este posibil să colectăm tipul de browser, numele domeniului, vizualizările paginii, orele de acces, înregistrări de dată/oră, sistemul de operare, limba, tipul de dispozitiv, ID unic, furnizorul de servicii de internet, adresele URL de trimitere și de ieșire, date despre fluxul de clicuri, dispozitive similare și informații de navigare.
    
* **Activități și utilizare** . De asemenea, este posibil să colectăm informații despre activitate legate de utilizarea de către dvs. a serviciilor, cum ar fi informații despre link-urile pe care ați făcut clic, căutări, caracteristici utilizate, articole vizualizate, timpul petrecut în cadrul serviciilor, interacțiunile dvs. cu noi și alții din cadrul serviciilor și alte informații similare despre activitate și utilizare.
    
* **Informații despre locație** . De asemenea, este posibil să colectăm sau să obținem informații generale legate de locația dvs., cum ar fi prin adresa dvs. IP.

Pentru mai multe informații despre utilizarea modulelor cookie și a altor tehnologii similare, vă rugăm să consultați secțiunea 6. Module cookie, direcționare și analiză de mai jos.

**3\. Scopuri de colectare și prelucrare**

În general, este posibil să colectăm, să folosim, să dezvăluim și să prelucrăm în orice alt mod categorii de informații cu caracter personal pe care le colectăm în următoarele scopuri:

* **Servicii și asistență** . Pentru a furniza și opera serviciile noastre (de exemplu, Tagged sau jocul Pets), a vă gestiona contul, a comunica cu dvs. despre utilizarea serviciilor, a oferi depanare, asistență tehnică sau pentru scopuri similare de asistență și pentru a răspunde întrebărilor dvs., a vă îndeplini cererile, a facilita procesarea plăților și pentru a ne desfășura operațiunile de zi cu zi. Aceasta include ca unele dintre informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal, cum ar fi ID-ul de utilizator, numele de utilizator, detaliile de contact, așa cum sunt selectate în setările de confidențialitate, să fie vizibile pentru utilizatorii serviciului respectiv sau ai celorlalte servicii ale noastre și alte aplicații pe care le deținem și alte aplicații și site-uri web care nu ne aparțin și cu care partajăm platforma noastră live. TMG se bazează pe temeiul juridic „executarea unui contract” (art. 6 (1) (b) din GDPR și GDPR din Regatul Unit și art. 31 (2) (b) nDSG). În măsura în care prelucrăm informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal pentru a le face vizibile utilizatorilor altor servicii, precum și altor aplicații pe care le deținem și altor aplicații și site-uri web care nu ne aparțin și cu care partajăm platforma noastră live, TMG se bazează pe „executarea unui contract" (art. 6 (1) (b) din GDPR și GDPR din Regatul Unit și art. 31 (2) (b) nDSG).

În ceea ce privește datele de localizare, TMG se bazează pe consimțământul dvs. (art. 6 (1) (a), art. 7 GDPR).

În ceea ce privește orientarea sexuală, TMG se bazează pe consimțământul dvs. explicit (art. 6 (1) (a), art. 7, art. 9 (2) (a) GDPR/GDPR din Regatul Unit) sau pe excepția de la art. 9 (2) (e) GDPR/GDPR din Regatul Unit, cu condiția ca dvs. să fi dezvăluit public orientarea dvs. sexuală (de exemplu, într-un flux live).

* **Analiză și îmbunătățire** . Pentru a înțelege mai bine modul în care utilizatorii accesează și utilizează serviciile și în alte scopuri de cercetare și analiză, cum ar fi evaluarea și îmbunătățirea site-ului, a serviciilor și a operațiunilor noastre de afaceri, inclusiv pentru a dezvolta serviciile și funcțiile acestora și pentru controlul intern al calității și în scopuri de instruire. TMG se bazează pe temeiul juridic „interese legitime” (art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR/GDPR din Regatul Unit și art. 31 (1) nDSG). În acest sens, TMG își urmărește interesul de a înțelege cum funcționează serviciul dintr-o perspectivă de afaceri.

**Comunicare** . Pentru a răspunde întrebărilor dvs., trimiteți materialele solicitate, precum și informații și materiale referitoare la serviciile și ofertele noastre. De asemenea, este posibil să folosim aceste informații pentru a vă trimite informații administrative, de exemplu, informații referitoare la servicii și modificări ale termenilor, condițiilor și politicilor noastre. TMG se bazează pe temeiul juridic „executarea unui contract” (art. 6 (1) (b) GDPR/GDPR din Regatul Unit și art. 31 (2) (a) nDSG) sau - în cazul în care nu există niciun contract între utilizatorul relevant și TMG -- „interese legitime” (art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR/GDPR din Regatul Unit și art. 31 (1) nDSG). Acolo unde TMG se bazează pe „interese legitime”, TMG își urmărește interesele de a oferi asistență, precum și de a răspunde solicitărilor pentru a asigura satisfacția utilizatorilor.

* **Configurare și personalizare** . Pentru a personaliza conținutul, este posibil să trimitem sau să afișăm în servicii, inclusiv pentru a facilita configurarea locației și pentru a vă personaliza altfel experiențele și ofertele. TMG se bazează pe temeiul juridic „executarea unui contract” (art. 6 (1) (b) din GDPR și GDPR din Regatul Unit și art. 31 (2) (b) nDSG.
    
* Mediile sociale și alte platforme de comunicare. Pentru a vă permite să împărtășiți informații sau conținut, să vă autentificați sau să vă conectați la servicii prin intermediul diverselor platforme de socializare, servicii de rețele sociale, sau alte caracteristici sau servicii integrate ale terților. În ceea ce privește posibilitatea de a vă autentifica sau de a vă conecta la servicii, TMG se bazează pe temeiul juridic „executarea unui contract” (art. 6 (1) (b) din GDPR și GDPR din Regatul Unit și art. 31 (2) (b) nDSG). Altfel, TMG se bazează pe temeiul juridic „interese legitime” (art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR/GDPR din Regatul Unit și art. 31 (1) nDSG). În acest sens, TMG își urmărește interesul de a permite utilizatorilor să inițieze anumite comunicări cu platforme de socializare, servicii de rețele sociale sau alte caracteristici sau servicii integrate terțe, dacă acest lucru este ceea ce doresc să facă.
    
* **Marketing și publicitate** . Pentru marketing, publicitate și scopuri promoționale. De exemplu, pentru a vă trimite informații promoționale despre serviciile noastre, inclusiv buletine informative, informații despre evenimentele TMG, seminarii web, prezentări, vânzări, oferte, reduceri și oferte noi, precum și orice alte informații la care vă înscrieți pentru a le primi. TMG se bazează pe temeiul juridic „consimțământ” (art. 6 (1) (a), art. 7 GDPR și GDPR din Regatul Unit și art. 31 (1) nDSG.

În scopuri de auto-reclamă / marketing direct prin e-mailuri promoționale și/sau mesaje push, sondaje (utilizator) și ghiduri individualizate (exclusiv produse TMG). (Temeiul legal este interesul legitim al TMG în marketingul direct pentru propriile produse, precum și secțiunea 7 (3) din Legea germană împotriva concurenței neloiale (UWG)).

* **Cercetări și sondaje** . Pentru a administra sondaje și chestionare, cum ar fi pentru cercetarea pieței, satisfacția utilizatorilor sau alte scopuri similare. TMG se bazează pe temeiul juridic „consimțământ” (art. 6 (1) (a), art. 7 GDPR și GDPR din Regatul Unit și art. 31 (1) nDSG.
    
* **Dezvoltarea perspectivei și îmbunătățirea datelor** . Este posibil să combinăm informații cu caracter personal colectate prin intermediul serviciilor cu alte informații pe care noi sau terți le colectăm despre dvs. în alte contexte. În cele mai multe cazuri, informațiile pe care le putem combina cu informațiile cu caracter personal colectate prin intermediul serviciilor de cercetare de piață, cum ar fi informațiile demografice, nu identifică în mod direct consumatorii. TMG se bazează pe temeiul juridic „interese legitime” (art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR/GDPR din Regatul Unit și art. 31 (1) nDSG). În acest sens, TMG își urmărește interesul de a înțelege cum funcționează serviciul din perspectiva afacerii.
    
* **Accesul și stocarea informațiilor pe dispozitivul final al utilizatorilor.** Este posibil să accesăm sau să stocăm informații pe dispozitivul dvs. TMG se bazează pe temeiul juridic al „consimțământului” art. 5 (3) Directiva e-Privacy și PECR Reg. 6(4) atunci când acest lucru nu este strict necesar pentru funcționarea site-ului nostru web, precum și pentru furnizarea serviciilor de telemedia solicitate expres de utilizator.
    
* **Planificarea și gestionarea evenimentelor** . Pentru planificarea evenimentelor și alte scopuri legate de management, cum ar fi înregistrarea la eveniment și participarea, conectarea dvs. cu alți participanți la evenimente și utilizatori TMG, și contactarea dvs. cu privire la evenimente relevante, prezentări și serviciile noastre. De asemenea, este posibil să folosim informații cu caracter personal în scopul de a facilita evenimente speciale, tombole, concursuri și promoții, care pot avea propriile reguli specifice de participare. TMG se bazează pe temeiul juridic „consimțământ” (art. 6 (1) (a), art. 7 GDPR și GDPR din Regatul Unit și art. 31 (1) nDSG.
    
* **Securitatea și protecția drepturilor** . Pentru a proteja serviciile și operațiunile noastre de afaceri, drepturile noastre și ale părților interesate și ale investitorilor noștri, pentru a preveni și detecta frauda, accesul și activitățile neautorizate și alte utilizări greșite ale site-ului nostru, inclusiv acolo unde considerăm că este necesar să investigăm, să prevenim sau să luăm măsuri privind activitățile ilegale, frauda suspectată, situații care implică potențiale amenințări la adresa siguranței sau a drepturilor legale ale oricărei persoane sau terțe părți sau încălcări ale Termenilor și condițiilor noastre. TMG se bazează pe temeiul juridic „interese legitime” (art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR/GDPR din Regatul Unit și art. 31 (1) nDSG). Interesul legitim al TMG și al utilizatorilor TMG ca serviciul TMG să nu fie utilizat abuziv pentru acte contractuale și/sau ilegale ale terților. Interesul nostru legitim este, de asemenea, protecția propriilor noastre sisteme de securizare IT a TMG și, astfel, în ultimă instanță, protecția datelor cu caracter personal ale utilizatorilor TMG. În ceea ce privește orientarea sexuală, TMG se bazează, în plus, pe stabilirea temeiului legal, exercitarea sau apărarea pretențiilor legale (art. 9 (2) (f) GDPR/GDPR din Regatul Unit).
    
* **Conformitatea și procesul legal** . Pentru a respecta obligațiile legale sau de reglementare aplicabile, inclusiv obligațiile statutare de păstrare sau ca parte a unei proceduri judiciare, pentru a răspunde la o citație, mandat, ordin judecătoresc sau alt proces legal sau ca parte a unei investigații sau cereri, fie formală sau informală, de la forțele de ordine sau de la o autoritate guvernamentală. TMG se bazează pe temeiul juridic al (i) „respectării obligațiilor legale” (art. 6 (1) (c) GDPR/GDPR din Regatul Unit , precum și art. 31 (2) (a) nDSG), dacă această obligație provine din legislația UE sau state membre ale UE sau (ii) „interes legitim” (art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR/GDPR din Regatul Unit precum și art. 31(1) nDSG), dacă această obligație provine din alte jurisdicții. În cazul în care interesele legitime sunt relevante, TMG își urmărește interesele în îndeplinirea obligațiilor legale cărora le este supusă TMG. În ceea ce privește orientarea sexuală, TMG se bazează, în plus, pe stabilirea temeiului legal, exercitarea sau apărarea pretențiilor legale (art. 9 (2) (f) GDPR/GDPR din Regatul Unit).
    
* **Audit, raportare și alte operațiuni interne** . Pentru a efectua audituri financiare, fiscale și contabile, audituri și evaluări ale operațiunilor noastre, inclusiv controale de confidențialitate, securitate și financiare, precum și în scopuri de risc și conformitate. De asemenea, este posibil să folosim informații cu caracter personal pentru a menține înregistrări comerciale adecvate și pentru a ne aplica politicile și procedurile. TMG se bazează pe temeiul juridic „interese legitime” (art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR/GDPR din Regatul Unit și art. 31 (1) nDSG). Interesul legitim al TMG este de a proteja operațiunile de afaceri și de a verifica periodic dacă obligațiile de raportare și conformitate sunt îndeplinite.
    
* **Asistență generală de afaceri și operațională** . Pentru a evalua și a pune în aplicare fuziuni, achiziții, reorganizări, falimente și alte tranzacții comerciale, cum ar fi finanțările, precum și pentru a ne administra afacerile, contabilitatea, auditul, conformitatea, păstrarea înregistrărilor și funcțiile juridice. TMG se bazează pe temeiul juridic „interes legitim” (art. 6(1)(f) DSGVO și art. 31(1) nDSG). În acest context, TMG are interes să dezvăluie și să prelucreze în orice alt mod informații despre activele și activitățile sale către potențialii cumpărători sau achizitori și consilierii externi ai acestora, pentru a facilita vânzarea acelor active și/sau activități.

Scopurile urmărite de noi în legătură cu utilizarea modulelor cookie și a tehnologiilor similare, în special în ceea ce privește direcționarea și analiza sunt descrise în secțiunea 6. Module cookie, direcționare și analiză.

Atunci când temeiul legal pentru prelucrare este consimțământul dvs., aveți dreptul să vă retrageți consimțământul în orice moment. Totuși, această retragere nu va afecta legalitatea niciunei prelucrări efectuate pe baza consimțământului dvs. înainte de retragere. Dacă temeiul legal este un interes legitim, aveți și dreptul, în general, de a vă opune prelucrării datelor dvs. cu caracter personal, în orice moment, din motive ce decurg din situația dvs specifică. În plus, aveți dreptul de a vă opune în orice moment prelucrării datelor dvs. cu caracter personal în scopuri de marketing direct. Articolul 21 GDPR / GDPR din Regatul Unit se aplică în acest sens.

Vă puteți opune utilizării de către noi a adresei dvs. de e-mail în scopuri promoționale sau pentru îndrumare personală, la înregistrare sau ulterior, în orice moment.

**4\. Dezvăluiri de informații personale**

Este posibil să dezvăluim informațiile cu caracter personal pe care le colectăm în scopurile descrise mai sus, pentru a vă furniza serviciile noastre, pentru a răspunde și a îndeplini solicitările dvs., conform indicațiilor sau a consimțământului dvs., și cu următorii destinatari:

* **Mărci, afiliați și filiale** . Este posibil să dezvăluim informații cu caracter personal pe care le colectăm cu mărcile noastre, companii afiliate și filiale.
    
* **Parteneri de afaceri** . În anumite circumstanțe, TMG se poate asocia cu alte companii pentru a-și oferi serviciile, inclusiv pentru a facilita anumite programe sau oferte speciale și este posibil să dezvăluim informații cu caracter personal acelor parteneri de afaceri.
    
* **Furnizori și prestatori de servicii** . Este posibil să dezvăluim informațiile cu caracter personal pe care le colectăm furnizorilor și prestatorilor de servicii care îndeplinesc funcții în numele nostru, cum ar fi găzduirea de site-uri web și IT, procesatori de plăți, furnizori de cercetare de marketing și marketing, asistență pentru clienți, stocare de date, furnizori de analiză a datelor, auditori, consultanți, consilieri si agenți, consilieri juridici.
    
* **Alți utilizatori TMG** . Cu alți utilizatori ai serviciilor în contextul unor caracteristici specifice care sunt de natură socială. De exemplu, dacă invitați alte persoane să folosească serviciile noastre sau dacă trimiteți sau puneți la dispoziție informații prin intermediul funcțiilor noastre publice, interactive, forumurilor comunitare sau blogurilor de discuții, inclusiv atunci când postați recenzii sau mărturii, anumite informații cu caracter personal, pot fi disponibile și pot fi căutate de către alți utilizatori ai serviciilor. De exemplu, dacă participați la Pets, alți utilizatori ai jocului Pets vor putea vedea informații cu caracter personal, cum ar fi fotografii de profil, sex, valoare, numerar, activele deținute și numărul de Pets.
    
* **Furnizori terți de marketing și analize** . De asemenea, putem dezvălui informațiile dumneavoastră cu caracter personal, cum ar fi dispozitivul și navigarea și informații despre activități și utilizare, către furnizori terți de marketing și analize de date și altor companii care furnizează servicii de marketing, publicitate, management de campanii sau analize în numele nostru. Pentru o prezentare detaliată a anumitor destinatari, consultați Platforma noastră de gestionare a consimțământului din aplicație.

De asemenea, este posibil să dezvăluim informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal în următoarele circumstanțe:

* **În sprijinul transferurilor de afaceri** . Dacă noi sau afiliații noștri suntem sau am putea fi achiziționați, am putea fuziona sau beneficia de investiții de la o altă companie, sau dacă oricare dintre activele noastre sunt sau ar putea fi transferate unei alte companii, fie ca parte a unei proceduri de faliment sau de insolvență sau în alt mod, este posibil să dezvăluim sau să transferăm informațiile cu caracter personal pe care le-am colectat de la dvs. cu sau către cealaltă companie, în conformitate cu legile aplicabile. De asemenea, este posibil să dezvăluim anumite informații cu caracter personal, după cum este necesar, înainte de finalizarea unei astfel de tranzacții sau alte tranzacții corporative, cum ar fi o finanțare sau restructurare, către creditori, auditori și consilieri terți, inclusiv avocați și consultanți.
    
* **Conformitatea și obligațiile legale** . De asemenea, este posibil să dezvăluim informații cu caracter personal unor terți în măsura în care este cerut de legislația aplicabilă și obligațiile legale. De exemplu, este posibil să dezvăluim informații ca răspuns la citații, hotărâri judecătorești și alte solicitări legale din partea autorităților de reglementare, entităților guvernamentale și organelor de aplicare a legii, inclusiv ca răspuns la cerințele de securitate națională sau de dezvăluire a informațiilor de către autoritățile de aplicare a legii sau ca urmare a altor cerințe legale sau a unui proces legal. În plus, și dacă este cazul, putem dezvălui numele câștigătorilor la tombole și concursuri, în conformitate cu legea aplicabilă.
    
* **Securitatea și protecția drepturilor** . Acolo unde credem că acest lucru este necesar pentru a proteja serviciile, drepturile și proprietatea noastră sau drepturile, proprietatea și siguranța altora. De exemplu, este posibil să dezvăluim informații cu caracter personal pentru (i) a preveni, a detecta, a investiga și a răspunde fraudelor, activităților și accesului neautorizat, activităților ilegale și utilizării greșite a serviciilor, (ii) situații care implică potențiale amenințări la adresa sănătății, siguranței sau drepturilor legale ale persoanelor sau părților terțe sau (iii) a impune, a detecta, a investiga și a lua măsuri ca răspuns la încălcările Termenilor și condițiilor noastre. De asemenea, este posibil să dezvăluim informații cu caracter personal legate de litigii și alte revendicări legale sau proceduri în care suntem implicați, precum și pentru contabilitatea internă, auditul, conformitatea, păstrarea evidențelor și funcțiile legale.
    
* **Alte dezvăluiri** . Este posibil să dezvăluim informații cu caracter personal în alte moduri care nu sunt descrise mai sus, despre care vă informăm sau pentru care obținem consimțământul dvs. sau care sunt autorizate sau impuse de lege.

Indiferent de orice altceva descris în această politică, este posibil să folosim și să dezvăluim date agregate, ce nu pot duce la identificare și alte date ce nu pot duce la identificare legate de afacerea noastră și de servicii pentru controlul calității, analiză, cercetare, dezvoltare și alte scopuri. În cazul în care folosim, dezvăluim sau procesăm date ce nu pot duce la identificare (date care nu mai sunt legate în mod rezonabil sau care nu mai pot fi legate de o persoană fizică identificată sau identificabilă, o gospodărie sau un dispozitiv personal sau de uz casnic), vom păstra și folosi informațiile în formă ce nu pot duce la identificare și nu vom încerca să reidentificăm informațiile, decât pentru a determina dacă procesele noastre de eliminare a procesului de identificare sunt rezonabile și adecvate în conformitate cu legile de confidențialitate aplicabile.

**5\. Transferuri de date cu caracter personal în contextul țărilor situate în afara SEE/UK/CH**

Destinatarii datelor cu caracter personal pot fi localizați în afara SEE/UK/Elveția. În cazul în care datele cu caracter personal sunt transferate în locații din afara SEE/UK/Elveția (care include transferuri de la noi în SUA în calitate de operator în domeniul de aplicare al GDPR / GDPR din Regatul Unit / nDSG către destinatari din SUA sau alte țări din afara SEE/UK/Elveția, care nu intră în domeniul de aplicare al GDPR / GDPR din Regatul Unit / nDSG), ne vom asigura, conform legii, că drepturile dvs. de confidențialitate sunt protejate în mod adecvat, fie deoarece Comisia Europeană a decis că țara în care datele sunt transferate asigură un nivel adecvat de protecție (art. 45 GDPR / GDPR din Regatul Unit), fie transferul face obiectul unor garanții adecvate (de exemplu, clauzele standard de protecție a datelor ale Uniunii Europene convenite cu destinatarul) (art. 46 GDPR / GDPR din Regatul Unit), cu excepția cazului în care GDPR / GDPR din Regatul Unit prevede o excepție (art. 49 GDPR / GDPR din Regatul Unit). În plus, intenționăm, acolo unde este cazul, să cădem de acord asupra unor măsuri suplimentare cu destinatarii pentru a asigura un nivel adecvat de protecție a datelor . Vedeți și art. 16 f. nDSG cu privire la dezvăluirea datelor cu caracter personal în afara Elveției.

Dacă este necesar, încheiem, de asemenea, o „Anexă UK” corespunzătoare cu partenerii noștri contractuali, în conformitate cu cerințele Biroului Comisarului pentru Informații (ICO) și o „Anexă CH ” corespunzătoare, în conformitate cu cerințele Comisarului Federal Elvețian pentru Protecția Datelor și Informațiilor (FDPIC).

Copii ale garanțiilor adecvate (în măsura în care ne bazăm pe acestea) și o listă a destinatarilor aflați în afara SEE/UK/Elveția pot fi solicitate de la [support@themeetgroup.com](mailto:support@themeetgroup.com). Vă rugăm să rețineți că o astfel de copie poate fi redactată în măsura în care este necesar pentru a proteja secretele de afaceri sau alte informații confidențiale.

**6\. Module cookie, direcționare și analize**

Noi și furnizorii noștri de servicii terți folosim module cookie, pixeli, obiecte de stocare locale, fișiere jurnal și alte mecanisme de urmărire pentru a colecta automat informații de navigare, activitate, dispozitiv și alte informații similare în cadrul serviciilor noastre. Folosim aceste informații pentru a analiza și înțelege modul în care utilizatorii accesează, utilizează și interacționează cu serviciile noastre, pentru a identifica și rezolva greșeli și erori în serviciile noastre, pentru a evalua securitatea, a proteja, optimiza și îmbunătăți performanța serviciilor noastre, cât și în scopuri de marketing și analiză și pentru a personaliza conținutul în serviciile noastre. În funcție de locația dvs., cele mai multe dintre acestea vor avea loc doar dacă v-ați dat consimțământul utilizând CMP-ul nostru, pe care îl puteți găsi în setările aplicației dvs. de gestionare a consimțământului / preferințelor cu privire la module cookie, publicitate direcționată și alte mecanisme de urmărire similare în cadrul serviciilor noastre, consultați secțiunea 7. Opțiunile dvs. de confidențialitate sunt mai jos. Multe dintre aceste opțiuni sunt specifice browserului și dispozitivului, ceea ce înseamnă că poate fi necesar să setați preferința pentru fiecare browser și dispozitiv pe care îl utilizați pentru a accesa serviciile noastre. În plus, dacă ștergeți sau blocați module cookie, poate fi necesar să aplicați din nou aceste preferințe pentru fiecare browser și/sau dispozitiv.

**Module cookie** . „Modulele cookie” sunt fișiere text mici stocate pe dispozitivul unui utilizator (cum ar fi un computer sau un smartphone) de către un site web pe care îl vizitează. Modulele cookie sunt create de serverul site-ului web și trimise către browser-ul utilizatorului, unde sunt stocate pentru referințe ulterioare. Unele module cookie ne permit să vă facilităm navigarea prin serviciile noastre, în timp ce altele sunt utilizate, de exemplu, pentru a permite un proces de conectare mai rapid, pentru a sprijini securitatea și performanța serviciilor sau ne permit să urmărim informații agregate și statistice despre activitatea utilizatorilor în cadrul serviciilor.

**Etichete de pixeli** . Etichetele de pixeli (uneori numite balize web sau GIF-uri transparente) sunt mici elemente grafice, cu un identificator unic, similare ca funcții cu modulele cookie. În timp ce modulele cookie sunt stocate local pe dispozitivul dvs., etichetele de pixeli sunt încorporate în paginile web și în conținutul online. Este posibil să le folosim în legătură cu serviciile noastre, printre altele, pentru a urmări activitățile utilizatorilor și pentru a ne ajuta să gestionăm conținutul și să compilăm statistici de utilizare. De asemenea, este posibil să le folosim în e-mailurile noastre pentru a afla când au fost deschise sau redirecționate acestea, astfel încât să putem urmări ratele de răspuns și să măsurăm eficacitatea comunicărilor noastre.

**Fișiere jurnal** . Este posibil să colectăm anumite informații despre activitate din fișierele jurnal. Informațiile din fișierul jurnal sunt colectate automat atunci când accesați site-urile noastre. Înregistrăm anumite informații din aceste fișiere jurnal, inclusiv solicitări web, adresa IP, tipul și versiunea browserului, informațiile privind limba, adresele URL de referință și de ieșire, linkurile pe care s-a făcut clic, paginile vizualizate și alte informații similare.

**Analize efectuate de părți terțe** . Este posibil să folosim dispozitive, aplicații și instrumente automate, cum ar fi Google Analytics, care sunt operate de companii terțe, pentru a evalua utilizarea serviciilor noastre. Aceste companii terțe pot folosi module cookie, pixeli și alte tehnologii de urmărire pentru a colecta date de utilizare despre serviciile noastre și pentru a ne furniza rapoarte și măsurători care ne ajută să evaluăm utilizarea serviciilor noastre și să îmbunătățim performanța și experiența utilizatorului. Pentru a afla mai multe despre practicile de confidențialitate ale Google, consultați Politica de confidențialitate Google la [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). De asemenea, puteți descărca Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on pentru a preveni utilizarea datelor dvs. de către Google Analytics la [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). O listă a terților angajați de noi în acest sens poate fi găsită în CMP-ul nostru, pe care îl puteți găsi în setările aplicației dvs.

**Publicitate efectuată de părți terțe** . Lucrăm cu rețele publicitare terță parte, parteneri de marketing, rețele publicitare mobile și altele („companii publicitare terță parte”) pentru a personaliza conținutul și a afișa reclame în cadrul serviciilor noastre, precum și pentru a ne gestiona publicitatea pe site-uri web ale terților. Noi și aceste companii de publicitate terță parte putem folosi module cookie, etichete de pixeli, SDK-uri (kituri de dezvoltare software) și alte instrumente pentru a colecta informații de navigare și de activitate în cadrul serviciilor noastre (precum și pe site-urile și serviciile terților), precum și adresa IP, ID-ul unic, module cookie și ID-uri de publicitate și alți identificatori online. Noi și aceste companii de publicitate terță parte utilizăm aceste informații pentru a vă oferi reclame și conținut mai relevant în cadrul serviciilor noastre și pe site-urile terțelor părți și pentru a evalua succesul acestor reclame și a conținutului. O listă a companiilor de publicitate terță parte poate fi găsită în CMP-ul nostru, pe care îl puteți găsi în setările aplicației dvs.

**Utilizare pe mai multe dispozitive** . Noi și furnizorii noștri de servicii terți putem folosi informațiile pe care le colectăm despre dvs. (fie direct de pe site-urile noastre sau din aplicația mobilă, prin intermediul dispozitivului (dispozitivelor) dvs. sau din surse terțe) pentru a ne ajuta pe noi și pe furnizorii noștri de servicii terți să identificăm alte dispozitive pe care le utilizați (de exemplu, un telefon mobil, o tabletă, un alt computer etc.). Noi și furnizorii noștri de servicii terți putem folosi, de asemenea, utilizarea pe mai multe dispozitive și alte informații pe care le aflăm despre dvs. pentru a difuza publicitate direcționată sau pentru a personaliza conținutul în cadrul serviciilor noastre.

**Liste de clienți și potrivire** . Este posibil să partajăm sau să punem la dispoziție anumite informații din lista de clienți (cum ar fi numele dvs., adresa de e-mail și alte informații de contact) unor terțe părți, astfel încât să putem direcționa mai bine către dvs. anunțurile și conținutul de pe site-uri web, platforme și servicii terțe. În unele cazuri, aceste terțe părți ne pot ajuta să îmbunătățim listele noastre de clienți cu informații demografice suplimentare sau alte informații similare, astfel încât să putem viza mai bine campaniile noastre de publicitate și marketing.

**7\. Opțiunile dvs. de confidențialitate**

**Gestionarea preferințelor dvs** . Vă punem la dispoziție mai multe moduri de a vă gestiona preferințele și opțiunile de confidențialitate, după cum se descrie mai jos:

* **Contul și profilul** . Puteți revizui și actualiza unele dintre informațiile cu caracter personal pe care le păstrăm despre dvs. conectându-vă la cont și actualizându-vă informațiile despre contul și profilul dvs.
    
* **Comunicări de marketing** . Vă putem trimite periodic e-mailuri promoționale, conținut sau alte comunicări similare. Puteți renunța la aceste comunicări urmând instrucțiunile furnizate în comunicare. Dacă renunțați să primiți conținut promoțional de la noi, este posibil să vă trimitem în continuare comunicări despre contul dvs. sau despre orice servicii pe care le-ați solicitat sau primit de la noi. În plus, vă puteți gestiona preferințele de comunicare în setările contului și profilului dvs.
    
* **Notificări push** . Puteți gestiona tipul de notificări push pe care le primiți de la noi ajustând setările dispozitivului mobil sau modificând setările din aplicația noastră mobilă. Acestea sunt mesaje pe care vi le trimitem în cursul îndeplinirii contractului, precum și informații promoționale.

**Module cookie și preferințe de urmărire/Publicitate direcționată/Analiză** . De asemenea, vă punem la dispoziție mai multe modalități de a vă gestiona preferințele cu privire la modulele cookie, publicitate direcționată, analize și alte mecanisme de urmărire în cadrul serviciilor noastre. Multe dintre aceste opțiuni sunt specifice browserului și dispozitivului, ceea ce înseamnă că poate fi necesar să setați preferința pentru fiecare browser și dispozitiv pe care îl utilizați pentru a accesa serviciile noastre. În plus, dacă ștergeți sau blocați module cookie, poate fi necesar să aplicați din nou aceste preferințe pentru fiecare browser și/sau dispozitiv. În plus, renunțarea la module cookie și publicitate nu înseamnă că nu veți mai primi conținut publicitar de la noi și este posibil să continuați să primiți reclame generice sau „contextuale” de la noi.

* **Platforma de gestionare a consimțământului (CMP).** Pentru a preveni ca modulele cookie sau mecanismele de urmărire care nu sunt strict necesare să urmărească activitatea dvs. pe site-urile noastre sau în aplicația noastră mobilă, puteți utiliza platforma de gestionare a consimțământului care este furnizată înainte ca modulele cookie și mecanismele de urmărire să fie utilizate. Odată oferit consimțământul, acesta poate fi retras în orice moment, cu efect pentru viitor. Pentru informații mai detaliate vă rugăm să consultați secțiunea 15. Informații suplimentare privind confidențialitatea pentru anumite jurisdicții, care includ informații suplimentare despre drepturile de confidențialitate pentru rezidenții anumitor jurisdicții.
    
* **Setări pentru modulele cookie** . Pentru a preveni ca modulele cookie să vă urmărească activitatea pe site-urile noastre sau la vizitele pe mai multe site-uri web, vă puteți seta browserul să blocheze anumite module cookie sau să vă anunțe când este setat un modul cookie. De asemenea, puteți șterge modulele cookie. Porțiunea „Ajutor” a barei de instrumente din majoritatea browserelor vă va spune cum să împiedicați acceptarea de module cookie noi, cum să setați browserul să vă anunțe când primiți un modul cookie nou sau cum să ștergeți modulele cookie. Vizitatorii site-urilor noastre care dezactivează modulele cookie vor putea naviga pe site, dar este posibil ca anumite caracteristici să nu funcționeze.
    
* **Semnale de browser** . În măsura cerută de legea aplicabilă, dacă site-urile noastre detectează că browserul dvs. transmite un semnal de preferință de renunțare, cum ar fi un semnal de „control global al confidențialității” (sau GPC), vom aplica acel semnal pentru a dezactiva browserul respectiv de pe dispozitivul dvs. în ceea ce privește modulele cookie de direcționare de pe site-urile noastre. Dacă accesați site-urile noastre de pe un dispozitiv diferit sau dintr-un browser diferit de pe dispozitiv, va trebui să aplicați GPC și pentru acel browser și/sau dispozitiv.
    
* **Programe pentru alegerea reclamelor din industrie** . De asemenea, puteți controla modul în care companiile de publicitate terțe participante utilizează informațiile pe care le colectează despre vizitele dvs. pe site-urile noastre și pe cele ale terților, pentru a vă afișa reclame direcționate mai relevante. Pentru informații suplimentare și asistență legată de mecanismele de urmărire web, vizitați [www.YourOnlineChoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/).

Rezidenții anumitor jurisdicții pot avea drepturi suplimentare asupra informațiilor cu caracter personal, așa cum se precizează mai jos în secțiunea 15. Informații suplimentare privind confidențialitatea pentru anumite jurisdicții.

**8\. Perioada de stocare a informațiilor personale**

Stocăm informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal atât timp cât este necesar pentru urmărirea scopurilor menționate în secțiunea 3 Scopuri de colectare și prelucrare și secțiunea 6 Module cookie, direcționare și analiză sau atât timp cât avem un interes legitim în continuarea stocării. În toate celelalte cazuri, ștergem informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal, cu excepția informațiilor pe care trebuie să le stocăm pentru a respecta perioadele legale de păstrare (de exemplu, rezultate din legislația fiscală sau comercială, cum ar fi cele referitoare la facturi). Restricționăm prelucrarea informațiilor cu caracter personal care sunt păstrate doar din cauza unei obligații de păstrare.

Informații despre durata de stocare a modulelor cookie și alte mecanisme de urmărire pot fi găsite în CMP-ul nostru, pe care îl puteți găsi în setările aplicației dvs.

**9\. Legături externe și caracteristici**

Serviciile noastre pot conține link-uri către site-uri web sau caracteristici ale terților sau pot oferi anumite conexiuni terță parte sau servicii integrate. Orice acces la și utilizarea acestor site-uri web sau caracteristici legate nu este guvernată de această Politică, ci este guvernată de politicile de confidențialitate ale acelor terți. Nu suntem responsabili pentru practicile de informare ale unor astfel de terțe părți, inclusiv colectarea, utilizarea și dezvăluirea informațiilor dvs. personale. Ar trebui să examinați politicile de confidențialitate și termenii pentru orice terță parte înainte de a accesa acele site-uri web sau de a utiliza acele funcții.

**10\. Conținut generat de utilizatori**

Putem oferi funcții interactive destinate publicului, forumuri comunitare sau bloguri de discuții în legătură cu serviciile noastre, care vă permit să împărtășiți informații despre servicii sau alte probleme de interes (de exemplu, recenzii, mărturii și întrebări). Trebuie să rețineți faptul că toate comunicările pe care le trimiteți sau le postați la oricare dintre aceste funcții interactive ale serviciilor pot fi vizualizate și căutate de alții, inclusiv de utilizatorii TMG și de public. Prin trimiterea sau postarea pe astfel de funcții interactive, destinate publicului, recunoașteți că nu aveți așteptări privind intimitatea sau confidențialitatea în conținutul pe care îl trimiteți pentru astfel de funcții, indiferent dacă acesta include sau nu informații cu caracter personal despre dvs.

**11\. Securitate**

Am implementat măsuri de precauție rezonabile menite să protejeze informațiile pe care le colectăm de pierdere, utilizare greșită și acces neautorizat, dezvăluire, modificare și distrugere. Vă rugăm să rețineți că, în ciuda eforturilor noastre, nicio măsură de securitate a datelor nu poate garanta securitatea.

**12\. Confidențialitatea copiilor**

Serviciile noastre nu sunt concepute pentru copii și nu colectăm cu bună știință informații cu caracter personal de la copii sub vârsta de optsprezece ani (18). Dacă aflăm că informații cu caracter personal au fost colectate în cadrul serviciilor de la persoane sub 18 ani, atunci vom lua măsurile necesare pentru a șterge aceste informații. Dacă sunteți părinte sau tutore legal și credeți că am colectat informații ale copilului dvs., încălcând legea aplicabilă, vă rugăm să ne contactați folosind informațiile de contact de mai jos.

**13\. Modificări ale acestei politici**

Această politică este valabilă de la data menționată mai sus. Putem schimba, actualiza sau modifica această politică din când în când, așa că vă rugăm să vă asigurați că reveniți periodic pentru a verifica. Vom publica orice actualizări ale acestei politici aici. Dacă facem modificări ale acestei politici care afectează în mod considerabil practicile noastre cu privire la utilizarea de către noi a informațiilor cu caracter personal pe care le-am colectat anterior de la dvs., ne vom strădui să vă furnizăm o notificare, prin e-mail sau prin postarea unei notificări vizibile pe site-urile noastre, în aplicația noastră mobilă sau în cadrul serviciilor.

**14\. Contactați-ne**

Dacă aveți întrebări sau nelămuriri cu privire la această politică sau practicile noastre de confidențialitate, ne puteți trimite un e-mail la [support@themeetgroup.com](mailto:support@themeetgroup.com) sau ne puteți contacta la:

The Meet Group, Inc.

100 Union Square Drive

New Hope, PA 18938

Puteți contacta responsabilul nostru cu protecția datelor la:

ePrivacy GmbH reprezentată de Prof. Dr. Christoph Bauer, Große Bleichen 21, 20354 Hamburg, [privacy@themeetgroup.com](mailto:privacy@themeetgroup.com)

Pentru toate solicitările referitoare la securitatea datelor dvs., contactați responsabilul nostru cu protecția datelor la [privacy@themeetgroup.com](mailto:privacy@themeetgroup.com).

Reprezentantul nostru UE în conformitate cu art. 27 GDPR poate fi contactat la: ParshipMeet Holding GmbH, Speersort 10, 20095 Hamburg, e-mail: [privacy@parshipmeet.com](mailto:privacy@parshipmeet.com)

Detaliile reprezentantului nostru din Regatul Unit în conformitate cu articolul 27 din GDPR pentru Regatul Unit sunt stabilite în secțiunea 15.B. Informații suplimentare pentru rezidenții din Regatul Unit

Detaliile reprezentantului nostru elvețian conform art. 14 nDSG (noua lege elvețiană privind protecția datelor) sunt prevăzute în secțiunea 15.C. Informații suplimentare pentru rezidenții din Elveția.

Treforma AG c/o MLL Legal; Grabenstrasse 25; 6340 Baar; Elveția; [meetgroup@dsg-mll.com](mailto:meetgroup@dsg-mll.com)

**15\. Informații suplimentare privind confidențialitatea pentru anumite jurisdicții**

Rezidenții din anumite jurisdicții au drepturi suplimentare în conformitate cu legi aplicabile privind confidențialitatea, așa cum este descris în această secțiune.

**A. GDPR**

Dacă aveți rezidența în Uniunea Europeană, aveți drepturi conform GDPR, cu condiția ca cerințele legale din acesta să fie îndeplinite:

**Dreptul de acces** - Puteți solicita informații despre prelucrarea datelor dvs. cu caracter personal și o copie a datelor cu caracter personal în curs de prelucrare, în măsura în care această copie nu afectează în mod negativ drepturile și libertățile altora și nu se aplică nicio altă excepție.

**Dreptul la rectificare** - Puteți solicita corectarea datelor dvs. cu caracter personal care sunt inexacte și/sau completarea unor asemenea date care sunt incomplete.

**Dreptul la ștergere** - Puteți solicita ștergerea datelor cu caracter personal, în special unde

* datele cu caracter personal nu mai sunt necesare în raport cu scopurile pentru care au fost colectate sau prelucrate în alt mod;
    
* v-ați retras consimțământul pe care s-a bazat prelucrarea și nu există un alt temei legal pentru prelucrare,
    
* v-ați opus prelucrării care se bazează pe temeiul legal „interese legitime” și nu există motive legitime imperative pentru prelucrare sau v-ați opus prelucrării în scopuri de marketing direct,
    
* datele dvs. cu caracter personal au fost prelucrate ilegal sau
    
* datele dvs. cu caracter personal trebuie șterse pentru respectarea unei obligații legale la care suntem supuși.

Cu toate acestea, dreptul la ștergere nu se aplică în special în cazul în care procesarea datelor dvs. cu caracter personal este necesară pentru îndeplinirea unei obligații sau pentru stabilirea, exercitarea sau apărarea unor pretenții legale.

**Dreptul la restricționarea prelucrării** - Puteți solicita restricționarea prelucrării

* pentru perioada în care verificăm exactitatea datelor dvs. cu caracter personal dacă ați contestat acuratețea datelor cu caracter personal,
    
* în cazul în care prelucrarea este ilegală și solicitați restricționarea prelucrări în loc de ștergerea datelor,
    
* în cazul în care nu mai avem nevoie de datele cu caracter personal, dar dvs. aveți nevoie de date pentru stabilirea, exercitarea sau apărarea unor pretenții legale sau
    
* dacă v-ați opus prelucrării care se bazează pe temeiul legal „interese legitime” până când nu a fost verificat dacă motivele noastre legitime prevalează asupra intereselor, drepturilor și libertăților dvs.

**Dreptul la portabilitatea datelor** - Puteți solicita să primiți datele dvs. cu caracter personal, pe care ni le-ați furnizat, într-un format structurat, utilizat în mod obișnuit, care poate fi prelucrat pe un computer și să transmiteți acele date unui alt operator fără obstacole din partea noastră, acolo unde prelucrarea este pe baza consimțământului sau executarea unui contract și prelucrarea se realizează prin mijloace automatizate; în aceste cazuri, puteți solicita, de asemenea, ca datele cu caracter personal să fie transmise direct unui alt operator, dacă acest lucru este fezabil din punct de vedere tehnic.

În plus, aveți următoarele drepturi:

**Dreptul de a retrage consimțământul -** Vă puteți retrage consimțământul în orice moment pentru viitor, în cazul în care prelucrarea se bazează pe consimțământul dvs., fără a afecta legalitatea prelucrării bazate pe consimțământ înainte de retragerea sa.

**Dreptul de a vă opune -**

**Aveți dreptul de a vă opune, din motive legate de situația dvs. particulară, în orice moment, prelucrării datelor dvs. cu caracter personal care se bazează pe interesul legitim al nostru sau al unui terț (art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR). Atunci nu vom mai prelucra datele dvs. cu caracter personal în scopul căruia v-ați opus, cu excepția cazului în care putem demonstra motive legitime convingătoare pentru prelucrare care prevalează asupra intereselor, drepturilor și libertăților dvs. sau pentru stabilirea, exercitarea sau apărarea unor pretenții legale.**

**În plus, aveți dreptul de a vă opune în orice moment prelucrării datelor dvs. cu caracter personal în scopuri de marketing direct. În cazul în care vă opuneți prelucrării în scopuri de marketing direct, nu vom mai procesa datele dvs. cu caracter personal în astfel de scopuri.**

* * *

**Dreptul de a depune o plângere -** Puteți depune o plângere la o autoritate de supraveghere, în special în statul membru în care aveți reședința obișnuită, locul de muncă sau locul unei presupuse încălcări dacă considerați că prelucrarea datelor dvs. cu caracter personal încalcă GDPR.

Autoritatea de protecție a datelor competentă pentru noi este:

Orașul liber și hanseatic Hamburg, Comisarul Hamburg pentru Protecția Datelor și Libertatea Informației, Ludwig-Erhard-Str. 22, 20459 Hamburg, e-mail: [mailbox@datenschutz.hamburg.de](mailto:mailbox@datenschutz.hamburg.de)

**B. GDPR pentru Regatul Unit**

Dacă vă aflați în Regatul Unit, în conformitate cu GDPR și legile privind protecția datelor din Regatul Unit, aveți drepturi. Dacă și în ce măsură se aplică drepturile poate depinde de circumstanțe. Pentru a vă exercita oricare dintre aceste drepturi, vă rugăm să utilizați detaliile de contact furnizate mai jos. Drepturile sunt:

**Dreptul dvs. de a fi informat** -- Aveți dreptul de a primi informații concise, transparente, inteligibile și ușor accesibile despre datele dvs. cu caracter personal și despre utilizarea acestora. Această politică este modul nostru de a vă informa despre aceste informații, dar dacă aveți întrebări sau nelămuriri suplimentare, vă rugăm să utilizați informațiile de contact furnizate mai jos.

**Dreptul dvs. de acces** -- Aveți dreptul de a ne solicita copii ale datelor dvs. cu caracter personal. Acest drept se aplică întotdeauna, dar există câteva excepții la aplicarea sa, ceea ce înseamnă că este posibil să nu primiți întotdeauna toate informațiile pe care le-ați solicitat. Când solicitați datele dvs. cu caracter personal, acest lucru este cunoscut sub numele de efectuarea unei cereri de acces la subiectul datelor (DSAR). Este posibil să fie nevoie să vă solicităm documente de identificare pentru a vă verifica identitatea la primirea unei DSAR de la dvs.

**Dreptul dvs. la rectificare** -- Aveți dreptul să ne cereți să rectificăm datele cu caracter personal pe care le considerați inexacte. De asemenea , aveți dreptul de a ne cere să completăm informațiile pe care le considerați incomplete.

**Dreptul dvs. la ștergere** -- Aveți dreptul de a ne cere să ștergem datele dvs. cu caracter personal în anumite circumstanțe. Avem dreptul de a refuza să ne conformăm unei cereri de ștergere dacă prelucrăm datele cu caracter personal din unul dintre următoarele motive:

* Pentru exercitarea dreptului la libertatea de exprimare și informare.
    
* Pentru a respecta o obligație legală.
    
* Pentru a îndeplini o sarcină de interes public sau a exercita autoritatea oficială.
    
* În scopuri de arhivare în interes public, cercetare științifică, cercetare istorică sau scopuri statistice.
    
* Pentru exercitarea sau apărarea pretențiilor legale.

**Dreptul dvs. la restricționarea prelucrării** -- Aveți dreptul să ne cereți să restricționăm prelucrarea datelor dvs. cu caracter personal în anumite circumstanțe. În acest caz, vom păstra în continuare datele, dar nu le vom mai prelucra. Acest drept este o alternativă la dreptul la ștergere. Dacă se aplică una dintre următoarele condiții, vă puteți exercita dreptul de a restricționa prelucrarea:

* Acuratețea datelor cu caracter personal este contestată.
    
* Prelucrarea datelor cu caracter personal este ilegală.
    
* Nu mai avem nevoie de datele cu caracter personal pentru prelucrare, dar acestea sunt necesare ca parte a unui proces legal.
    
* Dreptul de a vă opune a fost exercitat și prelucrarea este restricționată în așteptarea unei decizii cu privire la stadiul prelucrării.

**Dreptul dvs. de a vă opune prelucrării -- Aveți dreptul de a vă opune prelucrării în anumite circumstanțe, inclusiv marketing direct. De asemenea, vă puteți opune dacă prelucrarea se bazează pe interesele noastre legitime (sau pe cele ale unei terțe părți). Atunci nu vom mai prelucra datele dvs. cu caracter personal în scopul căruia v-ați opus, cu excepția cazului în care putem demonstra motive legitime convingătoare pentru prelucrare care prevalează asupra intereselor, drepturilor și libertăților dvs. sau pentru stabilirea, exercitarea sau apărarea unor pretenții legale.**

**Dreptul dvs. la portabilitatea datelor** -- Acesta este dreptul de a primi datele dvs. cu caracter personal într-un format structurat, utilizat în mod obișnuit, care poate fi prelucrat pe un computer, dar se aplică numai dacă prelucrăm informații pe baza consimțământului dvs. sau pentru executarea unui contract și prelucrarea este automatizată.

**Dreptul de a retrage consimțământul -** Vă puteți retrage consimțământul în orice moment pentru viitor, în cazul în care prelucrarea se bazează pe consimțământul dvs., fără a afecta legalitatea prelucrării bazate pe consimțământ înainte de retragerea sa.

**Informații de contact**

Dacă doriți să vă exercitați oricare dintre drepturile dvs. sau dacă aveți întrebări cu privire la utilizarea de către noi a datelor dvs. cu caracter personal, vă rugăm să utilizați informațiile din meniul pentru contactare. De asemenea, vă rugăm să vă asigurați că atunci când faceți acest lucru, furnizați suficiente informații pentru a ne permite să vă identificăm în mod clar.

Rețineți că am desemnat un reprezentant în Regatului Unit pe care să îl contactați în numele nostru în conformitate cu art. 27 al GDPR din Regatul Unit: eHarmony UK Ltd., 6-10 Great Portland Street, Londra W1W 8QL, Marea Britanie

**Transferuri de informații cu caracter personal în afara Regatului Unit**

Pentru detalii privind protecția și garanțiile aplicate datelor dvs. cu caracter personal atunci când acestea sunt transferate în afara Regatului Unit, consultați secțiunea 5 Transferuri de date cu caracter personal în contextul țărilor situate în afara SEE/UK/CH, de mai sus.

**Dreptul de a depune o plângere la o autoritate de supraveghere**

Aveți dreptul de a depune o plângere la o autoritate de protecție a datelor.

Puteți contacta autoritatea de protecție a datelor din Regatul Unit, Biroul Comisarului pentru Informații, la: Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF, Număr de telefon: + 44 (0) 303 123 1113, E-mail: [casework@ico.org.uk](mailto:casework@ico.org.uk).

**C. Legea elvețiană privind protecția datelor**

**Dreptul dvs. de acces** -- Aveți dreptul de a ne solicita copii ale datelor dvs. cu caracter personal. Acest drept se aplică întotdeauna, dar există câteva excepții la aplicarea sa, ceea ce înseamnă că este posibil să nu primiți întotdeauna toate informațiile pe care le-ați solicitat. Când solicitați datele dvs. cu caracter personal, acest lucru este cunoscut sub numele de efectuarea unei cereri de acces la subiectul datelor (DSAR).

**Dreptul dvs. la rectificare** -- Aveți dreptul să ne cereți să rectificăm datele cu caracter personal pe care le considerați inexacte. De asemenea , aveți dreptul de a ne cere să completăm informațiile pe care le considerați incomplete.

**Dreptul dvs. la ștergere** -- Aveți dreptul de a ne cere să ștergem datele dvs. cu caracter personal în anumite circumstanțe. Avem dreptul de a refuza să ne conformăm unei cereri de ștergere dacă prelucrăm datele cu caracter personal din unul dintre următoarele motive:

* Pentru exercitarea dreptului la libertatea de exprimare și informare.
    
* Pentru a respecta o obligație legală.
    
* Pentru a îndeplini o sarcină de interes public sau a exercita autoritatea oficială.
    
* În scopuri de arhivare în interes public, cercetare științifică, cercetare istorică sau scopuri statistice.
    
* Pentru exercitarea sau apărarea pretențiilor legale.

**Dreptul dvs. la restricționarea prelucrării** -- Aveți dreptul să ne cereți să restricționăm prelucrarea datelor dvs. cu caracter personal în anumite circumstanțe. În acest caz, vom păstra în continuare datele, dar nu le vom mai prelucra. Acest drept este o alternativă la dreptul la ștergere. Dacă se aplică una dintre următoarele condiții, vă puteți exercita dreptul de a restricționa prelucrarea:

* Acuratețea datelor cu caracter personal este contestată.
    
* Prelucrarea datelor cu caracter personal este ilegală.
    
* Nu mai avem nevoie de datele cu caracter personal pentru prelucrare, dar acestea sunt necesare ca parte a unui proces legal.
    
* Dreptul de a vă opune a fost exercitat și prelucrarea este restricționată în așteptarea unei decizii cu privire la stadiul prelucrării.

**Dreptul dvs. de a vă opune prelucrării** -- Aveți dreptul de a vă opune prelucrării în anumite circumstanțe. De asemenea, vă puteți opune dacă prelucrarea este pentru o sarcină de interes public, exercitarea autorității oficiale care vă este învestită sau interesele noastre legitime (sau ale unui terț).

**Dreptul dvs. de a vă opune marketingului direct** - De asemenea, vă puteți opune în orice moment la prelucrarea datelor dvs. cu caracter personal în scopuri publicitare („obiecție publicitară”). Rețineți faptul că, din motive organizatorice, poate exista o suprapunere între revocarea dvs. și utilizarea datelor dvs. în contextul unei campanii deja în desfășurare.

**Dreptul dvs. la portabilitatea datelor** -- Acest drept se aplică numai dacă prelucrăm informații pe baza consimțământului dvs. sau pentru executarea unui contract și prelucrarea este automatizată.

Dacă doriți să vă exercitați oricare dintre drepturile dvs., vă rugăm să utilizați informațiile din meniul pentru contactare. De asemenea, vă rugăm să vă asigurați că atunci când faceți acest lucru, furnizați suficiente informații pentru a ne permite să vă identificăm în mod clar .

**Informații de contact**

Dacă doriți să vă exercitați oricare dintre drepturile dvs. sau dacă aveți întrebări cu privire la utilizarea de către noi a datelor dvs. cu caracter personal, vă rugăm să utilizați informațiile din meniul pentru contactare. De asemenea, vă rugăm să vă asigurați că atunci când faceți acest lucru, furnizați suficiente informații pentru a ne permite să vă identificăm în mod clar.

Rețineți că am desemnat un reprezentant elvețian la art. 14 nDSG (noua lege elvețiană privind protecția datelor): Treforma AG c/o MLL Legal; Grabenstrasse 25; 6340 Baar; Elveția; [meetgroup@dsg-mll.com](mailto:meetgroup@dsg-mll.com)

**Transferuri de informații cu caracter personal în afara Elveției**

Pentru detalii privind protecția și garanțiile aplicate datelor dvs. cu caracter personal atunci când acestea sunt transferate în afara Elveției, consultați secțiunea 5 Transferuri de date cu caracter personal în contextul țărilor situate în afara SEE/UK/CH, de mai sus.

**Dreptul de a depune o plângere la o autoritate de supraveghere**

Aveți dreptul de a depune o plângere la o autoritate de protecție a datelor.

Puteți contacta autoritatea competentă de supraveghere a protecției datelor din Elveția. Aceasta este:

Comisarului Federal pentru Protecția Datelor și Informațiilor (FDPIC).

Puteți să-i contactați la:

[https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/de/home/deredoeb/kontakt/kontaktformular\_bgoe.html](https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/de/home/deredoeb/kontakt/kontaktformular_bgoe.html)
